1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	crawler-transporter	crawler-transporter	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	will	will	MD	O	4	aux
4	carry	carry	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	rocket	rocket	NN	O	4	dobj
7	on	on	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	4.2-mile	4.2-mile	JJ	O	10	amod
10	journey	journey	NN	O	6	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	Launch	launch	VB	O	4	advcl
13	Pad	pad	NN	O	14	compound
14	39B	39b	NN	O	12	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Maine	Maine	NNP	LOCATION	4	compound
2	Senator	Senator	NNP	O	4	compound
3	Olympia	Olympia	NNP	PERSON	4	compound
4	Snowe	Snowe	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	lone	lone	JJ	O	8	amod
8	Republican	Republican	NNP	MISC	4	appos
9	in	in	IN	O	13	case
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	Senate	Senate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
12	Finance	Finance	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	Committee	Committee	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nmod
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	vote	vote	VB	O	8	acl
16	for	for	IN	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	Baucus	Baucus	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
19	bill	bill	NN	O	15	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	4	punct
21	has	have	VBZ	O	22	aux
22	said	say	VBN	O	0	ROOT
23	she	she	PRP	O	25	nsubj
24	will	will	MD	O	25	aux
25	oppose	oppose	VB	O	22	ccomp
26	any	any	DT	O	27	det
27	plan	plan	NN	O	25	dobj
28	that	that	WDT	O	29	nsubj
29	emerges	emerge	VBZ	O	27	acl:relcl
30	with	with	IN	O	34	case
31	a	a	DT	O	34	det
32	``	``	``	O	34	punct
33	public	public	JJ	O	34	amod
34	option	option	NN	O	29	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	22	punct
36	''	''	''	O	22	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	think	think	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	it	it	PRP	O	8	nsubj
4	would	would	MD	O	8	aux
5	be	be	VB	O	8	cop
6	really	really	RB	O	8	advmod
7	politically	politically	RB	O	8	advmod
8	insane	insane	JJ	O	2	ccomp
9	for	for	IN	O	10	case
10	people	people	NNS	O	8	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	take	take	VB	O	8	xcomp
13	that	that	DT	O	12	dobj
14	too	too	RB	O	15	advmod
15	literally	literally	RB	O	12	advmod
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Update	Update	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	:	:	:	O	1	punct
3	Johnny-come-lamely	johnny-come-lamely	JJ	O	5	amod
4	Newt	Newt	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Gingrich	Gingrich	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	endorses	endorse	VBZ	O	1	parataxis
7	Hoffman	Hoffman	NNP	PERSON	6	dobj
8	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Following	follow	VBG	O	4	case
2	in	in	IN	O	4	case
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	spirit	spirit	NN	O	22	advcl
5	of	of	IN	O	11	case
6	the	the	DT	O	11	det
7	``	``	``	O	11	punct
8	tea	tea	NN	O	11	compound
9	party	party	NN	O	11	compound
10	''	''	''	O	11	punct
11	protests	protest	NNS	O	4	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	April	April	NNP	DATE	11	nmod
14	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
15	the	the	DT	O	19	det
16	Glenn	Glenn	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
17	Beck-inspired	beck-inspired	JJ	PERSON	19	amod
18	9/12	9/12	CD	NUMBER	17	nmod:tmod
19	rally	rally	NN	O	11	conj
20	,	,	,	O	22	punct
21	Bachmann	Bachmann	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
22	announced	announce	VBD	O	0	ROOT
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	``	``	``	O	22	punct
25	We	we	PRP	O	27	nsubj
26	're	be	VBP	O	27	aux
27	going	go	VBG	O	22	xcomp
28	to	to	TO	O	29	mark
29	have	have	VB	O	27	xcomp
30	a	a	DT	O	33	det
31	`	`	``	O	33	punct
32	house	house	NN	O	33	compound
33	call	call	NN	O	29	dobj
34	'	'	''	O	33	punct
35	and	and	CC	O	33	cc
36	a	a	DT	O	38	det
37	big	big	JJ	O	38	amod
38	party	party	NN	O	33	conj
39	out	out	RP	O	29	advmod
40	on	on	IN	O	43	case
41	the	the	DT	O	43	det
42	National	National	NNP	LOCATION	43	compound
43	Mall	mall	NN	LOCATION	39	nmod
44	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	46	punct
45	next	next	JJ	DATE	46	amod
46	week	week	NN	DATE	43	nmod:tmod
47	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
48	,	,	,	O	27	punct
49	and	and	CC	O	27	cc
50	we	we	PRP	O	52	nsubj
51	're	be	VBP	O	52	aux
52	going	go	VBG	O	27	conj
53	to	to	TO	O	54	mark
54	tell	tell	VB	O	52	xcomp
55	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	54	dobj
56	what	what	WP	O	59	dobj
57	they	they	PRP	O	59	nsubj
58	can	can	MD	O	59	aux
59	do	do	VB	O	55	acl:relcl
60	with	with	IN	O	64	case
61	their	they	PRP$	O	64	nmod:poss
62	health	health	NN	O	64	compound
63	care	care	NN	O	64	compound
64	bill	bill	NN	O	59	nmod
65	.	.	.	O	22	punct
66	''	''	''	O	22	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	think	think	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	'll	will	MD	O	5	aux
5	live-blog	live-blog	VB	O	2	ccomp
6	Halloween	Halloween	NNP	DATE	5	dobj
7	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	You	you	PRP	O	6	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	6	aux
3	,	,	,	O	6	punct
4	of	of	IN	O	5	case
5	course	course	NN	O	6	nmod
6	read	read	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	full	full	JJ	O	9	amod
9	review	review	NN	O	6	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	Motorola	Motorola	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	Droid	Droid	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod
14	on	on	IN	O	17	case
15	our	we	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
16	reviews	review	NNS	O	17	compound
17	website	website	NN	O	6	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	well-organized	well-organized	JJ	O	3	amod
3	party	party	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	aux
5	canvassing	canvass	VBG	O	12	ccomp
6	heavily	heavily	RB	O	5	advmod
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	Northern	Northern	NNP	LOCATION	9	compound
9	Virginia	Virginia	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	12	punct
11	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
12	campaigned	campaign	VBD	O	0	ROOT
13	personally	personally	RB	O	12	advmod
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	region	region	NN	O	12	nmod
17	rich	rich	JJ	O	16	amod
18	with	with	IN	O	20	case
19	black	black	JJ	O	20	amod
20	voters	voter	NNS	O	17	nmod
21	-	-	:	O	22	punct
22	Norfolk	Norfolk	NNP	LOCATION	20	dep
23	-	-	:	O	22	punct
24	raised	raise	VBD	O	20	acl:relcl
25	money	money	NN	O	24	dobj
26	for	for	IN	O	27	case
27	Deeds	deed	NNS	O	24	nmod
28	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
29	appeared	appear	VBD	O	24	conj
30	in	in	IN	O	33	case
31	a	a	DT	O	33	det
32	television	television	NN	O	33	compound
33	commercal	commercal	NN	O	29	nmod
34	for	for	IN	O	36	case
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	candidate	candidate	NN	O	29	nmod
37	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	3Flames	3flame	NNS	O	2	nsubj
2	shot	shoot	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	more	more	JJR	O	5	advmod
4	than	than	IN	O	3	mwe
5	100	100	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	feet	foot	NNS	O	2	dobj
7	high	high	JJ	O	6	advmod
8	in	in	IN	O	14	case
9	a	a	DT	O	14	det
10	successful	successful	JJ	O	14	amod
11	5.5-second	5.5-second	JJ	DURATION	14	amod
12	ground	ground	NN	O	14	compound
13	test	test	NN	O	14	compound
14	firing	firing	NN	O	7	nmod
15	Thursday	Thursday	NNP	DATE	14	nmod:tmod
16	,	,	,	DATE	14	punct
17	Nov.	Nov.	NNP	DATE	14	dep
18	20	20	CD	DATE	17	nummod
19	,	,	,	DATE	17	punct
20	2008	2008	CD	DATE	17	nummod
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	launch	launch	NN	O	2	nmod
24	abort	abort	VB	O	2	dep
25	motor	motor	NN	O	24	dobj
26	for	for	IN	O	31	case
27	NASA	NASA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	31	nmod:poss
28	's	's	POS	O	27	case
29	next	next	JJ	O	31	amod
30	generation	generation	NN	O	31	compound
31	spacecraft	spacecraft	NN	O	24	nmod
32	,	,	,	O	31	punct
33	the	the	DT	O	37	det
34	Orion	Orion	NNP	ORGANIZATION	37	compound
35	crew	crew	NN	O	37	compound
36	exploration	exploration	NN	O	37	compound
37	vehicle	vehicle	NN	O	31	appos
38	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	``	``	``	O	12	punct
2	And	and	CC	O	12	cc
3	then	then	RB	O	12	advmod
4	Arnold	Arnold	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	who	who	WP	O	7	nsubj
7	plays	play	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
8	my	my	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
9	old	old	JJ	O	10	amod
10	rival	rival	NN	O	7	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	4	punct
12	walks	walk	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
13	in	in	IN	O	16	dep
14	.	.	.	O	13	punct
15	We	we	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	have	have	VBP	O	12	dep
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	history	history	NN	O	16	dobj
19	together	together	RB	O	18	dep
20	.	.	.	O	19	punct
21	And	and	CC	O	16	cc
22	we	we	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	go	go	VBP	O	16	conj
24	back	back	RB	O	23	advmod
25	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
26	forth	forth	RB	O	24	conj
27	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
28	I	I	PRP	O	29	nsubj
29	tell	tell	VBP	O	12	conj
30	him	he	PRP	O	29	dobj
31	that	that	IN	O	35	mark
32	I	I	PRP	O	35	nsubj
33	should	should	MD	O	35	aux
34	have	have	VB	O	35	aux
35	shot	shoot	VBN	O	29	ccomp
36	him	he	PRP	O	35	dobj
37	a	a	DT	O	39	det
38	long	long	JJ	O	39	amod
39	time	time	NN	O	35	advmod
40	ago	ago	IN	O	39	case
41	when	when	WRB	O	43	advmod
42	I	I	PRP	O	43	nsubj
43	had	have	VBD	O	39	advcl
44	the	the	DT	O	45	det
45	chance	chance	NN	O	43	dobj
46	.	.	.	O	43	punct
47	Then	then	RB	O	12	advmod
48	it	it	PRP	O	49	nsubj
49	goes	go	VBZ	O	12	parataxis
50	on	on	IN	O	52	case
51	from	from	IN	O	52	case
52	there	there	EX	O	49	nmod
53	.	.	.	O	49	punct
54	And	and	CC	O	49	cc
55	here	here	RB	O	57	advmod
56	we	we	PRP	O	57	nsubj
57	are	be	VBP	O	49	conj
58	,	,	,	O	57	punct
59	the	the	DT	O	60	det
60	three	three	CD	NUMBER	57	dobj
61	of	of	IN	O	63	mark
62	us	we	PRP	O	63	nsubj
63	trying	try	VBG	O	60	acl
64	to	to	TO	O	65	mark
65	man	man	VB	O	63	xcomp
66	up	up	RP	O	65	compound:prt
67	to	to	TO	O	68	case
68	one	one	CD	NUMBER	65	nmod
69	another	another	DT	O	68	dep
70	,	,	,	O	63	punct
71	playing	play	VBG	O	63	dep
72	off	off	IN	O	71	advmod
73	of	of	IN	O	76	mark
74	who	who	WP	O	76	dobj
75	we	we	PRP	O	76	nsubj
76	are	be	VBP	O	72	advcl
77	,	,	,	O	63	punct
78	using	use	VBG	O	63	dep
79	our	we	PRP$	O	80	nmod:poss
80	baggage	baggage	NN	O	78	dobj
81	in	in	IN	O	84	case
82	this	this	DT	O	84	det
83	one	one	CD	NUMBER	84	nummod
84	scene	scene	NN	O	63	nmod
85	.	.	.	O	12	punct
86	''	''	''	O	12	punct

1	Erick	Erick	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Erickson	Erickson	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	correct	correct	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	iron	iron	NN	O	3	compound
3	lung	lung	NN	O	24	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	an	a	DT	O	7	det
6	antiquated	antiquated	JJ	O	7	amod
7	device	device	NN	O	3	appos
8	which	which	WDT	O	9	nsubj
9	uses	use	VBZ	O	7	acl:relcl
10	pressurised	pressurised	JJ	O	11	amod
11	bellows	bellows	NNS	O	9	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	force	force	VB	O	9	xcomp
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	lungs	lung	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	breathe	breathe	VB	O	13	xcomp
18	,	,	,	O	3	punct
19	was	be	VBD	O	24	cop
20	Middleton	Middleton	NNP	PERSON	24	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	best	best	JJS	O	24	amod
23	treatment	treatment	NN	O	24	compound
24	option	option	NN	O	0	ROOT
25	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	19	nmod
3	to	to	TO	O	4	case
4	stories	story	NNS	O	2	nmod
5	like	like	IN	O	10	case
6	Hamish	Hamish	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Bowles	Bowles	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	first-person	first-person	NN	O	10	compound
10	account	account	NN	O	4	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	15	case
12	his	he	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
13	wildlife	wildlife	NN	O	15	compound
14	survival	survival	NN	O	15	compound
15	mission	mission	NN	O	10	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	19	punct
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	magazine	magazine	NN	O	19	nsubj
19	dabbles	dabble	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
20	in	in	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	world	world	NN	O	19	nmod
23	of	of	IN	O	25	case
24	sustainable	sustainable	JJ	O	25	amod
25	food	food	NN	O	22	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	2	punct
2	Ed	Ed	NNP	O	9	nmod
3	.	.	.	O	2	punct
4	Oh	oh	UH	O	2	dep
5	,	,	,	O	9	punct
6	we	we	PRP	O	9	nsubj
7	'll	will	MD	O	9	aux
8	definitely	definitely	RB	O	9	advmod
9	know	know	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	that	that	DT	O	9	dobj
11	soon	soon	RB	O	12	advmod
12	enough	enough	RB	O	9	dep
13	.	.	.	O	12	punct
14	Intimately	intimately	RB	O	12	dep
15	.	.	.	O	9	punct
16	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	9	punct

1	Still	still	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	that	that	DT	O	4	nsubj
4	's	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	say	say	VB	O	4	xcomp
8	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
9	does	do	VBZ	O	11	aux
10	n't	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	work	work	VB	O	7	xcomp
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
14	we	we	PRP	O	17	nsubj
15	're	be	VBP	O	17	aux
16	particularly	particularly	RB	O	17	advmod
17	enjoying	enjoy	VBG	O	11	conj
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	unified	unify	VBN	O	20	amod
20	inbox	inbox	NN	O	17	dobj
21	-	-	:	O	20	punct
22	which	which	WDT	O	29	nsubj
23	,	,	,	O	29	punct
24	despite	despite	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	billing	billing	NN	O	29	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	29	punct
28	still	still	RB	O	29	advmod
29	keeps	keep	VBZ	O	20	acl:relcl
30	Gmail	Gmail	NNP	O	31	nsubj
31	separate	separate	VB	O	29	ccomp
32	from	from	IN	O	33	case
33	everything	everything	NN	O	31	nmod
34	else	else	RB	O	33	advmod
35	-	-	:	O	11	punct
36	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
37	the	the	DT	O	39	det
38	pop-up	pop-up	JJ	O	39	amod
39	menu	menu	NN	O	46	nsubj
40	tapping	tap	VBG	O	39	acl
41	on	on	IN	O	45	case
42	a	a	DT	O	43	det
43	contact	contact	NN	O	45	nmod:poss
44	's	's	POS	O	43	case
45	name	name	NN	O	40	nmod
46	brings	bring	VBZ	O	11	conj
47	,	,	,	O	46	punct
48	offering	offer	VBG	O	46	xcomp
49	the	the	DT	O	51	det
50	various	various	JJ	O	51	amod
51	ways	way	NNS	O	48	dobj
52	you	you	PRP	O	54	nsubj
53	can	can	MD	O	54	aux
54	communicate	communicate	VB	O	51	acl:relcl
55	with	with	IN	O	56	case
56	them	they	PRP	O	54	nmod
57	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	62	punct
58	email	email	NN	O	62	compound
59	,	,	,	O	62	punct
60	call	call	NN	O	62	dep
61	,	,	,	O	62	punct
62	SMS	sms	NN	O	56	appos
63	,	,	,	O	62	punct
64	Facebook	Facebook	NNP	ORGANIZATION	65	compound
65	message	message	NN	O	62	dep
66	,	,	,	O	62	punct
67	etc	etc	NN	O	62	dep
68	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	62	punct
69	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	iMac	iMac	NNP	O	3	compound
3	ships	ship	NNS	O	37	nsubj
4	in	in	IN	O	7	case
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	simple	simple	JJ	O	7	amod
7	box	box	NN	O	3	nmod
8	with	with	IN	O	10	case
9	styrofoam	styrofoam	NN	O	10	compound
10	corners	corner	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	3	punct
12	including	include	VBG	O	16	case
13	just	just	RB	O	16	advmod
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	power	power	NN	O	16	compound
16	cable	cable	NN	O	3	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	an	a	DT	O	20	det
19	accessory	accessory	NN	O	20	compound
20	box	box	NN	O	16	conj
21	that	that	WDT	O	22	nsubj
22	holds	hold	VBZ	O	20	acl:relcl
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	keyboard	keyboard	NN	O	34	nsubj
25	,	,	,	O	24	punct
26	mouse	mouse	NN	O	24	appos
27	,	,	,	O	24	punct
28	an	a	DT	O	30	det
29	introductory	introductory	JJ	O	30	amod
30	booklet	booklet	NN	O	24	appos
31	,	,	,	O	24	punct
32	a	a	DT	O	33	det
33	screen	screen	NN	O	24	appos
34	wipe	wipe	VBP	O	22	ccomp
35	cloth	cloth	NN	O	34	dobj
36	,	,	,	O	3	punct
37	install	install	VB	O	0	ROOT
38	and	and	CC	O	37	cc
39	restore	restore	VB	O	37	conj
40	DVDs	dvd	NNS	O	39	dobj
41	,	,	,	O	40	punct
42	stickers	sticker	NNS	O	40	conj
43	and	and	CC	O	40	cc
44	regulatory	regulatory	JJ	O	45	amod
45	information	information	NN	O	40	conj
46	.	.	.	O	37	punct

1	Here	here	RB	O	2	advmod
2	's	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	what	what	WP	O	5	dobj
4	voters	voter	NNS	O	5	nsubj
5	thought	think	VBD	O	2	dep
6	they	they	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	knew	know	VBD	O	5	ccomp
8	:	:	:	O	2	punct

1	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	3	punct
2	RSS	rss	NN	O	3	compound
3	AAC	aac	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	5	punct
5	Add	add	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	9	det
7	Engadget	Engadget	NNP	O	9	compound
8	Podcast	Podcast	NNP	O	9	compound
9	feed	feed	NN	O	5	dobj
10	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	13	punct
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	enhanced	enhance	VBN	O	13	amod
13	AAC	aac	NN	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod
14	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	13	punct
15	to	to	TO	O	18	case
16	your	you	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
17	RSS	rss	NN	O	18	compound
18	aggregator	aggregator	NN	O	5	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	det
2	Siena	Siena	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
3	Research	Research	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
4	Institute	Institute	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	poll	poll	NN	O	6	nsubj
6	shows	show	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	Democrat	Democrat	NNP	MISC	9	compound
8	Bill	Bill	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	Owens	Owens	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	Doug	Doug	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Hoffman	Hoffman	NNP	PERSON	9	conj
13	are	be	VBP	O	14	cop
14	neck-and-neck	neck-and-neck	JJ	O	6	ccomp
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	with	with	IN	O	17	case
17	Scozzafava	Scozzafava	NNP	PERSON	14	nmod
18	far	far	RB	O	19	advmod
19	behind	behind	RB	O	17	advmod
20	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Previous	previous	JJ	O	2	amod
2	studies	study	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	provide	provide	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	conflicting	conflicting	JJ	O	5	amod
5	results	result	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	about	about	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	incidence	incidence	NN	O	5	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	severity	severity	NN	O	8	conj
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	lupus	lupus	NN	O	13	compound
13	nephritis	nephritis	NN	O	8	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	patients	patient	NNS	O	3	nmod
16	with	with	IN	O	18	case
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	history	history	NN	O	15	nmod
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	lupus	lupus	NN	O	18	nmod
21	who	who	WP	O	23	nsubj
22	have	have	VBP	O	23	aux
23	undergone	undergo	VBN	O	15	acl:relcl
24	a	a	DT	O	26	det
25	kidney	kidney	NN	O	26	compound
26	transplant	transplant	NN	O	23	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Along	along	IN	O	31	advmod
2	with	with	IN	O	4	case
3	comparison	comparison	NN	O	4	compound
4	shopping	shopping	NN	O	1	nmod
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	making	make	VBG	O	4	conj
7	a	a	DT	O	10	det
8	simple	simple	JJ	O	10	amod
9	price	price	NN	O	10	compound
10	book	book	NN	O	6	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	31	punct
12	one	one	CD	NUMBER	31	nsubj
13	of	of	IN	O	17	case
14	the	the	DT	O	17	det
15	often	often	RB	O	16	advmod
16	overlooked	overlook	VBN	O	17	amod
17	uses	use	NNS	O	12	nmod
18	for	for	IN	O	20	case
19	ubiquitous	ubiquitous	JJ	O	20	amod
20	capture	capture	NN	O	17	nmod
21	-	-	:	O	12	punct
22	but	but	CC	O	23	case
23	one	one	CD	NUMBER	12	nmod
24	I	I	PRP	O	25	nsubj
25	use	use	VBP	O	23	acl:relcl
26	all	all	PDT	O	28	det:predet
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	time	time	NN	O	25	dobj
29	-	-	:	O	12	punct
30	is	be	VBZ	O	31	aux
31	using	use	VBG	O	0	ROOT
32	your	you	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
33	notebook	notebook	NN	O	31	dobj
34	to	to	TO	O	35	mark
35	capture	capture	VB	O	33	acl
36	gift	gift	NN	O	37	compound
37	ideas	idea	NNS	O	35	dobj
38	.	.	.	O	31	punct

1	Better	better	RBR	O	2	amod
2	news	news	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	for	for	IN	O	5	case
4	CAW	CAW	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	members	member	NNS	O	2	nmod
6	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
8	Ford	Ford	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	Oakville	Oakville	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
11	assembly	assembly	NN	O	12	compound
12	complex	complex	NN	O	18	nsubj
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	also	also	RB	O	16	advmod
15	in	in	IN	O	16	case
16	Ontario	Ontario	NNP	LOCATION	12	acl:relcl
17	,	,	,	O	12	punct
18	has	have	VBZ	O	6	ccomp
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	go-ahead	go-ahead	NN	O	18	dobj
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	add	add	VB	O	20	acl
23	a	a	DT	O	25	det
24	third	third	JJ	ORDINAL	25	amod
25	shift	shift	NN	O	22	dobj
26	when	when	WRB	O	27	advmod
27	needed	need	VBN	O	22	advcl
28	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Despite	despite	IN	O	9	mark
2	all	all	DT	O	9	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	custodial	custodial	JJ	O	6	amod
6	trauma	trauma	NN	O	2	nmod
7	Levi	Levi	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	claiming	claim	VBG	O	13	advcl
10	,	,	,	O	13	punct
11	you	you	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	've	have	VBP	O	13	aux
13	got	get	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	ta	ta	NN	O	15	compound
15	wonder	wonder	NN	O	13	dobj
16	if	if	IN	O	20	mark
17	he	he	PRP	O	20	nsubj
18	is	be	VBZ	O	20	aux
19	n't	not	RB	O	20	neg
20	enjoying	enjoy	VBG	O	13	advcl
21	his	he	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
22	time	time	NN	O	20	dobj
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	limelight	limelight	NN	O	20	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	strategy	strategy	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	also	also	RB	O	4	advmod
4	called	call	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	for	for	IN	O	9	case
6	later	later	JJ	O	9	amod
7	DVD	dvd	NN	O	9	compound
8	home	home	NN	O	9	compound
9	sales	sale	NNS	O	4	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	movie	movie	NN	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	a	a	DT	O	17	det
15	CD	cd	NN	O	17	compound
16	box	box	NN	O	17	compound
17	set	set	NN	O	12	conj
18	,	,	,	O	12	punct
19	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
20	all	all	PDT	O	23	det:predet
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	predictable	predictable	JJ	O	23	amod
23	merchandising	merchandising	NN	O	12	conj
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Like	like	IN	O	5	case
2	the	the	DT	O	5	det
3	``	``	``	O	5	punct
4	doc	doc	NN	O	5	compound
5	fix	fix	NN	O	15	nmod
6	''	''	''	O	5	punct
7	defeated	defeat	VBN	O	5	acl
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	Senate	Senate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	15	punct
12	it	it	PRP	O	15	nsubj
13	would	would	MD	O	15	aux
14	n't	not	RB	O	15	neg
15	add	add	VB	O	0	ROOT
16	to	to	TO	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	actual	actual	JJ	O	19	amod
19	costs	cost	NNS	O	15	nmod
20	in	in	IN	O	24	case
21	the	the	DT	O	24	det
22	health	health	NN	O	24	compound
23	care	care	NN	O	24	compound
24	bill	bill	NN	O	15	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	15	punct
26	thus	thus	RB	O	27	advmod
27	preserving	preserve	VBG	O	15	xcomp
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	illusion	illusion	NN	O	27	dobj
30	that	that	IN	O	35	mark
31	the	the	DT	O	33	det
32	big	big	JJ	O	33	amod
33	bill	bill	NN	O	35	nsubj
34	will	will	MD	O	35	aux
35	cost	cost	VB	O	27	ccomp
36	less	less	JJR	O	38	advmod
37	than	than	IN	O	36	mwe
38	$	$	$	MONEY	35	dobj
39	1	1	CD	MONEY	40	compound
40	trillion	trillion	CD	MONEY	38	nummod
41	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	any	any	DT	O	3	det
3	case	case	NN	O	8	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	what	what	WP	O	8	dobj
6	do	do	VBP	O	8	aux
7	you	you	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	think	think	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	?	?	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	new	new	JJ	O	3	amod
3	27	27	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT
4	''	''	''	O	3	punct
5	iMac	iMac	NNP	O	3	dep
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	along	along	IN	O	16	advmod
8	with	with	IN	O	13	case
9	its	its	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
10	smaller	smaller	JJR	O	13	amod
11	21.5	21.5	CD	NUMBER	10	dep
12	''	''	''	O	13	punct
13	partner	partner	NN	O	7	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	also	also	RB	O	13	advmod
16	sport	sport	NN	O	5	appos
17	higher	higher	JJR	O	18	dep
18	quality	quality	NN	O	16	amod
19	IPS	IPS	NNP	O	20	compound
20	LCD	lcd	NNS	O	16	dep
21	screen	screen	NN	O	22	compound
22	technology	technology	NN	O	20	dep
23	,	,	,	O	5	punct
24	resulting	result	VBG	O	5	acl
25	in	in	IN	O	27	case
26	spectacular	spectacular	JJ	O	27	amod
27	color	color	NN	O	24	nmod
28	,	,	,	O	3	punct
29	contrast	contrast	NN	O	3	appos
30	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
31	wide	wide	JJ	O	33	amod
32	viewing	view	VBG	O	33	amod
33	angles	angle	NNS	O	29	conj
34	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	times	time	NNS	O	2	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	5	case
5	inconvenience	inconvenience	NN	O	3	nmod
6	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
7	any	any	DT	O	8	det
8	abuse	abuse	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
9	will	will	MD	O	11	aux
10	be	be	VB	O	11	auxpass
11	fought	fight	VBN	O	2	conj
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	overcome	overcome	VBN	O	11	conj
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	That	that	DT	O	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	bit	bit	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	digression	digression	NN	O	4	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	4	punct
9	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
10	salient	salient	JJ	O	4	conj
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	UPDATE	UPDATE	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	:	:	:	O	1	punct
3	Republican	Republican	NNP	MISC	4	compound
4	nominee	nominee	NN	O	9	nsubj
5	for	for	IN	O	8	case
6	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
7	Dede	Dede	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Scozzafava	Scozzafava	NNP	PERSON	4	nmod
9	announced	announce	VBD	O	1	parataxis
10	Saturday	Saturday	NNP	DATE	9	nmod:tmod
11	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
12	she	she	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	has	have	VBZ	O	14	aux
14	dropped	drop	VBN	O	9	ccomp
15	out	out	IN	O	14	compound:prt
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	race	race	NN	O	14	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	14	punct
20	according	accord	VBG	O	25	case
21	to	to	TO	O	20	mwe
22	the	the	DT	O	25	det
23	Watertown	Watertown	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
24	Daily	Daily	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
25	Times	Times	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	16	cc
2	when	when	WRB	O	4	advmod
3	they	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	get	get	VBP	O	16	advcl
5	this	this	DT	O	7	det
6	healthcare	healthcare	NN	O	7	compound
7	bill	bill	NN	O	4	dobj
8	,	,	,	O	16	punct
9	if	if	IN	O	11	mark
10	they	they	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	do	do	VBP	O	16	advcl
12	,	,	,	O	16	punct
13	that	that	DT	O	16	nsubj
14	's	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	easiest	easiest	JJS	O	0	ROOT
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	fastest	fastest	JJS	O	19	amod
19	way	way	NN	O	16	appos
20	for	for	IN	O	21	case
21	them	they	PRP	O	19	nmod
22	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
23	be	be	VB	O	24	cop
24	able	able	JJ	O	19	acl
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	regulate	regulate	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	every	every	DT	O	28	det
28	aspect	aspect	NN	O	26	dobj
29	of	of	IN	O	31	case
30	human	human	JJ	O	31	amod
31	behavior	behavior	NN	O	28	nmod
32	,	,	,	O	26	punct
33	because	because	IN	O	37	mark
34	it	it	PRP	O	37	nsubj
35	'll	will	MD	O	37	aux
36	all	all	RB	O	37	advmod
37	have	have	VB	O	26	advcl
38	some	some	DT	O	40	det
39	related	related	JJ	O	40	amod
40	cost	cost	NN	O	37	dobj
41	to	to	TO	O	42	case
42	healthcare	healthcare	NN	O	37	nmod
43	:	:	:	O	26	punct
44	what	what	WP	O	46	dobj
45	you	you	PRP	O	46	nsubj
46	drive	drive	VBP	O	26	parataxis
47	,	,	,	O	50	punct
48	what	what	WP	O	50	dobj
49	you	you	PRP	O	50	nsubj
50	eat	eat	VBP	O	46	parataxis
51	,	,	,	O	50	punct
52	where	where	WRB	O	54	advmod
53	you	you	PRP	O	54	nsubj
54	live	live	VBP	O	46	advcl
55	,	,	,	O	16	punct
56	what	what	WP	O	58	dobj
57	you	you	PRP	O	58	nsubj
58	do	do	VBP	O	16	acl:relcl
59	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	David	David	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Cromer	Cromer	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
5	also	also	RB	O	6	advmod
6	directed	direct	VBD	O	2	acl:relcl
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	production	production	NN	O	6	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	``	``	``	O	12	punct
11	Our	we	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	Town	town	NN	O	8	nmod
13	''	''	''	O	12	punct
14	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	17	aux
16	still	still	RB	O	17	advmod
17	running	run	VBG	O	8	acl:relcl
18	Off	off	IN	O	19	case
19	Broadway	Broadway	NNP	LOCATION	17	advmod
20	,	,	,	O	2	punct
21	was	be	VBD	O	22	aux
22	directing	direct	VBG	O	0	ROOT
23	both	both	DT	O	24	det
24	Simon	Simon	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubj
25	plays	play	VBZ	O	22	ccomp
26	.	.	.	O	22	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	5	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	candidate	candidate	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
5	black	black	JJ	O	17	dep
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	male	male	JJ	O	5	conj
8	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
9	fills	fill	VBZ	O	5	conj
10	this	this	DT	O	11	det
11	bill	bill	NN	O	9	dobj
12	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	14	punct
13	Michael	Michael	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Williams	Williams	NNP	PERSON	11	appos
15	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	14	punct
16	,	,	,	O	17	punct
17	great	great	JJ	O	0	ROOT
18	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	Only	only	RB	O	3	advmod
2	this	this	DT	O	3	det
3	time	time	NN	O	7	nmod:tmod
4	Elisabeth	Elisabeth	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Hasselbeck	Hasselbeck	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	7	aux
7	wearing	wear	VBG	O	0	ROOT
8	an	a	DT	O	11	det
9	enormous	enormous	JJ	O	11	amod
10	cereal	cereal	NN	O	11	compound
11	box	box	NN	O	7	dobj
12	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Women	woman	NNS	O	7	nsubj
2	are	be	VBP	O	7	cop
3	more	more	RBR	O	7	advmod
4	than	than	IN	O	3	case
5	their	they	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
6	reproductive	reproductive	JJ	O	7	amod
7	organs	organ	NNS	O	0	ROOT
8	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	device	device	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
4	quite	quite	RB	O	5	advmod
5	awesome	awesome	JJ	O	0	ROOT
6	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	special	special	JJ	O	3	amod
3	election	election	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	Tuesday	Tuesday	NNP	DATE	4	nmod:tmod
6	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Under	under	IN	O	2	case
2	Armour	Armour	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
3	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	4	punct
4	NYSE	NYSE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	appos
5	:	:	:	O	4	punct
6	UA	UA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	dep
7	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	4	punct
8	posted	post	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	better-than-expectedquarterly	better-than-expectedquarterly	JJ	O	10	amod
10	results	result	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
12	raised	raise	VBD	O	8	conj
13	its	its	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
14	full-year	full-year	JJ	O	15	amod
15	guidance	guidance	NN	O	8	dep
16	along	along	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	way	way	NN	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Overall	overall	RB	O	12	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	12	punct
3	however	however	RB	O	12	advmod
4	,	,	,	O	12	punct
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	majority	majority	NN	O	12	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	6	nmod
9	across	across	IN	O	11	case
10	their	they	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	country	country	NN	O	8	nmod
12	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
13	a	a	DT	O	16	det
14	reasonably	reasonably	RB	O	15	advmod
15	high	high	JJ	O	16	amod
16	level	level	NN	O	12	dobj
17	of	of	IN	O	18	case
18	trust	trust	NN	O	16	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	their	they	PRP$	O	21	nmod:poss
21	neighbors	neighbor	NNS	O	18	nmod
22	with	with	IN	O	26	case
23	even	even	RB	O	26	advmod
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	lowest-ranking	lowest-ranking	JJ	O	26	amod
26	state	state	NN	O	12	nmod
27	having	have	VBG	O	26	acl
28	60	60	CD	PERCENT	29	nummod
29	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	27	dobj
30	who	who	WP	O	31	nsubj
31	believe	believe	VBP	O	29	acl:relcl
32	their	they	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
33	wallets	wallet	NNS	O	36	nsubjpass
34	would	would	MD	O	36	aux
35	be	be	VB	O	36	auxpass
36	returned	return	VBN	O	31	ccomp
37	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	goal	goal	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	program	program	NN	O	2	nmod
6	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	provide	provide	VB	O	6	xcomp
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	road	road	NN	O	11	compound
11	map	map	NN	O	8	dobj
12	for	for	IN	O	13	case
13	associates	associate	NNS	O	8	nmod
14	detailing	detail	VBG	O	13	acl
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	specific	specific	JJ	O	17	amod
17	skills	skill	NNS	O	14	dobj
18	required	require	VBN	O	17	acl
19	at	at	IN	O	20	case
20	each	each	DT	O	18	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	25	case
22	the	the	DT	O	25	det
23	newly	newly	RB	O	24	advmod
24	created	create	VBN	O	25	amod
25	levels	level	NNS	O	20	nmod
26	-	-	:	O	25	punct
27	junior	junior	NN	O	25	dep
28	,	,	,	O	27	punct
29	midlevel	midlevel	JJ	O	27	conj
30	,	,	,	O	27	punct
31	and	and	CC	O	27	cc
32	senior	senior	JJ	O	33	amod
33	associates	associate	NNS	O	27	conj
34	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Whereas	whereas	IN	O	4	mark
2	Cavallari	Cavallari	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	introduced	introduce	VBN	O	14	advcl
5	as	as	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	anti-heroine	anti-heroine	NN	O	4	nmod
8	off	off	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	bat	bat	NN	O	4	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	14	punct
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	role	role	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	already	already	RB	O	0	ROOT
15	occupied	occupy	VBN	O	14	xcomp
16	to	to	TO	O	17	case
17	perfection	perfection	NN	O	15	nmod
18	by	by	IN	O	20	case
19	Heidi	Heidi	NNP	PERSON	20	compound
20	Montag	Montag	NNP	PERSON	17	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	You	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	3	aux
3	take	take	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	`	`	``	O	3	punct
5	The	the	DT	O	6	det
6	Hills	Hills	NNPS	O	3	dobj
7	'	'	POS	O	6	case
8	out	out	IN	O	11	advmod
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	Orange	Orange	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
11	County	County	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	3	punct
13	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
14	you	you	PRP	O	17	nsubj
15	ca	can	MD	O	17	aux
16	n't	not	RB	O	17	neg
17	take	take	VB	O	3	conj
18	Lauren	Lauren	NNP	PERSON	19	compound
19	Conrad	Conrad	NNP	PERSON	17	dobj
20	out	out	IN	O	23	case
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	`	`	``	O	23	punct
23	The	the	DT	O	17	nmod
24	Hills	Hills	NNPS	O	23	nmod:poss
25	'	'	POS	O	24	case
26	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	4	cc
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	fact	fact	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
6	there	there	EX	O	7	expl
7	are	be	VBP	O	4	ccomp
8	many	many	JJ	O	9	amod
9	women	woman	NNS	O	7	nsubj
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	9	nmod
12	like	like	IN	O	14	case
13	DeDe	DeDe	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Scozzafava	Scozzafava	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	7	punct
16	Republicans	Republicans	NNPS	MISC	20	nsubj
17	with	with	IN	O	19	case
18	an	a	DT	O	19	det
19	ideological	ideological	JJ	O	16	nmod
20	disconnect	disconnect	VB	O	7	dep
21	with	with	IN	O	23	case
22	many	many	JJ	O	23	amod
23	facets	facet	NNS	O	20	nmod
24	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
25	decidedly	decidedly	RB	O	23	dep
26	in	in	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	sphere	sphere	NN	O	25	nmod
29	of	of	IN	O	31	case
30	social	social	JJ	O	31	amod
31	policy	policy	NN	O	28	nmod
32	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	25	punct
33	of	of	IN	O	36	case
34	the	the	DT	O	36	det
35	modern	modern	JJ	O	36	amod
36	GOP	GOP	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	nmod
37	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	5	mark
2	what	what	WP	O	5	dobj
3	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	's	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
5	worth	worth	JJ	O	8	advcl
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	agree	agree	VBP	O	0	ROOT
9	with	with	IN	O	12	case
10	Prof	Prof	NNP	O	12	compound
11	David	David	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Nutt	Nutt	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	adviser	adviser	NN	O	12	appos
16	sacked	sack	VBN	O	15	acl
17	after	after	IN	O	18	mark
18	criticising	criticise	VBG	O	16	advcl
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	Government	Government	NNP	O	22	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	decision	decision	NN	O	18	dobj
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	categorise	categorise	VB	O	22	acl
25	cannabis	cannabis	NN	O	24	dobj
26	as	as	IN	O	30	case
27	a	a	DT	O	30	det
28	Class	class	NN	O	30	compound
29	B	B	NNP	O	30	compound
30	Drug	Drug	NNP	O	24	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Individuals	individual	NNS	O	13	nsubj
2	with	with	IN	O	8	case
3	the	the	DT	O	8	det
4	autoimmune	autoimmune	JJ	O	8	amod
5	disease	disease	NN	O	8	compound
6	systemic	systemic	JJ	O	8	amod
7	lupus	lupus	NN	O	8	compound
8	erythematosus	erythematosus	NN	O	1	nmod
9	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	10	punct
10	lupus	lupus	NN	O	1	appos
11	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	10	punct
12	can	can	MD	O	13	aux
13	experience	experience	VB	O	0	ROOT
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	number	number	NN	O	13	dobj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	medical	medical	JJ	O	18	amod
18	complications	complication	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	15	punct
20	such	such	JJ	O	23	case
21	as	as	IN	O	20	mwe
22	lupus	lupus	NN	O	23	compound
23	nephritis	nephritis	NN	O	15	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	23	punct
25	an	a	DT	O	28	det
26	inflammatory	inflammatory	JJ	O	28	amod
27	kidney	kidney	NN	O	28	compound
28	disorder	disorder	NN	O	23	appos
29	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	UPDATE	update	NN	O	8	nsubj
2	II	ii	CD	NUMBER	1	nummod
3	:	:	:	O	1	punct
4	Here	here	RB	O	1	dep
5	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	three-part	three-part	JJ	O	8	amod
8	segment	segment	NN	O	0	ROOT
9	I	I	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	taped	tape	VBD	O	8	acl:relcl
11	yesterday	yesterday	NN	DATE	10	nmod:tmod
12	with	with	IN	O	14	case
13	Bill	Bill	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Moyers	Moyers	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod
15	:	:	:	O	8	punct

1	Yet	yet	RB	O	3	advmod
2	another	another	DT	O	3	det
3	musicians	musician	NNS	O	0	ROOT
4	showing	show	VBG	O	3	acl
5	how	how	WRB	O	6	advmod
6	CwF	CwF	NNP	O	4	dep
7	+	+	CC	O	6	cc
8	RtB	rtb	NN	O	9	compound
9	works	work	NNS	O	6	conj
10	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
2	's	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
4	their	they	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	fault	fault	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
7	top	top	JJ	O	8	amod
8	management	management	NN	O	11	nsubj
9	could	could	MD	O	11	aux
10	n't	not	RB	O	11	neg
11	make	make	VB	O	5	ccomp
12	more	more	JJR	O	13	amod
13	money	money	NN	O	11	dobj
14	from	from	IN	O	15	case
15	them	they	PRP	O	11	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	wanted	want	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
4	be	be	VB	O	6	cop
5	like	like	IN	O	6	case
6	Leo	Leo	NNP	PERSON	2	xcomp
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	Cameron	Cameron	NNP	PERSON	6	conj
9	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	ex-Mrs	ex-mr	NNS	O	6	conj
12	.	.	.	O	6	punct
13	Larry	Larry	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	David	David	NNP	PERSON	6	dep
15	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
16	all	all	PDT	O	18	det:predet
17	those	those	DT	O	18	det
18	stars	star	NNS	O	6	conj
19	who	who	WP	O	20	nsubj
20	live	live	VBP	O	18	acl:relcl
21	in	in	IN	O	22	case
22	houses	house	NNS	O	20	nmod
23	covered	cover	VBN	O	22	acl
24	with	with	IN	O	26	case
25	solar	solar	JJ	O	26	amod
26	panels	panel	NNS	O	23	nmod
27	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
28	bathe	bathe	VB	O	6	conj
29	in	in	IN	O	32	case
30	self-sustaining	self-sustaining	JJ	O	32	amod
31	irrigation	irrigation	NN	O	32	compound
32	systems	system	NNS	O	28	nmod
33	,	,	,	O	2	punct
34	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
35	who	who	WP	O	36	nsubj
36	think	think	VBP	O	42	advcl
37	cooking	cooking	JJ	O	38	amod
38	oil	oil	NN	O	40	nsubj
39	is	be	VBZ	O	40	cop
40	something	something	NN	O	36	ccomp
41	you	you	PRP	O	42	nsubj
42	put	put	VBP	O	2	conj
43	in	in	IN	O	48	case
44	your	you	PRP$	O	45	nmod:poss
45	car	car	NN	O	48	nmod:poss
46	's	's	POS	O	45	case
47	fuel	fuel	NN	O	48	compound
48	tank	tank	NN	O	42	nmod
49	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Seaman	Seaman	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Ware	Ware	NNP	PERSON	23	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	who	who	WP	O	5	nsubj
5	grew	grow	VBD	O	2	acl:relcl
6	up	up	RP	O	5	compound:prt
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	cramped	cramped	JJ	O	9	amod
9	apartment	apartment	NN	O	5	nmod
10	in	in	IN	O	13	case
11	a	a	DT	O	13	det
12	tough	tough	JJ	O	13	amod
13	neighborhood	neighborhood	NN	O	5	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	Bronx	Bronx	NNP	LOCATION	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	2	punct
18	had	have	VBD	O	23	aux
19	never	never	RB	O	23	neg
20	been	be	VBN	O	23	cop
21	on	on	IN	O	23	case
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	boat	boat	NN	O	0	ROOT
24	before	before	IN	O	25	case
25	Thursday	Thursday	NNP	DATE	23	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	Some	some	DT	O	2	det
2	choice	choice	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	quotes	quote	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	:	:	:	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	group	group	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	includes	include	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	young	young	JJ	O	6	amod
6	mother	mother	NN	O	3	dobj
7	riding	ride	VBG	O	6	acl
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	boat	boat	NN	O	7	dobj
10	for	for	IN	O	13	case
11	the	the	DT	O	13	det
12	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	13	amod
13	time	time	NN	O	9	nmod
14	in	in	IN	O	16	case
15	her	she	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	life	life	NN	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	9	punct
18	a	a	DT	O	19	det
19	veteran	veteran	NN	O	9	conj
20	of	of	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	Navy	Navy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	nmod
23	remembering	remember	VBG	O	19	acl
24	her	she	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	love	love	NN	O	23	dobj
26	of	of	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	sea	sea	NN	O	19	nmod
29	,	,	,	O	9	punct
30	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
31	a	a	DT	O	32	det
32	man	man	NN	O	9	conj
33	trying	try	VBG	O	32	acl
34	to	to	TO	O	35	mark
35	escape	escape	VB	O	33	xcomp
36	a	a	DT	O	38	det
37	troubled	troubled	JJ	O	38	amod
38	neighborhood	neighborhood	NN	O	35	dobj
39	to	to	TO	O	40	mark
40	provide	provide	VB	O	35	advcl
41	for	for	IN	O	43	case
42	his	he	PRP$	O	43	nmod:poss
43	siblings	sibling	NNS	O	40	nmod
44	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	case
2	for	for	IN	O	3	case
3	Android	Android	NNP	O	12	nmod
4	2.0	2.0	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
5	itself	itself	PRP	O	3	advmod
6	,	,	,	O	12	punct
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	new	new	JJ	O	9	amod
9	OS	OS	NNP	O	12	nsubj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
11	less	less	RBR	O	12	advmod
12	obvious	obvious	JJ	O	0	ROOT
13	in	in	IN	O	15	case
14	its	its	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	changes	change	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	than	than	IN	O	18	mark
17	we	we	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	expected	expect	VBD	O	12	advcl
19	from	from	IN	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	run-up	run-up	NN	O	18	nmod
22	to	to	TO	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	release	release	NN	O	18	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	12	punct
26	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
27	much	much	RB	O	31	nsubj
28	of	of	IN	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	functionality	functionality	NN	O	27	nmod
31	seems	seem	VBZ	O	12	conj
32	to	to	TO	O	35	mark
33	have	have	VB	O	35	aux
34	been	be	VBN	O	35	auxpass
35	borrowed	borrow	VBN	O	31	xcomp
36	or	or	CC	O	35	cc
37	previewed	preview	VBN	O	35	conj
38	by	by	IN	O	41	case
39	the	the	DT	O	41	det
40	work	work	NN	O	41	compound
41	HTC	htc	NN	ORGANIZATION	35	nmod
42	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
43	Motorola	Motorola	NNP	ORGANIZATION	45	nsubj
44	have	have	VBP	O	45	aux
45	done	do	VBN	O	12	conj
46	on	on	IN	O	47	mark
47	distinguishing	distinguish	VBG	O	45	advcl
48	their	they	PRP$	O	51	nmod:poss
49	own	own	JJ	O	51	amod
50	Android	android	NN	O	51	compound
51	handsets	handset	NNS	O	47	dobj
52	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	Giving	give	VBG	O	12	csubj
2	my	my	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
3	fans	fan	NNS	O	4	compound
4	something	something	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	new	new	JJ	O	1	xcomp
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	talk	talk	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	about	about	IN	O	11	case
9	every	every	DT	SET	11	det
10	two	two	CD	SET	11	nummod
11	weeks	week	NNS	SET	7	nmod
12	meant	mean	VBD	O	0	ROOT
13	exactly	exactly	RB	O	12	advmod
14	that	that	IN	O	12	advmod
15	:	:	:	O	12	punct
16	they	they	PRP	O	17	nsubj
17	talk	talk	VBP	O	12	parataxis
18	about	about	IN	O	19	case
19	me	I	PRP	O	17	nmod
20	every	every	DT	SET	22	det
21	two	two	CD	SET	22	nummod
22	weeks	week	NNS	SET	17	nmod:tmod
23	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	exchange	exchange	NN	O	8	nmod
3	for	for	IN	O	5	case
4	your	you	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	dignity	dignity	NN	O	2	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	you	you	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	get	get	VBP	O	0	ROOT
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	free	free	JJ	O	11	amod
11	burrito	burrito	NN	O	8	dobj
12	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Ultimately	ultimately	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	it	it	PRP	O	6	nsubj
4	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	leadership	leadership	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	party	party	NN	O	6	nmod
10	itself	itself	PRP	O	9	advmod
11	that	that	IN	O	12	nsubj
12	elected	elect	VBN	O	6	acl:relcl
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	turn	turn	VB	O	12	xcomp
15	their	they	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	backs	back	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	on	on	IN	O	18	case
18	her	she	PRP	O	14	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	12	punct
20	with	with	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	chairman	chairman	NN	O	12	nmod
23	of	of	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	Republican	Republican	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	compound
26	Party	Party	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	26	punct
28	Michael	Michael	NNP	PERSON	29	compound
29	Steele	Steele	NNP	PERSON	26	appos
30	,	,	,	O	26	punct
31	saying	say	VBG	O	22	acl
32	yesterday	yesterday	NN	DATE	31	nmod:tmod
33	that	that	IN	O	47	mark
34	a	a	DT	O	35	det
35	victory	victory	NN	O	47	nsubj
36	by	by	IN	O	41	case
37	third-party	third-party	JJ	O	41	amod
38	insurgent	insurgent	JJ	O	41	amod
39	candidate	candidate	NN	O	41	compound
40	Doug	Doug	NNP	PERSON	41	compound
41	Hoffman	Hoffman	NNP	PERSON	35	nmod
42	was	be	VBD	O	47	cop
43	just	just	RB	O	47	advmod
44	like	like	IN	O	47	case
45	a	a	DT	O	47	det
46	Republican	republican	JJ	ORGANIZATION	47	amod
47	victory	victory	NN	O	31	ccomp
48	to	to	TO	O	49	case
49	him	he	PRP	O	47	nmod
50	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	4	mark
2	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	were	be	VBD	O	4	aux
4	running	run	VBG	O	12	advcl
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	law	law	NN	O	7	compound
7	school	school	NN	O	4	dobj
8	,	,	,	O	12	punct
9	I	I	PRP	O	12	nsubj
10	'd	would	MD	O	12	aux
11	be	be	VB	O	12	aux
12	looking	look	VBG	O	0	ROOT
13	for	for	IN	O	14	case
14	ways	way	NNS	O	12	nmod
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	collaborate	collaborate	VB	O	12	xcomp
17	in	in	IN	O	18	case
18	all	all	DT	O	16	nmod
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	that	that	DT	O	18	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	because	because	IN	O	25	mark
23	it	it	PRP	O	25	nsubj
24	's	be	VBZ	O	25	aux
25	smack	smack	VBP	O	20	dep
26	in	in	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	middle	middle	NN	O	25	nmod
29	of	of	IN	O	33	case
30	our	we	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
31	``	``	``	O	33	punct
32	core	core	NN	O	33	compound
33	competencies	competency	NNS	O	28	nmod
34	''	''	''	O	33	punct
35	;	;	:	O	25	punct
36	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
37	if	if	IN	O	40	mark
38	I	I	PRP	O	40	nsubj
39	were	be	VBD	O	40	aux
40	running	run	VBG	O	25	conj
41	a	a	DT	O	43	det
42	law	law	NN	O	43	compound
43	firm	firm	NN	O	40	dobj
44	,	,	,	O	49	punct
45	I	I	PRP	O	49	nsubj
46	'd	would	MD	O	49	aux
47	be	be	VB	O	49	cop
48	really	really	RB	O	49	advmod
49	interested	interested	JJ	O	40	parataxis
50	in	in	IN	O	51	mark
51	hearing	hear	VBG	O	49	advcl
52	what	what	WP	O	56	dobj
53	the	the	DT	O	55	det
54	law	law	NN	O	55	compound
55	schools	school	NNS	O	56	nsubj
56	have	have	VBP	O	51	ccomp
57	to	to	TO	O	58	mark
58	say	say	VB	O	56	ccomp
59	,	,	,	O	58	punct
60	and	and	CC	O	58	cc
61	to	to	TO	O	62	mark
62	think	think	VB	O	58	conj
63	about	about	IN	O	64	case
64	ways	way	NNS	O	62	nmod
65	in	in	IN	O	66	case
66	which	which	WDT	O	71	nmod
67	the	the	DT	O	69	det
68	law	law	NN	O	69	compound
69	schools	school	NNS	O	71	nsubj
70	could	could	MD	O	71	aux
71	help	help	VB	O	64	acl:relcl
72	them	they	PRP	O	73	nsubj
73	get	get	VB	O	71	ccomp
74	where	where	WRB	O	76	advmod
75	they	they	PRP	O	76	nsubj
76	want	want	VBP	O	73	advcl
77	to	to	TO	O	78	mark
78	get	get	VB	O	76	xcomp
79	,	,	,	O	49	punct
80	for	for	IN	O	83	case
81	the	the	DT	O	83	det
82	same	same	JJ	O	83	amod
83	reason	reason	NN	O	40	nmod
84	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	Is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	It	it	PRP	O	14	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	the	the	DT	O	9	det
6	new	new	JJ	O	9	amod
7	Michael	Michael	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
8	Jackson	Jackson	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	documentary	documentary	NN	O	3	appos
10	,	,	,	O	3	punct
11	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
12	a	a	DT	O	14	det
13	no-surprise	no-surprise	JJ	O	14	amod
14	sensation	sensation	NN	O	2	ccomp
15	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	4	cc
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	company	company	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	did	do	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	conduct	conduct	VB	O	4	ccomp
6	an	a	DT	O	8	det
7	internal	internal	JJ	O	8	amod
8	investigation	investigation	NN	O	5	dobj
9	,	,	,	O	4	punct
10	before	before	IN	O	13	mark
11	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	12	compound
12	Moffat	Moffat	NNP	PERSON	13	nsubj
13	agreed	agree	VBD	O	4	advcl
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	leave	leave	VB	O	13	xcomp
16	,	,	,	O	13	punct
17	according	accord	VBG	O	20	case
18	to	to	TO	O	17	mwe
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	person	person	NN	O	13	nmod
21	who	who	WP	O	23	nsubjpass
22	was	be	VBD	O	23	auxpass
23	told	tell	VBN	O	20	acl:relcl
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	review	review	NN	O	23	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Committees	committee	NNS	O	7	nsubj
2	in	in	IN	O	4	case
3	both	both	DT	O	4	det
4	houses	house	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
7	defeated	defeat	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	thirty	thirty	CD	NUMBER	10	nummod
9	different	different	JJ	O	10	amod
10	amendments	amendment	NNS	O	7	dobj
11	barring	bar	VBG	O	13	case
12	such	such	JJ	O	13	amod
13	funding	funding	NN	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Did	do	VBD	O	0	ROOT
2	Levi	Levi	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	approach	approach	NN	O	1	nsubj
4	VF	VF	NNP	O	1	dep
5	?	?	.	O	1	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	advent	advent	NN	O	8	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	5	case
5	Android	Android	NNP	O	3	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	people	people	NNS	O	8	nsubj
8	began	begin	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	wonder	wonder	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	if	if	IN	O	14	mark
12	Google	Google	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nsubj
13	would	would	MD	O	14	aux
14	build	build	VB	O	10	advcl
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	killer	killer	NN	O	17	compound
17	piece	piece	NN	O	14	dobj
18	of	of	IN	O	19	case
19	hardware	hardware	NN	O	17	nmod
20	that	that	WDT	O	23	nsubj
21	would	would	MD	O	23	aux
22	finally	finally	RB	O	23	advmod
23	give	give	VB	O	17	acl:relcl
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	iPhone	iPhone	NNP	O	23	iobj
26	a	a	DT	O	28	det
27	true	true	JJ	O	28	amod
28	challenge	challenge	NN	O	23	dobj
29	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Here	here	RB	O	2	advmod
2	's	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	how	how	WRB	O	5	advmod
4	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	works	work	VBZ	O	2	dep
6	:	:	:	O	2	punct

1	``	``	``	O	3	punct
2	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	seemed	seem	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
5	be	be	VB	O	9	cop
6	a	a	DT	O	9	det
7	Jap	jap	NN	MISC	9	compound
8	reconnaissance	reconnaissance	NN	O	9	compound
9	patrol	patrol	NN	O	3	xcomp
10	...	...	:	O	3	punct
11	one	one	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	group	group	NN	O	13	nsubj
13	stopped	stop	VBD	O	3	parataxis
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	ate	eat	VBD	O	13	conj
16	chow	chow	NN	O	15	dobj
17	on	on	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	road	road	NN	O	20	compound
20	bank	bank	NN	O	15	nmod
21	opposite	opposite	JJ	O	20	dep
22	us	we	PRP	O	13	dobj
23	;	;	:	O	3	punct
24	we	we	PRP	O	27	nsubj
25	were	be	VBD	O	27	cop
26	scared	scared	JJ	O	27	amod
27	stiff	stiff	JJ	O	38	dep
28	they	they	PRP	O	30	nsubj
29	would	would	MD	O	30	aux
30	come	come	VB	O	27	ccomp
31	over	over	RB	O	30	advmod
32	and	and	CC	O	30	cc
33	find	find	VB	O	30	conj
34	us	we	PRP	O	33	dobj
35	.	.	.	O	27	punct
36	It	it	PRP	O	38	nsubj
37	was	be	VBD	O	38	cop
38	hard	hard	JJ	O	3	parataxis
39	for	for	IN	O	40	case
40	the	the	DT	O	38	nmod
41	wounded	wound	VBN	O	40	amod
42	to	to	TO	O	43	mark
43	lie	lie	VB	O	38	xcomp
44	quiet	quiet	JJ	O	43	advmod
45	.	.	.	O	44	punct
46	Our	we	PRP$	O	48	nmod:poss
47	tank	tank	NN	O	48	compound
48	driver	driver	NN	O	43	dobj
49	had	have	VBD	O	48	acl:relcl
50	a	a	DT	O	51	det
51	rivet	rivet	NN	O	49	dobj
52	stuck	stick	VBD	O	51	acl:relcl
53	in	in	IN	O	55	case
54	his	he	PRP$	O	55	nmod:poss
55	throat	throat	NN	O	52	nmod
56	-	-	:	O	3	punct
57	every	every	DT	O	58	det
58	time	time	NN	O	67	nsubj
59	he	he	PRP	O	60	nsubj
60	took	take	VBD	O	58	acl:relcl
61	a	a	DT	O	62	det
62	drink	drink	NN	O	60	dobj
63	,	,	,	O	67	punct
64	the	the	DT	O	65	det
65	water	water	NN	O	67	nsubj
66	would	would	MD	O	67	aux
67	come	come	VB	O	3	parataxis
68	leaking	leak	VBG	O	67	xcomp
69	out	out	IN	O	68	compound:prt
70	...	...	:	O	3	punct
71	''	''	''	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	booster	booster	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
3	used	use	VBN	O	2	acl
4	for	for	IN	O	8	case
5	the	the	DT	O	8	det
6	Ares	Ares	NNP	O	8	compound
7	I-X	I-X	NNP	O	8	compound
8	launch	launch	NN	O	3	nmod
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	aux
10	being	be	VBG	O	11	auxpass
11	modified	modify	VBN	O	0	ROOT
12	by	by	IN	O	13	mark
13	adding	add	VBG	O	11	advcl
14	new	new	JJ	O	13	xcomp
15	forward	forward	RB	O	16	advmod
16	structures	structure	NNS	O	14	dep
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	a	a	DT	O	21	det
19	fifth	fifth	JJ	ORDINAL	21	amod
20	segment	segment	NN	O	21	compound
21	simulator	simulator	NN	O	16	conj
22	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Now	now	RB	DATE	3	advmod
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	faced	face	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	his	he	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
5	most	most	RBS	O	6	advmod
6	important	important	JJ	O	7	amod
7	task	task	NN	O	3	dobj
8	yet	yet	RB	O	3	advmod
9	:	:	:	O	3	punct
10	use	use	VB	O	3	parataxis
11	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
12	last	last	JJ	O	13	amod
13	sputtering	sputtering	NN	O	10	dobj
14	,	,	,	O	10	punct
15	wheezing	wheeze	VBG	O	10	parataxis
16	boats	boat	NNS	O	15	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	ferret	ferret	VB	O	15	advcl
19	precious	precious	JJ	O	21	amod
20	human	human	JJ	O	21	amod
21	cargo	cargo	NN	O	18	dobj
22	across	across	IN	O	24	case
23	enemy-infested	enemy-infested	JJ	O	24	amod
24	waters	water	NNS	O	21	nmod
25	to	to	TO	O	28	case
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	southern	southern	JJ	O	28	amod
28	island	island	NN	O	18	nmod
29	of	of	IN	O	30	case
30	Mindanao	Mindanao	NNP	LOCATION	28	nmod
31	,	,	,	O	18	punct
32	where	where	WRB	O	41	advmod
33	MacArthur	MacArthur	NNP	ORGANIZATION	41	nsubjpass
34	and	and	CC	O	33	cc
35	his	he	PRP$	O	36	nmod:poss
36	contingent	contingent	NN	O	33	conj
37	could	could	MD	O	41	aux
38	then	then	RB	O	41	advmod
39	be	be	VB	O	41	auxpass
40	safely	safely	RB	O	41	advmod
41	flown	fly	VBN	O	18	advcl
42	to	to	TO	O	43	case
43	Melbourne	Melbourne	NNP	LOCATION	41	nmod
44	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	concert	concert	NN	O	3	compound
3	tour	tour	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
5	start	start	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	5	punct
9	but	but	CC	O	5	cc
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	long-term	long-term	JJ	O	13	amod
12	master	master	NN	O	13	compound
13	plan	plan	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	was	be	VBD	O	5	conj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	take	take	VB	O	14	xcomp
17	it	it	PRP	O	16	dobj
18	to	to	TO	O	20	case
19	other	other	JJ	O	20	amod
20	cities	city	NNS	O	16	nmod
21	in	in	IN	O	22	case
22	Europe	Europe	NNP	LOCATION	20	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
24	Asia	Asia	NNP	LOCATION	22	conj
25	as	as	RB	O	16	advmod
26	well	well	RB	O	25	mwe
27	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	3	cc
2	she	she	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	goes	go	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	even	even	RB	O	5	advmod
5	greener	greener	JJR	O	11	amod
6	by	by	IN	O	7	mark
7	waking	wake	VBG	O	5	advcl
8	up	up	RP	O	7	compound:prt
9	at	at	IN	O	10	case
10	5	5	CD	TIME	7	nmod
11	a.m.	a.m.	NN	TIME	3	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	cook	cook	VB	O	11	acl
14	overflowing	overflow	VBG	O	15	amod
15	deliveries	delivery	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	of	of	IN	O	18	case
17	local	local	JJ	O	18	amod
18	produce	produce	NN	O	15	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	3	det
2	third-party	third-party	JJ	O	3	amod
3	candidate	candidate	NN	O	27	nsubj
4	there	there	EX	O	5	expl
5	attracting	attract	VBG	O	3	acl:relcl
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	fair	fair	JJ	O	8	amod
8	amount	amount	NN	O	5	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	support	support	NN	O	8	nmod
11	-	-	:	O	13	punct
12	14	14	CD	PERCENT	13	nummod
13	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	3	dep
14	for	for	IN	O	17	case
15	independent	independent	JJ	O	17	amod
16	Chris	Chris	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Daggett	Daggett	NNP	PERSON	13	nmod
18	in	in	IN	O	24	case
19	the	the	DT	O	24	det
20	Monmouth	Monmouth	NNP	O	24	compound
21	University/Gannett	University/Gannett	NNP	O	24	compound
22	New	New	NNP	O	24	compound
23	Jersey	Jersey	NNP	O	24	compound
24	Poll	Poll	NNP	O	13	nmod
25	--	--	:	O	13	punct
26	could	could	MD	O	27	aux
27	have	have	VB	O	0	ROOT
28	an	a	DT	O	29	det
29	impact	impact	NN	O	27	dobj
30	on	on	IN	O	32	case
31	the	the	DT	O	32	det
32	outcome	outcome	NN	O	29	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	27	punct

1	Media	Media	NNP	O	2	nsubj
2	becomes	become	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	platform	platform	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	with	with	IN	O	6	case
6	a	a	DT	O	4	nmod
7	funnel	funnel	VB	O	2	ccomp
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	traffic	traffic	NN	O	7	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	conversions	conversion	NNS	O	9	conj
12	to	to	TO	O	15	case
13	alternative	alternative	JJ	O	15	amod
14	revenue	revenue	NN	O	15	compound
15	streams	stream	NNS	O	7	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	iMac	iMac	NNP	O	4	nsubjpass
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	auxpass
4	equipped	equip	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	with	with	IN	O	10	case
6	a	a	DT	O	10	det
7	new	new	JJ	O	10	amod
8	SD	sd	NN	O	10	compound
9	card	card	NN	O	10	compound
10	slot	slot	NN	O	4	nmod
11	under	under	IN	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	DVD	dvd	NN	O	14	compound
14	drive	drive	NN	O	4	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	4	punct
16	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
17	back	back	RB	O	20	advmod
18	panel	panel	NN	O	19	compound
19	ports	port	NNS	O	20	nsubj
20	provide	provide	VBP	O	4	conj
21	Gigabit	Gigabit	NNP	O	22	compound
22	Ethernet	Ethernet	NNP	O	20	dobj
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	Mini	Mini	NNP	O	25	compound
25	DisplayPort	DisplayPort	NNP	O	22	conj
26	,	,	,	O	22	punct
27	Firewire	Firewire	NNP	O	22	conj
28	800	800	CD	NUMBER	27	nummod
29	,	,	,	O	22	punct
30	four	four	CD	NUMBER	33	nummod
31	USB	usb	JJ	O	33	amod
32	2.0	2.0	CD	NUMBER	33	nummod
33	ports	port	NNS	O	22	conj
34	,	,	,	O	22	punct
35	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
36	hybrid	hybrid	NN	O	40	compound
37	analog/optical	analog/optical	JJ	O	40	amod
38	digital	digital	JJ	O	40	amod
39	audio	audio	NN	O	40	compound
40	input	input	NN	O	22	conj
41	and	and	CC	O	40	cc
42	output	output	NN	O	43	compound
43	ports	port	NNS	O	40	conj
44	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Google	Google	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nsubj
2	tonight	tonight	RB	DATE	3	nmod:tmod
3	moved	move	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	quashed	quash	VBN	O	3	xcomp
6	rumors	rumor	NNS	O	5	dobj
7	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
8	it	it	PRP	O	10	nsubj
9	would	would	MD	O	10	aux
10	make	make	VB	O	5	ccomp
11	its	its	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
12	own	own	JJ	O	13	amod
13	smartphone	smartphone	NN	O	10	dobj
14	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Simon	Simon	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubjpass
3	could	could	MD	O	6	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
5	be	be	VB	O	6	auxpass
6	reached	reach	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	8	case
8	comment	comment	NN	O	6	nmod
9	Friday	Friday	NNP	DATE	10	compound
10	night	night	NN	TIME	6	nmod:tmod
11	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Paul	Paul	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Saffo	Saffo	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	an	a	DT	O	6	det
5	American	american	JJ	MISC	6	amod
6	futurologist	futurologist	NN	O	2	appos
7	,	,	,	O	2	punct
8	recently	recently	RB	DATE	9	advmod
9	told	tell	VBD	O	0	ROOT
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	Telegraph	Telegraph	NNP	O	9	dobj
12	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	ultra-rich	ultra-rich	JJ	O	17	nsubj
15	may	may	MD	O	17	aux
16	slowly	slowly	RB	O	17	advmod
17	evolve	evolve	VB	O	9	ccomp
18	into	into	IN	O	21	case
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	separate	separate	JJ	O	21	amod
21	species	species	NNS	O	17	nmod
22	thanks	thanks	NNS	O	17	advmod
23	to	to	TO	O	25	case
24	medical	medical	JJ	O	25	amod
25	advances	advance	NNS	O	22	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Senator	Senator	NNP	O	3	compound
2	Richard	Richard	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Lugar	Lugar	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	ranking	ranking	JJ	O	7	amod
7	Republican	Republican	NNP	MISC	3	appos
8	on	on	IN	O	13	case
9	the	the	DT	O	13	det
10	Senate	Senate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
11	Foreign	Foreign	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
12	Relations	Relations	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	compound
13	Committee	Committee	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	3	punct
15	is	be	VBZ	O	17	cop
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	guest	guest	NN	O	0	ROOT
18	on	on	IN	O	19	case
19	C-Span	C-Span	NNP	O	17	nmod
20	's	's	POS	O	19	case
21	``	``	``	O	19	punct
22	Newsmakers	newsmaker	NNS	MISC	19	dep
23	.	.	.	O	17	punct
24	''	''	''	O	17	punct

1	Among	among	IN	O	5	case
2	the	the	DT	O	5	det
3	thirteen	thirteen	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
4	new	new	JJ	O	5	amod
5	taxes	tax	NNS	O	20	nmod
6	found	find	VBN	O	5	acl
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	bill	bill	NN	O	6	nmod
10	by	by	IN	O	11	case
11	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	6	nmod
12	for	for	IN	O	14	case
13	Tax	Tax	NNP	O	14	compound
14	Reform	Reform	NNP	O	11	nmod
15	is	be	VBZ	O	20	cop
16	the	the	DT	O	20	det
17	``	``	``	O	20	punct
18	medicine	medicine	NN	O	20	compound
19	cabinet	cabinet	NN	O	20	compound
20	tax	tax	NN	O	0	ROOT
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	''	''	''	O	20	punct
23	which	which	WDT	O	20	acl:relcl
24	bars	bar	NNS	O	25	compound
25	people	people	NNS	O	20	nsubj
26	from	from	IN	O	27	mark
27	paying	pay	VBG	O	25	acl
28	for	for	IN	O	30	case
29	non-prescription	non-prescription	JJ	O	30	amod
30	medicine	medicine	NN	O	27	nmod
31	with	with	IN	O	35	case
32	tax-deferred	tax-deferred	JJ	O	35	amod
33	health	health	NN	O	35	compound
34	savings	savings	NNS	O	35	compound
35	accounts	account	NNS	O	27	nmod
36	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	good	good	JJ	O	3	amod
3	news	news	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	13	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	13	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	segment	segment	NN	O	13	nsubj
5	I	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	taped	tape	VBD	O	4	acl:relcl
7	yesterday	yesterday	NN	DATE	6	nmod:tmod
8	with	with	IN	O	10	case
9	Bill	Bill	NNP	PERSON	10	compound
10	Moyers	Moyers	NNP	PERSON	6	nmod
11	should	should	MD	O	13	aux
12	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
13	available	available	JJ	O	0	ROOT
14	on	on	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	PBS	PBS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
17	site	site	NN	DATE	13	nmod
18	later	later	RB	DATE	19	advmod
19	today	today	NN	DATE	17	nmod:tmod
20	--	--	:	O	17	punct
21	here	here	RB	O	17	advmod
22	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	where	where	WRB	O	6	advmod
4	evolution	evolution	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	aux
6	unfolding	unfold	VBG	O	2	advcl
7	as	as	IN	O	11	mark
8	direct	direct	JJ	O	10	amod
9	consumer	consumer	NN	O	10	compound
10	spending	spending	NN	O	11	nsubj
11	spurs	spur	VBZ	O	6	advcl
12	media	media	NNS	O	13	compound
13	development	development	NN	O	11	dobj
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Got	Got	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	anything	anything	NN	O	1	dep
3	else	else	RB	O	2	advmod
4	?	?	.	O	1	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	new	new	JJ	O	3	amod
3	screens	screen	NNS	O	6	nsubjpass
4	are	be	VBP	O	6	auxpass
5	also	also	RB	O	6	advmod
6	LED	lead	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	backlit	backlit	JJ	O	6	dobj
8	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	11	punct
9	unlike	unlike	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	30	30	CD	NUMBER	7	nmod
12	''	''	''	O	11	punct
13	Cinema	Cinema	NNP	O	14	nsubj
14	Display	display	VB	O	11	acl:relcl
15	HD	hd	NN	O	14	dobj
16	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	11	punct
17	,	,	,	O	7	punct
18	which	which	WDT	O	19	nsubj
19	means	mean	VBZ	O	7	acl:relcl
20	they	they	PRP	O	21	nsubj
21	turn	turn	VB	O	19	ccomp
22	on	on	RP	O	21	compound:prt
23	instantly	instantly	RB	O	21	advmod
24	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
25	allow	allow	VB	O	21	conj
26	for	for	IN	O	27	case
27	finer	finer	JJR	O	25	nmod
28	grained	grain	VBN	O	27	acl
29	control	control	NN	O	28	dobj
30	over	over	IN	O	31	case
31	brightness	brightness	NN	O	29	nmod
32	than	than	IN	O	35	case
33	conventional	conventional	JJ	O	35	amod
34	cold	cold	JJ	O	35	amod
35	cathode	cathode	NN	O	28	nmod
36	fluorescent	fluorescent	JJ	O	38	amod
37	lamp	lamp	NN	O	38	compound
38	backlighting	backlighting	NN	O	21	dobj
39	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	7	cc
2	,	,	,	O	7	punct
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	course	course	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	Ebel	Ebel	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	seems	seem	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
9	certainly	certainly	RB	O	10	advmod
10	recognize	recognize	VB	O	7	xcomp
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	CwF	cwf	NN	O	10	dobj
13	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	14	punct
14	connect	connect	VB	O	10	parataxis
15	with	with	IN	O	16	case
16	fans	fan	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	14	punct
18	part	part	NN	O	10	dobj
19	that	that	WDT	O	20	nsubj
20	has	have	VBZ	O	18	acl:relcl
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	go	go	VB	O	20	xcomp
23	along	along	RP	O	22	compound:prt
24	with	with	IN	O	26	case
25	this	this	DT	O	26	det
26	RtB	rtb	NN	O	22	nmod
27	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	28	punct
28	reason	reason	NN	O	26	dep
29	to	to	TO	O	30	mark
30	buy	buy	VB	O	28	acl
31	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	28	punct
32	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Overall	overall	RB	O	7	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	7	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	new	new	JJ	O	5	amod
5	machines	machine	NNS	O	7	nsubj
6	also	also	RB	O	7	advmod
7	meet	meet	VBP	O	0	ROOT
8	Energy	Energy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
9	Star	Star	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	dobj
10	5.0	5.0	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
11	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
12	EPEAT	EPEAT	NNP	O	14	compound
13	Gold	Gold	NNP	O	14	compound
14	standards	standard	NNS	O	9	conj
15	for	for	IN	O	17	case
16	energy	energy	NN	O	17	compound
17	efficiency	efficiency	NN	O	9	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
19	environmentally-sound	environmentally-sound	JJ	O	20	amod
20	design	design	NN	O	9	conj
21	,	,	,	O	20	punct
22	manufacturing	manufacturing	NN	O	20	appos
23	,	,	,	O	9	punct
24	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
25	use	use	NN	O	9	conj
26	of	of	IN	O	28	case
27	recyclable	recyclable	JJ	O	28	amod
28	materials	material	NNS	O	25	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	*	*	SYM	O	4	dep
2	The	the	DT	O	4	det
3	amusing	amusing	JJ	O	4	amod
4	thing	thing	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	about	about	IN	O	9	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	right	right	NN	O	9	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	claim	claim	NN	O	4	nmod
10	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
11	Bill	Bill	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Ayers	Ayers	NNP	PERSON	16	nsubj
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	Jeremiah	Jeremiah	NNP	PERSON	15	compound
15	Wright	Wright	NNP	PERSON	12	conj
16	visited	visit	VBD	O	4	dep
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	White	White	NNP	LOCATION	19	compound
19	House	House	NNP	LOCATION	20	nsubj
20	is	be	VBZ	O	16	ccomp
21	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
22	officials	official	NNS	O	23	nsubj
23	made	make	VBD	O	20	ccomp
24	it	it	PRP	O	25	nsubj
25	clear	clear	JJ	O	23	xcomp
26	on	on	IN	O	30	case
27	the	the	DT	O	30	det
28	very	very	RB	O	29	advmod
29	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	30	amod
30	page	page	NN	O	25	nmod
31	of	of	IN	O	34	case
32	the	the	DT	O	34	det
33	document	document	NN	O	34	compound
34	dump	dump	NN	O	30	nmod
35	-	-	:	O	36	punct
36	even	even	RB	O	25	dep
37	before	before	IN	O	39	case
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	names	name	NNS	O	36	nmod
40	!	!	.	O	36	punct
41	-	-	:	O	36	punct
42	that	that	IN	O	45	mark
43	the	the	DT	O	44	det
44	duo	duo	NN	O	45	nsubj
45	were	be	VBD	O	25	ccomp
46	n't	not	RB	O	45	neg
47	who	who	WP	O	49	dobj
48	they	they	PRP	O	49	nsubj
49	seemed	seem	VBD	O	23	ccomp
50	to	to	TO	O	51	mark
51	be	be	VB	O	49	xcomp
52	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
2	lol	lol	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	this	this	DT	O	5	nsubjpass
4	was	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
5	filmed	film	VBN	O	2	acl:relcl
6	right	right	RB	O	9	advmod
7	down	down	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	street	street	NN	O	5	nmod
10	from	from	IN	O	11	case
11	me	I	PRP	O	9	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	5	punct
13	so	so	RB	O	14	advmod
14	enjoy	enjoy	VB	O	5	ccomp
15	my	my	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
16	`	`	``	O	17	punct
17	hood	hood	NN	O	14	dobj
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Android	Android	NNP	O	2	nsubj
2	struggled	struggle	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	somewhat	somewhat	RB	O	2	advmod
4	withe	withe	VB	O	2	ccomp
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	G1	g1	NN	O	7	compound
7	device	device	NN	O	4	dobj
8	,	,	,	O	2	punct
9	but	but	CC	O	2	cc
10	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
11	seemingly	seemingly	RB	O	2	conj
12	about	about	IN	O	26	case
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	experience	experience	VB	O	26	dep
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	resurgence	resurgence	NN	O	14	dobj
17	with	with	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	launch	launch	NN	O	14	nmod
20	of	of	IN	O	23	case
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	Droid	Droid	NNP	MISC	23	compound
23	smartphone	smartphone	NN	O	19	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	26	punct
25	a	a	DT	O	26	det
26	device	device	NN	O	11	nmod
27	that	that	WDT	O	29	nsubj
28	is	be	VBZ	O	29	aux
29	garnering	garner	VBG	O	26	acl:relcl
30	brilliant	brilliant	JJ	O	31	amod
31	reviews	review	NNS	O	29	dobj
32	,	,	,	O	29	punct
33	even	even	RB	O	38	advmod
34	from	from	IN	O	38	case
35	the	the	DT	O	38	det
36	most	most	RBS	O	37	advmod
37	Apple-centric	apple-centric	JJ	MISC	38	amod
38	authors	author	NNS	O	29	nmod
39	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Executives	executive	NNS	O	4	nsubj
2	there	there	EX	O	4	expl
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	cop
4	receptive	receptive	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	7	case
6	new	new	JJ	O	7	amod
7	ideas	idea	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
9	move	move	VB	O	4	conj
10	forward	forward	RB	O	9	advmod
11	quickly	quickly	RB	O	9	advmod
12	,	,	,	O	9	punct
13	leaving	leave	VBG	O	9	xcomp
14	me	I	PRP	O	16	nsubj
15	somewhat	somewhat	RB	O	16	advmod
16	optimistic	optimistic	JJ	O	13	xcomp
17	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	looks	look	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	HOrrendous	horrendous	JJ	O	2	xcomp
4	!	!	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	stack	stack	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	5	auxpass
5	positioned	position	VBN	O	2	ccomp
6	on	on	IN	O	7	case
7	top	top	NN	O	5	nmod
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	segments	segment	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	already	already	RB	O	5	advmod
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	place	place	NN	O	5	nmod
14	on	on	IN	O	18	case
15	the	the	DT	O	18	det
16	mobile	mobile	JJ	O	18	amod
17	launcher	launcher	NN	O	18	compound
18	platform	platform	NN	O	5	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	21	case
20	High	High	NNP	LOCATION	21	compound
21	Bay	Bay	NNP	LOCATION	18	nmod
22	3	3	CD	LOCATION	21	nummod
23	,	,	,	O	5	punct
24	completing	complete	VBG	O	5	xcomp
25	assembly	assembly	NN	O	24	dobj
26	of	of	IN	O	29	case
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	327-foot-tall	327-foot-tall	JJ	O	29	amod
29	rocket	rocket	NN	O	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	5	mark
2	consumers	consumer	NNS	O	5	nsubj
3	have	have	VBP	O	5	aux
4	been	be	VBN	O	5	aux
5	enjoying	enjoy	VBG	O	21	advcl
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	service	service	NN	O	5	dobj
8	since	since	IN	O	10	case
9	its	its	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	launch	launch	NN	O	5	nmod
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	2007	2007	CD	DATE	10	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	21	punct
14	recent	recent	JJ	O	15	amod
15	statements	statement	NNS	O	21	nsubj
16	by	by	IN	O	20	case
17	a	a	DT	O	20	det
18	News	News	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
19	Corp	Corp	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
20	exec	exec	NN	O	15	nmod
21	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
22	people	people	NNS	O	21	dobj
23	wondering	wonder	VBG	O	22	acl
24	:	:	:	O	21	punct
25	can	can	MD	O	27	aux
26	Hulu	Hulu	NNP	LOCATION	27	nsubj
27	make	make	VB	O	21	parataxis
28	the	the	DT	O	31	det
29	ad-supported	ad-supported	JJ	O	31	amod
30	model	model	NN	O	31	compound
31	work	work	NN	O	27	dobj
32	?	?	.	O	21	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	does	do	VBZ	O	4	aux
3	n't	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	say	say	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	President	President	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Obama	Obama	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	responsible	responsible	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	for	for	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	need	need	NN	O	4	nmod
8	for	for	IN	O	11	case
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	special	special	JJ	O	11	amod
11	election	election	NN	O	7	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	17	case
13	the	the	DT	O	17	det
14	Upstate	Upstate	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
15	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
16	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
17	district	district	NN	O	11	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	4	punct
19	having	have	VBG	O	20	aux
20	tapped	tap	VBN	O	4	xcomp
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	former	former	JJ	O	23	amod
23	congressman	congressman	NN	O	20	dobj
24	in	in	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	district	district	NN	O	20	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	26	punct
28	Rep.	Rep.	NNP	O	30	compound
29	John	John	NNP	PERSON	30	compound
30	McHugh	McHugh	NNP	PERSON	26	appos
31	,	,	,	O	26	punct
32	R-NY	R-NY	NNP	O	26	appos
33	,	,	,	O	26	punct
34	as	as	IN	O	38	case
35	his	he	PRP$	O	38	nmod:poss
36	new	new	JJ	O	38	amod
37	Army	Army	NNP	O	38	compound
38	Secretary	Secretary	NNP	O	26	nmod
39	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	3	3	CD	PERCENT	3	compound
3	%	%	NN	PERCENT	4	amod
4	discount	discount	NN	O	6	nsubjpass
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	auxpass
6	reflected	reflect	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	as	as	IN	O	10	case
8	``	``	``	O	10	punct
9	Instant	instant	JJ	O	10	amod
10	Discount	discount	NN	O	6	nmod
11	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	12	punct
12	s	s	NNS	O	10	dep
13	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	12	punct
14	''	''	''	O	10	punct
15	during	during	IN	O	16	case
16	checkout	checkout	NN	O	6	nmod
17	at	at	IN	O	18	case
18	ClubMac	ClubMac	NNP	O	16	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	6	punct
20	after	after	IN	O	25	mark
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	items	item	NNS	O	25	nsubjpass
23	have	have	VBP	O	25	aux
24	been	be	VBN	O	25	auxpass
25	placed	place	VBN	O	6	advcl
26	in	in	IN	O	29	case
27	your	you	PRP$	O	29	nmod:poss
28	shopping	shopping	NN	O	29	compound
29	cart	cart	NN	O	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	6	mark
2	you	you	PRP	O	6	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	6	cop
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	media	media	NNS	O	6	compound
6	exec	exec	NN	O	24	advcl
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	you	you	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	look	look	VBP	O	6	conj
10	at	at	IN	O	12	case
11	your	you	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	product	product	NN	O	9	nmod
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	at	at	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	DATE	16	det
16	end	end	NN	DATE	12	conj
17	of	of	IN	DATE	19	case
18	the	the	DT	DATE	19	det
19	day	day	NN	DATE	16	nmod
20	it	it	PRP	O	24	nsubj
21	's	be	VBZ	O	24	cop
22	a	a	DT	O	24	det
23	digital	digital	JJ	O	24	amod
24	file	file	NN	O	0	ROOT
25	that	that	WDT	O	28	nsubjpass
26	can	can	MD	O	28	aux
27	be	be	VB	O	28	auxpass
28	copied	copy	VBN	O	24	acl:relcl
29	,	,	,	O	24	punct
30	then	then	RB	O	32	advmod
31	you	you	PRP	O	32	nsubj
32	have	have	VBP	O	24	parataxis
33	a	a	DT	O	35	det
34	serious	serious	JJ	O	35	amod
35	problem	problem	NN	O	32	dobj
36	with	with	IN	O	38	case
37	your	you	PRP$	O	38	nmod:poss
38	format	format	NN	O	35	nmod
39	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	Sounds	sound	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
2	intrepid	intrepid	JJ	O	1	xcomp
3	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	7	cc
2	,	,	,	O	7	punct
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	course	course	NN	O	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	uses	use	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	social	social	JJ	O	9	amod
9	media	media	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	connect	connect	VB	O	7	xcomp
12	as	as	RB	O	13	advmod
13	much	much	JJ	O	11	xcomp
14	as	as	IN	O	15	case
15	possible	possible	JJ	O	13	advcl
16	:	:	:	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	possibilities	possibility	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	cop
4	numerous	numerous	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	-	-	:	O	4	punct
6	career	career	NN	O	7	compound
7	choices	choice	NNS	O	4	dep
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	children	child	NNS	O	7	appos
10	,	,	,	O	7	punct
11	freedom	freedom	NN	O	7	appos
12	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	2	case
2	pigeons	pigeon	NNS	O	5	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	he	he	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	developed	develop	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	ideas	idea	NNS	O	5	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	11	case
9	``	``	``	O	11	punct
10	operant	operant	JJ	O	11	amod
11	conditioning	conditioning	NN	O	7	nmod
12	''	''	''	O	11	punct
13	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
14	``	``	``	O	15	punct
15	shaping	shape	VBG	O	11	conj
16	behavior	behavior	NN	O	15	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct
18	''	''	''	O	5	punct

1	``	``	``	O	9	punct
2	He	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	aux
4	yelling	yell	VBG	O	9	dep
5	.	.	.	O	4	punct
6	It	it	PRP	O	9	nsubj
7	was	be	VBD	O	9	cop
8	pretty	pretty	RB	O	9	advmod
9	bad	bad	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	.	.	.	O	9	punct
11	''	''	''	O	9	punct

1	Pakistan	Pakistan	NNP	LOCATION	0	ROOT
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	Daily	Daily	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
4	Times	Times	NNP	ORGANIZATION	1	dep
5	crops	crop	NNS	O	1	dep
6	Clinton	Clinton	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	comments	comment	NNS	O	5	dep

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	omission	omission	NN	O	17	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	4	case
4	multitouch	multitouch	NN	O	2	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	2	punct
6	which	which	WDT	O	7	nsubj
7	has	have	VBZ	O	2	acl:relcl
8	no	no	DT	O	9	neg
9	provision	provision	NN	O	7	dobj
10	anywhere	anywhere	RB	O	11	advmod
11	natively	natively	RB	O	9	amod
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	Android	Android	NNP	O	11	nmod
14	2.0	2.0	CD	NUMBER	13	nummod
15	,	,	,	O	2	punct
16	is	be	VBZ	O	17	cop
17	frustrating	frustrating	JJ	O	0	ROOT
18	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Republican	Republican	NNP	MISC	3	compound
3	nominee	nominee	NN	O	12	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	Assemblywoman	Assemblywoman	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
6	Dede	Dede	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Scozzafava	Scozzafava	NNP	PERSON	3	appos
8	,	,	,	O	3	punct
9	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
10	in	in	IN	O	12	case
11	third	third	JJ	ORDINAL	12	amod
12	place	place	NN	O	0	ROOT
13	in	in	IN	O	15	case
14	many	many	JJ	O	15	amod
15	polls	poll	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	12	punct
17	having	have	VBG	O	20	aux
18	largely	largely	RB	O	20	advmod
19	been	be	VBN	O	20	auxpass
20	abandoned	abandon	VBN	O	12	xcomp
21	by	by	IN	O	24	case
22	national	national	JJ	O	24	amod
23	Republican	republican	JJ	MISC	24	amod
24	figures	figure	NNS	O	20	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	Virginia	Virginia	NNP	LOCATION	7	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	7	punct
4	Democrat	Democrat	NNP	O	6	compound
5	Creigh	Creigh	NNP	O	6	compound
6	Deeds	Deeds	NNP	O	7	nsubj
7	trailed	trail	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	Republican	republican	JJ	MISC	10	amod
9	Bob	Bob	NNP	PERSON	10	compound
10	McDonnell	McDonnell	NNP	PERSON	7	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	44	44	CD	PERCENT	13	compound
13	%	%	NN	PERCENT	16	dep
14	to	to	TO	O	13	dep
15	55	55	CD	PERCENT	13	compound
16	%	%	NN	PERCENT	10	dep
17	,	,	,	O	10	punct
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	latest	latest	JJS	O	7	nmod
21	Washington	Washington	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
22	Post	Post	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
23	poll	poll	NN	O	20	dep
24	through	through	IN	O	25	case
25	October	October	NNP	DATE	7	nmod
26	25	25	CD	DATE	25	nummod
27	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	company	company	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	gave	give	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	her	she	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
5	just	just	RB	O	7	advmod
6	a	a	DT	DURATION	7	advmod
7	few	few	JJ	DURATION	8	nummod
8	minutes	minute	NNS	DURATION	3	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	leave	leave	VB	O	3	advcl
11	its	its	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	offices	office	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	SSA	SSA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nsubj
3	subsequently	subsequently	RB	O	4	advmod
4	sent	send	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	CMS	CMS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	iobj
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	letter	letter	NN	O	4	dobj
8	stating	state	VBG	O	7	acl
9	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	background	background	NN	O	12	compound
12	check	check	NN	O	13	nsubj
13	showed	show	VBD	O	8	ccomp
14	Studnitz	Studnitz	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
15	was	be	VBD	O	17	cop
16	``	``	``	O	17	punct
17	unsuitable	unsuitable	JJ	O	13	ccomp
18	''	''	''	O	17	punct
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	work	work	VB	O	17	xcomp
21	on	on	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	contract	contract	NN	O	20	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Even	even	RB	O	7	advmod
2	though	though	IN	O	7	mark
3	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
4	had	have	VBD	O	7	aux
5	already	already	RB	O	7	advmod
6	secretly	secretly	RB	O	7	advmod
7	signed	sign	VBD	O	45	advcl
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	contract	contract	NN	O	7	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	do	do	VB	O	7	advcl
12	as	as	RB	O	15	advmod
13	many	many	JJ	O	15	advmod
14	as	as	IN	O	15	advmod
15	50	50	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
16	concerts	concert	NNS	O	11	dobj
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
19	not	not	RB	O	20	neg
20	just	just	RB	O	16	conj
21	the	the	DT	O	23	det
22	10	10	CD	NUMBER	23	nummod
23	concerts	concert	NNS	O	20	dep
24	he	he	PRP	O	25	nsubj
25	announced	announce	VBD	O	45	parataxis
26	that	that	DT	O	27	det
27	day	day	NN	DURATION	25	nmod:tmod
28	,	,	,	O	25	punct
29	Michael	Michael	NNP	PERSON	30	compound
30	Jackson	Jackson	NNP	PERSON	45	nsubj
31	told	tell	VBD	O	45	parataxis
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	world	world	NN	O	31	nsubj
34	,	,	,	O	31	punct
35	``	``	``	O	31	punct
36	This	this	DT	O	41	nsubj
37	is	be	VBZ	O	41	cop
38	the	the	DT	O	41	det
39	final	final	JJ	O	41	amod
40	curtain	curtain	NN	O	41	compound
41	call	call	NN	O	31	ccomp
42	.	.	.	O	31	punct
43	I	I	PRP	O	45	nsubj
44	'll	will	MD	O	45	aux
45	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
46	you	you	PRP	O	45	dobj
47	in	in	IN	O	48	case
48	July	July	NNP	DATE	45	nmod
49	.	.	.	O	45	punct
50	''	''	''	O	45	punct

1	Perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	4	advmod
2	this	this	DT	O	4	nsubj
3	will	will	MD	O	4	aux
4	change	change	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	as	as	IN	O	11	mark
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	show	show	NN	O	10	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	new	new	JJ	O	10	amod
10	lineup	lineup	NN	O	11	nsubj
11	settles	settle	VBZ	O	4	advcl
12	into	into	IN	O	13	case
13	itself	itself	PRP	O	11	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	new	new	JJ	O	3	amod
3	iMac	iMac	NNP	O	5	nsubjpass
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	auxpass
5	priced	price	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	$	$	$	MONEY	7	dep
7	100	100	CD	MONEY	8	nmod:npmod
8	less	less	JJR	O	5	advmod
9	than	than	IN	O	14	case
10	Apple	Apple	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nmod:poss
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	standalone	standalone	JJ	O	14	amod
13	big	big	JJ	O	14	amod
14	screen	screen	NN	O	8	nmod
15	however	however	RB	O	14	advmod
16	,	,	,	O	5	punct
17	despite	despite	IN	O	18	case
18	packing	packing	NN	O	5	nmod
19	in	in	IN	O	22	case
20	a	a	DT	O	22	det
21	powerful	powerful	JJ	O	22	amod
22	computer	computer	NN	O	18	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
24	new	new	JJ	O	18	conj
25	LED	lead	VBN	O	24	acl
26	backlighting	backlighting	NN	O	25	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	3	cc
2	who	who	WP	O	3	nsubj
3	knows	know	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	4	case
2	all	all	PDT	O	4	det:predet
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	criticism	criticism	NN	O	6	nmod
5	Apple	Apple	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	nsubj
6	draws	draw	VBZ	O	19	ccomp
7	on	on	IN	O	11	case
8	the	the	DT	O	11	det
9	walled	walled	JJ	O	11	amod
10	garden	garden	NN	O	11	compound
11	nature	nature	NN	O	6	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	its	its	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	business	business	NN	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	19	punct
16	it	it	PRP	O	19	nsubj
17	has	have	VBZ	O	19	aux
18	even	even	RB	O	19	advmod
19	come	come	VBN	O	0	ROOT
20	around	around	IN	O	19	advmod
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	stripping	strip	VBG	O	20	advcl
23	DRM	DRM	NNP	MISC	22	dobj
24	and	and	CC	O	22	cc
25	allowing	allow	VBG	O	22	conj
26	users	user	NNS	O	25	dobj
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	download	download	VB	O	25	xcomp
29	mp3	mp3	NN	O	30	compound
30	files	file	NNS	O	28	dobj
31	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	So	so	RB	O	2	advmod
2	far	far	RB	O	7	advmod
3	,	,	,	O	7	punct
4	it	it	PRP	O	7	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	7	aux
6	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
7	gotten	get	VBN	O	0	ROOT
8	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
9	much	much	JJ	O	23	nsubj
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	reaction	reaction	NN	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	18	advmod
15	because	because	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	little	little	JJ	O	18	amod
18	kids	kid	NNS	O	12	acl:relcl
19	around	around	IN	O	20	case
20	here	here	RB	O	18	nmod
21	are	be	VBP	O	23	cop
22	very	very	RB	O	23	advmod
23	polite	polite	JJ	O	7	ccomp
24	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	5	5	LS	NUMBER	7	dep
2	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	7	punct
3	The	the	DT	O	6	det
4	winning	win	VBG	O	6	amod
5	six-word	six-word	JJ	O	6	amod
6	writer	writer	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	gets	get	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	keep	keep	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	all	all	PDT	O	12	det:predet
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	loot	loot	NN	O	9	dobj
13	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Apple	Apple	NNP	O	3	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	made	make	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	it	it	PRP	O	9	nsubj
5	painless	painless	JJ	O	9	dep
6	for	for	IN	O	7	case
7	consumers	consumer	NNS	O	5	nmod
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	spend	spend	VB	O	3	xcomp
10	money	money	NN	O	9	dobj
11	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
12	get	get	VB	O	9	conj
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	media	media	NNS	O	12	dobj
15	they	they	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	want	want	VBP	O	14	acl:relcl
17	where	where	WRB	O	19	advmod
18	they	they	PRP	O	19	nsubj
19	want	want	VBP	O	16	advcl
20	it	it	PRP	O	19	dobj
21	,	,	,	O	19	punct
22	proving	prove	VBG	O	19	advcl
23	that	that	IN	O	26	mark
24	consumers	consumer	NNS	O	26	nsubj
25	are	be	VBP	O	26	cop
26	happy	happy	JJ	O	22	ccomp
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	pay	pay	VB	O	26	xcomp
29	for	for	IN	O	30	case
30	media	media	NNS	O	28	nmod
31	if	if	IN	O	32	mark
32	delivered	deliver	VBN	O	19	advcl
33	in	in	IN	O	34	case
34	ways	way	NNS	O	32	nmod
35	that	that	WDT	O	36	nsubj
36	make	make	VBP	O	34	acl:relcl
37	it	it	PRP	O	42	nsubj
38	easy	easy	JJ	O	42	dep
39	and	and	CC	O	38	cc
40	blissful	blissful	JJ	O	38	conj
41	to	to	TO	O	42	mark
42	consume	consume	VB	O	36	xcomp
43	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Operant	operant	JJ	O	2	amod
2	conditioning	conditioning	NN	O	5	nsubjpass
3	can	can	MD	O	5	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	5	auxpass
5	used	use	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	shape	shape	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	behavior	behavior	NN	O	7	dobj
9	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	never	never	RB	O	3	neg
3	fails	fail	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	entertain	entertain	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	press	press	NN	O	5	dobj
8	,	,	,	O	3	punct
9	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
10	sometimes	sometimes	RB	O	13	advmod
11	it	it	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	even	even	RB	O	13	advmod
13	gives	give	VBZ	O	3	conj
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	stock	stock	NN	O	13	iobj
16	a	a	DT	O	18	det
17	small	small	JJ	O	18	amod
18	bump	bump	NN	O	13	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	This	this	DT	TIME	2	det
2	morning	morning	NN	TIME	13	nmod:tmod
3	,	,	,	O	13	punct
4	at	at	IN	O	7	case
5	8:20	8:20	CD	TIME	7	nummod
6	a.m.	a.m.	NN	TIME	7	compound
7	EST	est	NN	TIME	13	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	13	punct
9	I	I	PRP	O	13	nsubj
10	'll	will	MD	O	13	aux
11	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
12	on	on	IN	O	13	case
13	Democracy	Democracy	NNP	MISC	0	ROOT
14	Now	now	RB	DATE	13	advmod
15	talking	talk	VBG	O	13	xcomp
16	about	about	IN	O	18	case
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	variety	variety	NN	O	15	nmod
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	issues	issue	NNS	O	18	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Apple	Apple	NNP	O	2	compound
2	benchmarks	benchmark	NNS	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	high	high	JJ	O	5	amod
5	end	end	NN	O	2	dep
6	Nehalem	Nehalem	NNP	O	7	compound
7	Core	Core	NNP	O	5	dep
8	i7	i7	RB	O	5	advmod
9	as	as	IN	O	15	mark
10	being	be	VBG	O	15	cop
11	up	up	RP	O	13	dep
12	to	to	TO	O	13	dep
13	2.4	2.4	CD	NUMBER	14	nummod
14	times	time	NNS	O	15	nmod:npmod
15	faster	faster	JJR	O	2	dep
16	than	than	IN	O	20	case
17	the	the	DT	O	20	det
18	Core	core	NN	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
19	2	2	CD	NUMBER	20	nummod
20	Duo	duo	NN	O	15	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	music	music	NN	O	3	compound
3	industry	industry	NN	O	17	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	as	as	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	one	one	CD	NUMBER	3	nmod
8	that	that	WDT	O	10	nsubj
9	has	have	VBZ	O	10	aux
10	suffered	suffer	VBN	O	7	acl:relcl
11	most	most	JJS	O	10	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	carnage	carnage	NN	O	11	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	3	punct
16	is	be	VBZ	O	17	cop
17	ripest	ripest	JJS	O	0	ROOT
18	for	for	IN	O	19	case
19	change	change	NN	O	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	gave	give	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	him	he	PRP	O	2	iobj
4	extra	extra	JJ	O	5	amod
5	candy	candy	NN	O	2	dobj
6	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
7	Meade	Meade	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
8	took	take	VBD	O	2	conj
9	off	off	RP	O	8	compound:prt
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	mask	mask	NN	O	8	dobj
12	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
13	acted	act	VBD	O	8	conj
14	especially	especially	RB	O	15	advmod
15	friendly	friendly	JJ	O	13	xcomp
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	You	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	3	aux
3	see	see	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	all	all	PDT	O	6	det:predet
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	documents	document	NNS	O	3	dobj
7	here	here	RB	O	3	advmod
8	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	4	mark
2	hardcore	hardcore	NN	O	3	compound
3	hackers	hacker	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	had	have	VBD	O	23	advcl
5	any	any	DT	O	6	det
6	doubts	doubt	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	whether	whether	IN	O	15	mark
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	real-time	real-time	JJ	O	10	amod
10	web	web	NN	O	15	nsubj
11	was	be	VBD	O	15	cop
12	a	a	DT	O	15	det
13	legitimate	legitimate	JJ	O	15	amod
14	development	development	NN	O	15	compound
15	environment	environment	NN	O	4	ccomp
16	,	,	,	O	23	punct
17	Y	y	NN	O	23	nsubj
18	Combinator	Combinator	NNP	O	21	compound
19	co-founder	co-founder	NN	O	21	compound
20	Paul	Paul	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
21	Graham	Graham	NNP	PERSON	17	dep
22	is	be	VBZ	O	23	aux
23	dispelling	dispel	VBG	O	0	ROOT
24	them	they	PRP	O	23	dobj
25	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	Middleton	Middleton	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	she	she	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	had	have	VBD	O	2	ccomp
5	no	no	DT	O	6	neg
6	idea	idea	NN	O	4	dobj
7	how	how	WRB	O	9	advmod
8	she	she	PRP	O	9	nsubj
9	contracted	contract	VBD	O	6	dep
10	polio	polio	NNP	O	9	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	which	which	WDT	O	16	nsubj
13	was	be	VBD	O	16	cop
14	at	at	IN	O	16	case
15	epidemic	epidemic	JJ	O	16	amod
16	levels	level	NNS	O	10	acl:relcl
17	at	at	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	time	time	NN	DATE	16	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	4	punct
21	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
22	never	never	RB	O	23	neg
23	felt	feel	VBD	O	4	conj
24	pity	pity	NN	O	23	dobj
25	for	for	IN	O	26	case
26	herself	herself	PRP	O	23	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Keep	keep	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	your	you	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	readers	reader	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	aware	aware	JJ	O	1	xcomp
5	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
6	if	if	IN	O	7	dep
7	possible	possible	JJ	O	4	conj
8	,	,	,	O	1	punct
9	keep	keep	VB	O	1	dep
10	directing	direct	VBG	O	9	xcomp
11	them	they	PRP	O	10	dobj
12	to	to	TO	O	15	case
13	Doug	Doug	NNP	PERSON	15	nmod:poss
14	's	's	POS	O	13	case
15	website	website	NN	O	10	nmod
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	contribute	contribute	VB	O	15	acl
18	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Or	or	CC	O	5	cc
2	maybe	maybe	RB	O	5	advmod
3	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	just	just	RB	O	5	advmod
5	means	mean	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
7	,	,	,	O	23	punct
8	if	if	IN	O	12	mark
9	Yahoo	Yahoo	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	nsubj
10	ca	can	MD	O	12	aux
11	n't	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	find	find	VB	O	23	advcl
13	new	new	JJ	O	14	amod
14	ways	way	NNS	O	12	dobj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	monetize	monetize	VB	O	12	advcl
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	web	web	NN	O	16	dobj
19	,	,	,	O	23	punct
20	it	it	PRP	O	23	nsubj
21	can	can	MD	O	23	aux
22	instead	instead	RB	O	23	advmod
23	rent	rent	VB	O	5	ccomp
24	out	out	RP	O	23	compound:prt
25	office	office	NN	O	26	compound
26	space	space	NN	O	23	dobj
27	to	to	TO	O	28	case
28	someone	someone	NN	O	23	nmod
29	who	who	WP	O	30	nsubj
30	can	can	MD	O	28	acl:relcl
31	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	``	``	``	O	9	punct
2	She	she	PRP	O	9	nsubjpass
3	just	just	RB	O	4	advmod
4	loved	love	VBD	O	9	parataxis
5	life	life	NN	O	4	nsubj
6	.	.	.	O	4	punct
7	Whatever	whatever	WDT	O	9	nsubjpass
8	was	be	VBD	O	9	auxpass
9	given	give	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	case
11	her	she	PRP$	O	9	nmod
12	she	she	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	lived	live	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
14	it	it	PRP	O	13	dobj
15	day	day	NN	DURATION	13	nmod:tmod
16	by	by	IN	O	17	case
17	day	day	NN	DURATION	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	9	punct
19	''	''	''	O	9	punct

1	Five	five	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
2	super	super	JJ	O	3	amod
3	stacks	stack	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	make	make	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	up	up	RP	O	4	compound:prt
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	rocket	rocket	NN	O	10	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	upper	upper	JJ	O	10	amod
10	stage	stage	NN	O	4	dobj
11	that	that	WDT	O	13	nsubjpass
12	is	be	VBZ	O	13	auxpass
13	integrated	integrate	VBN	O	10	acl:relcl
14	with	with	IN	O	19	case
15	the	the	DT	O	19	det
16	four-segment	four-segment	JJ	O	19	amod
17	solid	solid	JJ	O	19	amod
18	rocket	rocket	NN	O	19	compound
19	booster	booster	NN	O	13	nmod
20	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	21	amod
21	stage	stage	NN	O	19	dep
22	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Five	five	CD	NUMBER	4	nsubj
2	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	3	compound
3	England	England	NNP	LOCATION	1	dep
4	states	state	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	land	land	NN	O	4	dobj
6	$	$	$	MONEY	7	dep
7	226M	226m	CD	MONEY	4	nmod:tmod
8	for	for	IN	O	10	case
9	smart	smart	JJ	O	10	amod
10	meters	meter	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	:	:	:	O	4	punct
12	At	at	IN	O	13	case
13	least	least	JJS	O	14	nmod:npmod
14	832,000	832,000	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
15	smart	smart	JJ	O	16	amod
16	meters	meter	NNS	O	19	nsubjpass
17	will	will	MD	O	19	aux
18	be	be	VB	O	19	auxpass
19	installed	install	VBN	O	4	parataxis
20	across	across	IN	O	22	case
21	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	22	compound
22	England	England	NNP	LOCATION	19	nmod
23	as	as	IN	O	25	case
24	a	a	DT	O	25	det
25	part	part	NN	O	22	nmod
26	of	of	IN	O	29	case
27	smart	smart	JJ	O	29	amod
28	grid	grid	NN	O	29	compound
29	projects	project	NNS	O	25	nmod
30	receiving	receive	VBG	O	19	xcomp
31	funding	funding	NN	O	30	dobj
32	from	from	IN	O	35	case
33	the	the	DT	O	35	det
34	U.S.	U.S.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	35	compound
35	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	nmod
36	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	43	case
37	Energy	Energy	NNP	ORGANIZATION	43	nmod:poss
38	's	's	POS	O	37	case
39	Smart	Smart	NNP	O	43	compound
40	Grid	Grid	NNP	O	43	compound
41	Investment	Investment	NNP	O	43	compound
42	Grant	Grant	NNP	O	43	compound
43	funding	funding	NN	O	35	nmod
44	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Illegal	illegal	JJ	O	2	amod
2	aliens	alien	NNS	O	5	nsubjpass
3	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	5	auxpass
5	covered	cover	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	since	since	IN	O	9	mark
8	there	there	EX	O	9	expl
9	is	be	VBZ	O	5	advcl
10	no	no	DT	O	11	neg
11	language	language	NN	O	9	nsubj
12	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubj
13	would	would	MD	O	14	aux
14	enforce	enforce	VB	O	11	acl:relcl
15	any	any	DT	O	16	det
16	prohibition	prohibition	NN	O	14	dobj
17	against	against	IN	O	18	case
18	them	they	PRP	O	16	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	drew	draw	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	attention	attention	NN	O	2	dobj
4	to	to	TO	O	6	case
5	her	she	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	gender	gender	NN	O	2	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	ethnicity	ethnicity	NN	O	6	conj
9	rather	rather	RB	O	12	case
10	than	than	IN	O	9	mwe
11	her	she	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	substance	substance	NN	O	2	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Constellation	constellation	NN	O	3	compound
3	program	program	NN	O	6	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
5	under	under	IN	O	6	case
6	pressure	pressure	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	as	as	IN	O	12	mark
8	a	a	DT	O	11	det
9	recent	recent	JJ	O	11	amod
10	committee	committee	NN	O	11	compound
11	report	report	NN	O	12	nsubj
12	depicted	depict	VBD	O	6	advcl
13	it	it	PRP	O	12	dobj
14	as	as	IN	O	16	case
15	overly	overly	RB	O	16	advmod
16	expensive	expensive	JJ	O	12	advcl
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	All	all	PDT	O	3	det:predet
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	video	video	NN	O	12	nsubj
4	from	from	IN	O	7	case
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	L.A.	L.A.	NNP	LOCATION	7	compound
7	rehearsals	rehearsal	NNS	O	3	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	the	the	DT	O	11	det
10	London	London	NNP	LOCATION	11	compound
11	concerts	concert	NNS	O	7	conj
12	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
13	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
14	be	be	VB	O	15	auxpass
15	fashioned	fashion	VBN	O	12	xcomp
16	into	into	IN	O	20	case
17	a	a	DT	O	20	det
18	blockbuster	blockbuster	NN	O	20	compound
19	theatrical	theatrical	NN	O	20	compound
20	release	release	NN	O	15	nmod
21	which	which	WDT	O	22	nsubj
22	promised	promise	VBD	O	20	acl:relcl
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	bring	bring	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	in	in	RP	O	24	compound:prt
26	countless	countless	JJ	O	27	amod
27	millions	million	NNS	O	24	dobj
28	more	more	RBR	O	24	advmod
29	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	Over	over	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	DURATION	3	det
3	years	year	NNS	DURATION	5	nmod
4	Jackson	Jackson	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	got	get	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	mileage	mileage	NN	O	5	dobj
7	out	out	IN	O	17	advmod
8	of	of	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	public	public	NN	O	7	nmod
11	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	13	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
13	music	music	NN	O	10	dep
14	industry	industry	NN	O	15	compound
15	executives	executive	NNS	O	13	dep
16	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	13	punct
17	underestimating	underestimate	VBG	O	6	acl
18	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
19	business	business	NN	O	20	compound
20	acumen	acumen	NNS	O	17	dobj
21	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	internet	internet	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	aux
4	stripping	strip	VBG	O	0	ROOT
5	them	they	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	their	they	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	control	control	NN	O	5	nmod
9	over	over	IN	O	10	case
10	the	the	DT	O	4	nmod
11	how	how	WRB	O	15	advmod
12	their	they	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	products	product	NNS	O	15	nsubjpass
14	are	be	VBP	O	15	auxpass
15	distributed	distribute	VBN	O	10	dep
16	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	3	cc
2	fun	fun	NN	O	3	compound
3	fact	fact	NN	O	8	nsubj
4	:	:	:	O	3	punct
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	school	school	NN	O	3	dep
7	they	they	PRP	O	6	dep
8	filmed	film	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	this	this	DT	O	10	nsubj
10	is	be	VBZ	O	8	ccomp
11	in	in	IN	O	14	mark
12	is	be	VBZ	O	14	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	school	school	NN	O	10	advcl
15	your	you	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
16	cutie	cutie	NN	O	18	compound
17	Anton	Anton	NNP	PERSON	18	compound
18	Yelchin	Yelchin	NNP	PERSON	19	nsubj
19	attended	attend	VBD	O	14	acl:relcl

1	As	as	IN	O	5	mark
2	they	they	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	had	have	VBD	O	5	aux
4	already	already	RB	O	5	advmod
5	done	do	VBN	O	24	advcl
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	everything	everything	NN	O	5	nmod
8	but	but	CC	O	9	case
9	name	name	NN	O	7	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	24	punct
11	the	the	DT	O	14	det
12	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
13	campaign	campaign	NN	O	14	compound
14	wing	wing	NN	O	24	nsubj
15	of	of	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	Republican	Republican	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
18	Party	Party	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nmod
19	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	21	punct
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	NRCC	nrcc	NN	ORGANIZATION	18	appos
22	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	21	punct
23	has	have	VBZ	O	24	aux
24	endorsed	endorse	VBN	O	0	ROOT
25	Hoffman	Hoffman	NNP	PERSON	24	dobj
26	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	Certainly	certainly	RB	O	5	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
5	seem	seem	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	help	help	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	Hoffman	Hoffman	NNP	PERSON	7	dobj
9	if	if	IN	O	11	mark
10	Scozzafava	Scozzafava	NNP	PERSON	11	nsubj
11	decided	decide	VBD	O	7	advcl
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	endorse	endorse	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	him	he	PRP	O	13	dobj
15	-	-	:	O	5	punct
16	but	but	CC	O	5	cc
17	only	only	RB	O	19	advmod
18	15	15	CD	PERCENT	19	nummod
19	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	24	nsubj
20	of	of	IN	O	23	case
21	Scozzafava	Scozzafava	NNP	PERSON	23	nmod:poss
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	voters	voter	NNS	O	19	nmod
24	had	have	VBD	O	5	conj
25	a	a	DT	O	27	det
26	favorable	favorable	JJ	O	27	amod
27	view	view	NN	O	24	dobj
28	of	of	IN	O	29	case
29	Hoffman	Hoffman	NNP	PERSON	27	nmod
30	,	,	,	O	5	punct
31	so	so	IN	O	5	dep
32	they	they	PRP	O	35	nsubj
33	are	be	VBP	O	35	aux
34	n't	not	RB	O	35	neg
35	going	go	VBG	O	5	parataxis
36	to	to	TO	O	37	mark
37	come	come	VB	O	35	xcomp
38	over	over	RP	O	37	compound:prt
39	easily	easily	RB	O	37	advmod
40	,	,	,	O	35	punct
41	if	if	IN	O	35	dep
42	at	at	IN	O	43	case
43	all	all	DT	O	41	nmod
44	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
2	Speaker	Speaker	NNP	O	4	compound
3	Nancy	Nancy	NNP	PERSON	4	compound
4	Pelosi	Pelosi	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
5	promises	promise	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	ram	ram	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	it	it	PRP	O	7	dobj
9	through	through	IN	O	10	case
10	quickly	quickly	RB	O	7	advcl
11	,	,	,	O	5	punct
12	exhibiting	exhibit	VBG	O	5	xcomp
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	disdain	disdain	NN	O	12	dobj
15	for	for	IN	O	17	case
16	her	she	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	countrymen	countryman	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	that	that	WDT	O	19	nsubj
19	makes	make	VBZ	O	14	acl:relcl
20	Marie	Marie	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
21	Antoinette	Antoinette	NNP	PERSON	22	nsubj
22	look	look	VB	O	19	ccomp
23	like	like	IN	O	25	case
24	a	a	DT	O	25	det
25	populist	populist	NN	O	22	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Each	each	DT	O	2	det
2	one	one	CD	NUMBER	3	nsubj
3	grows	grow	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	exponentially	exponentially	RB	O	3	advmod
5	;	;	:	O	3	punct
6	creates	create	VBZ	O	3	conj
7	dependent	dependent	JJ	O	8	amod
8	constituencies	constituency	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	that	that	WDT	O	10	nsubj
10	lobby	lobby	VBP	O	8	acl:relcl
11	for	for	IN	O	15	case
12	yet	yet	RB	O	13	advmod
13	more	more	JJR	O	15	amod
14	tax	tax	NN	O	15	compound
15	dollars	dollar	NNS	O	10	nmod
16	;	;	:	O	3	punct
17	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
18	empowers	empower	VBZ	O	3	conj
19	bureaucrats	bureaucrat	NNS	O	18	dobj
20	for	for	IN	O	24	mark
21	whom	whom	WP	O	24	dobj
22	mission	mission	NN	O	23	compound
23	failure	failure	NN	O	24	nsubj
24	ensures	ensure	VBZ	O	18	advcl
25	more	more	RBR	O	24	advmod
26	staff	staff	NN	O	24	dobj
27	,	,	,	O	26	punct
28	more	more	JJR	O	29	amod
29	money	money	NN	O	26	conj
30	,	,	,	O	26	punct
31	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
32	more	more	JJR	O	33	amod
33	power	power	NN	O	26	conj
34	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	live	live	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	in	in	IN	O	5	case
4	Rochester	Rochester	NNP	LOCATION	5	compound
5	NY	NY	NNP	LOCATION	2	nmod
6	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
7	took	take	VBD	O	2	conj
8	the	the	DT	DURATION	11	det
9	five	five	CD	DURATION	11	nummod
10	hour	hour	NN	DURATION	11	compound
11	drive	drive	NN	O	7	dobj
12	up	up	RB	O	11	advmod
13	to	to	TO	O	15	case
14	Saranac	Saranac	NNP	LOCATION	15	compound
15	Lake	Lake	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod
16	last	last	JJ	DATE	17	amod
17	Tuesday	Tuesday	NNP	DATE	7	nmod:tmod
18	to	to	TO	O	19	mark
19	see	see	VB	O	7	advcl
20	how	how	WRB	O	23	advmod
21	I	I	PRP	O	23	nsubj
22	could	could	MD	O	23	aux
23	help	help	VB	O	19	ccomp
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	Hoffman	Hoffman	NNP	PERSON	26	compound
26	campaign	campaign	NN	O	23	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Who	who	WP	O	3	nsubj
2	will	will	MD	O	3	aux
3	die	die	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	Every	every	DT	O	3	det
2	conservative	conservative	JJ	O	3	amod
3	woman	woman	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	knows	know	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	how	how	WRB	O	7	advmod
6	abortion	abortion	NN	O	7	nsubj
7	defines	define	VBZ	O	4	ccomp
8	most	most	RBS	O	9	advmod
9	modern	modern	JJ	O	10	amod
10	feminists	feminist	NNS	O	7	dobj
11	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	will	will	MD	O	3	aux
3	show	show	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	up	up	RP	O	3	compound:prt
5	as	as	IN	O	8	case
6	``	``	``	O	8	punct
7	Instant	instant	JJ	O	8	amod
8	Discount	discount	NN	O	3	nmod
9	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	10	punct
10	s	s	NNS	O	8	dep
11	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	10	punct
12	''	''	''	O	8	punct
13	during	during	IN	O	14	case
14	checkout	checkout	NN	O	3	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	3	punct
16	only	only	RB	O	20	advmod
17	affter	affter	RB	O	20	advmod
18	you	you	PRP	O	20	nsubj
19	've	have	VBP	O	20	aux
20	added	add	VBN	O	3	parataxis
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	Mac	Mac	NNP	O	20	dobj
23	to	to	TO	O	26	case
24	your	you	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
25	shopping	shopping	NN	O	26	compound
26	cart	cart	NN	O	20	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	UN	UN	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	still	still	RB	O	5	advmod
5	continuing	continue	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	its	its	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
7	electoral	electoral	JJ	O	8	amod
8	support	support	NN	O	5	dobj
9	,	,	,	O	5	punct
10	despite	despite	IN	O	14	case
11	this	this	DT	DATE	12	det
12	week	week	NN	DATE	14	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	attacks	attack	NNS	O	5	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Blacksn0w	blacksn0w	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
2	will	will	MD	O	4	aux
3	be	be	VB	O	4	auxpass
4	released	release	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	jailbreaking	jailbreaking	NN	O	8	compound
8	baseband	baseband	NN	O	4	nmod
9	unlocking	unlock	VBG	O	4	xcomp
10	masses	mass	NNS	O	13	nsubj
11	on	on	IN	O	12	case
12	November	November	NNP	DATE	10	nmod
13	4th	4th	JJ	DATE	9	xcomp
14	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
15	can	can	MD	O	17	aux
16	be	be	VB	O	17	auxpass
17	loaded	load	VBN	O	4	conj
18	onto	onto	IN	O	20	case
19	your	you	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	device	device	NN	O	17	nmod
21	directly	directly	RB	O	23	advmod
22	from	from	IN	O	23	case
23	Blackra1n	blackra1n	NN	O	17	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Or	or	CC	O	3	cc
2	its	its	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	ideological	ideological	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	rigidity	rigidity	NN	O	3	dep
5	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	study	study	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	by	by	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	Lewin	Lewin	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	Group	Group	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
7	estimates	estimate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
8	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
9	88	88	CD	NUMBER	10	compound
10	million	million	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
11	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	13	nsubj
12	would	would	MD	O	13	aux
13	lose	lose	VB	O	7	ccomp
14	their	they	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
15	private	private	JJ	O	16	amod
16	insurance	insurance	NN	O	13	dobj
17	if	if	IN	O	22	mark
18	a	a	DT	O	20	det
19	government	government	NN	O	20	compound
20	competitor	competitor	NN	O	22	nsubjpass
21	is	be	VBZ	O	22	auxpass
22	created	create	VBN	O	13	advcl
23	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Media	Media	NNP	O	2	compound
2	scarcity	scarcity	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	dead	dead	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	.	.	.	O	4	punct
