1	We	we	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	tried	try	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	run	run	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	similar	similar	JJ	O	7	amod
7	piece	piece	NN	O	4	dobj
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	which	which	WDT	O	15	dobj
10	apparently	apparently	RB	O	15	advmod
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	Post	post	NN	ORGANIZATION	15	nsubj
13	did	do	VBD	O	15	aux
14	n't	not	RB	O	15	neg
15	like	like	VB	O	7	acl:relcl
16	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	worries	worry	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	upsets	upset	NNS	O	5	dep
5	me	I	PRP	O	2	conj
6	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	bill	bill	NN	O	11	nsubjpass
9	has	have	VBZ	O	11	aux
10	been	be	VBN	O	11	auxpass
11	passed	pass	VBN	O	2	dep
12	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	know	know	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	you	you	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	realize	realize	VB	O	2	ccomp
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	importance	importance	NN	O	4	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	this	this	DT	O	9	det
9	appointment	appointment	NN	O	6	nmod
10	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Dear	Dear	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Jeb	Jeb	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	wrote	write	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	case
7	you	you	PRP	O	5	nmod
8	previously	previously	RB	DATE	5	advmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	recommend	recommend	VB	O	5	xcomp
11	Tim	Tim	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
12	Harley	Harley	NNP	PERSON	10	dobj
13	for	for	IN	O	15	case
14	a	a	DT	O	15	det
15	seat	seat	NN	O	12	nmod
16	on	on	IN	O	20	case
17	the	the	DT	O	20	det
18	local	local	JJ	O	20	amod
19	circuit	circuit	NN	O	20	compound
20	court	court	NN	O	15	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	3	det
2	new	new	JJ	O	3	amod
3	documentary	documentary	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	--	--	:	O	3	punct
5	Waco	Waco	NNP	O	3	dep
6	:	:	:	O	3	punct
7	The	the	DT	O	8	det
8	Rules	rule	NNS	MISC	3	dep
9	of	of	IN	MISC	12	case
10	Engagement	engagement	NN	MISC	12	compound
11	infrared	infrared	JJ	O	12	amod
12	photography	photography	NN	O	8	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	3	punct
14	FBI	FBI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
15	snipers	sniper	NNS	O	16	nsubj
16	killing	kill	VBG	O	3	dep
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	Davidians	Davidians	NNPS	MISC	16	dobj
19	by	by	IN	O	20	mark
20	shooting	shoot	VBG	O	16	advcl
21	through	through	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	back	back	NN	O	20	nmod
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	church	church	NN	O	23	nmod
27	,	,	,	O	26	punct
28	where	where	WRB	O	33	advmod
29	no	no	DT	O	31	neg
30	media	media	NNS	O	31	compound
31	cameras	camera	NNS	O	33	nsubjpass
32	were	be	VBD	O	33	auxpass
33	allowed	allow	VBN	O	26	acl:relcl
34	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	4	cop
3	very	very	RB	O	4	advmod
4	gracious	gracious	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	your	you	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	office	office	NN	O	4	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Nothing	nothing	NN	O	7	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	7	aux
3	be	be	VB	O	7	cop
4	further	further	RB	O	7	advmod
5	from	from	IN	O	7	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	truth	truth	NN	O	0	ROOT
8	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Hope	Hope	NNP	O	4	nsubj
2	this	this	DT	O	1	dep
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	helpful	helpful	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	2	cc
2	thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
3	you	you	PRP	O	2	dobj
4	for	for	IN	O	6	case
5	your	you	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	assistance	assistance	NN	O	2	nmod
7	in	in	IN	O	8	mark
8	appointing	appoint	VBG	O	6	acl
9	my	my	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	wife	wife	NN	O	8	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	Dr.	Dr.	NNP	O	14	compound
13	Judy	Judy	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Clay	Clay	NNP	PERSON	10	appos
15	,	,	,	O	10	punct
16	to	to	TO	O	18	case
17	your	you	PRP$	O	18	nmod:poss
18	Partnership	Partnership	NNP	O	8	nmod
19	for	for	IN	O	22	case
20	School	School	NNP	O	22	compound
21	Readiness	Readiness	NNP	O	22	compound
22	program	program	NN	O	18	nmod
23	that	that	WDT	O	24	nsubj
24	led	lead	VBD	O	18	acl:relcl
25	to	to	TO	O	26	case
26	her	she	PRP$	O	24	nmod
27	receiving	receive	VBG	O	24	xcomp
28	the	the	DT	O	27	dobj
29	''	''	''	O	27	punct
30	Optometrist	optometrist	NN	O	27	dobj
31	of	of	IN	O	35	case
32	the	the	DT	DATE	35	det
33	Year	year	NN	DATE	35	compound
34	''	''	''	O	35	punct
35	award	award	NN	O	30	nmod
36	at	at	IN	O	42	case
37	a	a	DT	O	42	det
38	recent	recent	JJ	O	42	amod
39	Florida	Florida	NNP	ORGANIZATION	42	compound
40	Optometric	Optometric	NNP	ORGANIZATION	42	compound
41	Association	Association	NNP	ORGANIZATION	42	compound
42	Convention	Convention	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nmod
43	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	late	late	JJ	DATE	3	amod
3	1997	1997	CD	DATE	7	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	7	punct
5	I	I	PRP	O	7	nsubjpass
6	was	be	VBD	O	7	auxpass
7	diagnosed	diagnose	VBN	O	0	ROOT
8	with	with	IN	O	10	case
9	colon	colon	NN	O	10	compound
10	cancer	cancer	NN	O	7	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	7	punct
12	had	have	VBD	O	7	conj
13	surgery	surgery	NN	O	12	dobj
14	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
15	shortly	shortly	RB	O	17	advmod
16	thereafter	thereafter	RB	O	17	advmod
17	began	begin	VBD	O	7	conj
18	chemotherapy	chemotherapy	NN	O	19	compound
19	treatments	treatment	NNS	O	17	dobj
20	to	to	TO	O	21	case
21	which	which	WDT	O	23	nmod
22	I	I	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	had	have	VBD	O	19	acl:relcl
24	an	a	DT	O	27	det
25	extremely	extremely	RB	O	26	advmod
26	violent	violent	JJ	O	27	amod
27	reaction	reaction	NN	O	23	dobj
28	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	5	compound
2	Kim	Kim	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
3	A.	A.	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
4	Marston	Marston	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Jr.	Jr.	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT
6	256	256	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
7	Platon	Platon	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Ave	Ave	NNP	PERSON	5	dep
9	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	These	these	DT	O	2	det
2	states	state	NNS	O	18	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	18	cop
4	:	:	:	O	18	punct
5	California	California	NNP	LOCATION	18	compound
6	,	,	,	O	18	punct
7	Colorado	Colorado	NNP	LOCATION	18	appos
8	,	,	,	O	18	punct
9	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	18	appos
10	,	,	,	O	18	punct
11	Kentucky	Kentucky	NNP	LOCATION	18	appos
12	,	,	,	O	18	punct
13	Massachusetts	Massachusetts	NNP	LOCATION	18	appos
14	,	,	,	O	18	punct
15	Michigan	Michigan	NNP	LOCATION	18	appos
16	,	,	,	O	18	punct
17	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	18	appos
18	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	0	ROOT
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	North	North	NNP	LOCATION	21	compound
21	Carolina	Carolina	NNP	LOCATION	18	conj
22	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
23	Texas	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	18	conj
24	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	wish	wish	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	expand	expand	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Autoimmune	autoimmune	NN	O	7	compound
7	Center	center	NN	O	4	dobj
8	by	by	IN	O	9	mark
9	identifying	identify	VBG	O	4	advcl
10	Centers	Centers	NNPS	O	9	dobj
11	throughout	throughout	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	State	state	NN	O	9	nmod
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	enhance	enhance	VB	O	13	acl
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	database	database	NN	O	15	dobj
18	,	,	,	O	9	punct
19	having	have	VBG	O	9	dep
20	physicians	physician	NNS	O	19	dobj
21	going	go	VBG	O	19	advcl
22	through	through	IN	O	25	case
23	our	we	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
24	training	training	NN	O	25	compound
25	programs	program	NNS	O	21	nmod
26	to	to	TO	O	27	mark
27	alleviate	alleviate	VB	O	21	xcomp
28	the	the	DT	O	31	det
29	50	50	CD	PERCENT	30	compound
30	%	%	NN	PERCENT	31	amod
31	misdiagnosis	misdiagnosis	NN	O	27	dobj
32	,	,	,	O	27	punct
33	develop	develop	VB	O	27	dep
34	a	a	DT	O	36	det
35	statewide	statewide	JJ	O	36	amod
36	network	network	NN	O	33	dobj
37	of	of	IN	O	39	case
38	disease	disease	NN	O	39	compound
39	management	management	NN	O	36	nmod
40	,	,	,	O	27	punct
41	develop	develop	VB	O	27	dep
42	model	model	NN	O	44	compound
43	autoimmune	autoimmune	JJ	O	44	amod
44	practices	practice	NNS	O	41	dobj
45	through	through	IN	O	47	case
46	the	the	DT	O	47	det
47	State	state	NN	O	41	nmod
48	...	...	:	O	2	punct
49	all	all	DT	O	50	nsubj
50	enabling	enable	VBG	O	2	parataxis
51	us	we	PRP	O	50	dobj
52	to	to	TO	O	53	mark
53	disseminate	disseminate	VB	O	50	xcomp
54	our	we	PRP$	O	55	nmod:poss
55	knowledge	knowledge	NN	O	53	dobj
56	gained	gain	VBN	O	55	acl
57	by	by	IN	O	61	case
58	the	the	DT	DURATION	61	det
59	past	past	JJ	DURATION	61	amod
60	three	three	CD	DURATION	61	nummod
61	years	year	NNS	DURATION	56	nmod
62	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	4	case
2	an	a	DT	O	4	det
3	aged	aged	JJ	O	4	amod
4	individual	individual	NN	O	13	nmod
5	with	with	IN	O	7	case
6	incalcitrant	incalcitrant	JJ	O	7	amod
7	knees	knee	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	13	punct
9	I	I	PRP	O	13	nsubjpass
10	was	be	VBD	O	13	auxpass
11	n't	not	RB	O	13	neg
12	particularly	particularly	RB	O	13	advmod
13	overjoyed	overjoy	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	with	with	IN	O	18	case
15	the	the	DT	O	18	det
16	11-story	11-story	JJ	O	18	amod
17	stairwell	stairwell	NN	O	18	compound
18	exit	exit	NN	O	13	nmod
19	undergone	undergo	VBN	O	18	acl
20	by	by	IN	O	22	case
21	some	some	DT	O	22	det
22	emergency	emergency	NN	O	19	nmod
23	which	which	WDT	O	25	nsubj
24	never	never	RB	O	25	neg
25	became	become	VBD	O	22	acl:relcl
26	clear	clear	JJ	O	25	xcomp
27	before	before	IN	O	29	mark
28	we	we	PRP	O	29	nsubj
29	had	have	VBD	O	25	advcl
30	to	to	TO	O	31	mark
31	leave	leave	VB	O	29	xcomp
32	,	,	,	O	13	punct
33	but	but	CC	O	13	cc
34	that	that	DT	O	35	nsubj
35	's	be	VBZ	O	13	conj
36	still	still	RB	O	35	advmod
37	grist	grist	VB	O	35	ccomp
38	for	for	IN	O	40	case
39	embellished	embellished	JJ	O	40	amod
40	tales	tale	NNS	O	37	nmod
41	back	back	RB	O	37	advmod
42	home	home	NN	O	41	dep
43	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Bob	Bob	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	8	punct
3	evidently	evidently	RB	O	8	advmod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	someone	someone	NN	O	8	nsubj
6	in	in	IN	O	7	case
7	Alabama	Alabama	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
8	spread	spread	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	false	false	JJ	O	11	amod
11	rumor	rumor	NN	O	8	dobj
12	that	that	WDT	O	18	dobj
13	Gov.	Gov.	NNP	O	15	compound
14	Jeb	Jeb	NNP	PERSON	15	compound
15	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	18	nsubj
16	is	be	VBZ	O	18	cop
17	against	against	IN	O	18	case
18	passage	passage	NN	O	11	acl:relcl
19	of	of	IN	O	23	case
20	any	any	DT	O	23	det
21	concurrent	concurrent	JJ	O	23	amod
22	receipt	receipt	NN	O	23	compound
23	law	law	NN	O	18	nmod
24	by	by	IN	O	26	case
25	The	the	DT	O	26	det
26	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	mark
2	accepting	accept	VBG	O	14	advcl
3	that	that	IN	O	4	case
4	reasoning	reasoning	NN	O	2	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	14	punct
6	we	we	PRP	O	14	nsubjpass
7	in	in	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	news	news	NN	O	10	compound
10	media	media	NNS	O	14	nmod
11	are	be	VBP	O	14	auxpass
12	also	also	RB	O	14	advmod
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	engaged	engage	VBN	O	0	ROOT
15	in	in	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	protests	protest	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Please	please	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	share	share	VB	O	1	xcomp
3	this	this	DT	O	2	dobj
4	with	with	IN	O	5	case
5	him	he	PRP	O	3	nmod
6	for	for	IN	O	7	case
7	me	I	PRP	O	2	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Please	please	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	do	do	VB	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	veto	veto	VB	O	1	ccomp
5	the	the	DT	O	8	det:predet
6	these	these	DT	O	8	det
7	critical	critical	JJ	O	8	amod
8	funds	fund	NNS	O	4	dobj
9	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubj
10	will	will	MD	O	11	aux
11	help	help	VB	O	8	acl:relcl
12	the	the	DT	O	15	det
13	fastest	fastest	JJS	O	15	amod
14	growing	grow	VBG	O	15	amod
15	counties	county	NNS	O	11	dobj
16	in	in	IN	O	17	case
17	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	15	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	>	>	JJR	O	2	nmod:npmod
2	>	>	JJR	O	3	amod
3	Kathleen	Kathleen	NNP	PERSON	6	dep
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	>	>	JJR	O	3	appos
6	>	>	JJR	O	0	ROOT

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	DATE	3	det
3	summer	summer	NN	DATE	10	nmod
4	of	of	IN	DATE	5	case
5	2001	2001	CD	DATE	3	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	10	punct
7	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Davis	Davis	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
9	had	have	VBD	O	10	aux
10	proposed	propose	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	cutting	cut	VBG	O	10	xcomp
12	$	$	$	MONEY	13	dep
13	98-million	98-million	CD	MONEY	11	dobj
14	from	from	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	community	community	NN	O	11	nmod
17	-	-	:	O	16	punct
18	college	college	NN	O	19	compound
19	system	system	NN	O	21	nmod:poss
20	's	's	POS	O	19	case
21	budget	budget	NN	O	16	dep
22	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	You	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	never	never	RB	O	3	neg
3	gave	give	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	me	I	PRP	O	3	iobj
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	translation	translation	NN	O	3	dobj
7	for	for	IN	O	10	case
8	''	''	''	O	10	punct
9	charter	charter	NN	O	10	compound
10	school	school	NN	O	6	nmod
11	''	''	''	O	10	punct
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	unanimous	unanimous	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
5	no	no	DT	O	6	neg
6	member	member	NN	O	11	nsubj
7	of	of	IN	O	9	case
8	this	this	DT	O	9	det
9	family	family	NN	O	6	nmod
10	will	will	MD	O	11	aux
11	seek	seek	VB	O	3	ccomp
12	assistance	assistance	NN	O	11	dobj
13	or	or	CC	O	11	cc
14	provide	provide	VB	O	11	conj
15	any	any	DT	O	17	det
16	willing	willing	JJ	O	17	amod
17	cooperation	cooperation	NN	O	14	dobj
18	to	to	TO	O	22	case
19	any	any	DT	O	22	det
20	law	law	NN	O	22	compound
21	enforcement	enforcement	NN	O	22	compound
22	agency	agency	NN	O	14	nmod
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	this	this	DT	O	25	det
25	city	city	NN	O	22	nmod
26	in	in	IN	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	DATE	28	det
28	future	future	NN	DATE	25	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	so	so	IN	O	3	dep
2	they	they	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	went	go	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	3	advcl
5	public	public	JJ	O	4	dep
6	school	school	NN	O	5	dep
7	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	5	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
9	we	we	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	do	do	VBP	O	11	aux
11	believe	believe	VB	O	3	conj
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	education	education	NN	O	11	nmod
14	for	for	IN	O	15	case
15	everyone	everyone	NN	O	3	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	am	be	VBP	O	3	cop
3	open	open	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	case
5	any	any	DT	O	3	nmod
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	your	you	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	thoughts	thought	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	--	--	:	O	3	punct
10	I	I	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	would	would	MD	O	12	aux
12	appreciate	appreciate	VB	O	3	parataxis
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	extra	extra	JJ	O	15	amod
15	300	300	CD	NUMBER	12	dobj
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	do	do	VBP	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	feel	feel	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	BS	bs	NN	O	12	dep
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	business	business	NN	O	7	nmod
10	or	or	CC	O	9	cc
11	other	other	JJ	O	9	conj
12	non	non	JJ	O	4	dep
13	-	-	:	O	4	punct
14	related	related	JJ	O	15	amod
15	fields	field	NNS	O	16	nsubj
16	qualifies	qualify	VBZ	O	4	parataxis
17	a	a	DT	O	18	det
18	person	person	NN	O	16	dobj
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	do	do	VB	O	18	acl
21	that	that	DT	O	22	det
22	job	job	NN	O	20	dobj
23	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	just	just	RB	O	3	advmod
3	want	want	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	thank	thank	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	you	you	PRP	O	5	dobj
7	for	for	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	strong	strong	JJ	O	10	amod
10	statement	statement	NN	O	5	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	12	case
12	support	support	NN	O	10	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	15	case
14	your	you	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	budget	budget	NN	O	5	nmod
16	for	for	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	principles	principle	NNS	O	15	nmod
19	which	which	WDT	O	28	dobj
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	Board	Board	NNP	O	28	nsubj
22	of	of	IN	O	23	case
23	Regents	Regents	NNP	O	21	nmod
24	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
25	I	I	PRP	O	23	conj
26	have	have	VBP	O	28	aux
27	been	be	VBN	O	28	aux
28	advocating	advocate	VBG	O	18	acl:relcl
29	over	over	IN	O	32	case
30	the	the	DT	DATE	32	det
31	past	past	JJ	DATE	32	amod
32	year	year	NN	DATE	28	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	did	do	VBD	O	3	aux
3	go	go	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	6	case
5	St.	St.	NNP	LOCATION	6	compound
6	Lucie	Lucie	NNP	LOCATION	3	nmod
7	where	where	WRB	O	9	advmod
8	there	there	EX	O	9	expl
9	is	be	VBZ	O	3	advcl
10	no	no	DT	O	11	neg
11	one	one	NN	NUMBER	9	nsubj
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	shelter	shelter	NN	O	11	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Both	both	DT	O	3	det
2	my	my	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	children	child	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	express	express	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	their	they	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	disillusion	disillusion	NN	O	4	dobj
7	at	at	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	impression	impression	NN	O	4	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	police	police	NN	O	9	nmod
13	before	before	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	incident	incident	NN	O	12	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
17	will	will	MD	O	20	aux
18	no	no	RB	O	19	neg
19	longer	longer	RB	O	20	advmod
20	trust	trust	VB	O	4	conj
21	any	any	DT	O	24	det
22	law	law	NN	O	24	compound
23	enforcement	enforcement	NN	O	24	compound
24	officer	officer	NN	O	20	dobj
25	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Dick	Dick	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	sent	send	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	me	I	PRP	O	2	iobj
4	this	this	DT	O	2	dobj
5	e	e	SYM	O	7	dep
6	-	-	:	O	7	punct
7	mail	mail	NN	O	4	dep
8	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Representatives	representative	NNS	O	8	nsubj
2	from	from	IN	O	4	case
3	federal	federal	JJ	O	4	amod
4	agencies	agency	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	were	be	VBD	O	8	cop
6	also	also	RB	O	8	advmod
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	attendance	attendance	NN	O	0	ROOT
9	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	May	may	MD	O	2	aux
2	have	have	VB	O	8	dep
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	hang	hang	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	it	it	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	up	up	RP	O	4	compound:prt
7	...	...	:	O	8	punct
8	sure	sure	JJ	O	0	ROOT
9	appreciated	appreciate	VBN	O	8	dep
10	your	you	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	diligence	diligence	NN	O	13	nsubj
12	...	...	:	O	13	punct
13	waiting	wait	VBG	O	9	dep
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	see	see	VB	O	13	xcomp
16	what	what	WP	O	17	nsubj
17	happens	happen	VBZ	O	15	ccomp
18	now	now	RB	DATE	17	advmod
19	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	wrote	write	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	an	a	DT	O	4	det
4	article	article	NN	O	2	dobj
5	for	for	IN	O	8	case
6	my	my	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
7	web	web	NN	O	8	compound
8	site	site	NN	O	4	nmod
9	about	about	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	tactics	tactic	NNS	O	2	nmod
12	used	use	VBN	O	11	acl
13	by	by	IN	O	17	case
14	an	a	DT	O	17	det
15	abortion	abortion	NN	O	17	compound
16	clinic	clinic	NN	O	17	compound
17	owner	owner	NN	O	12	nmod
18	that	that	WDT	O	19	nsubj
19	resulted	result	VBD	O	17	acl:relcl
20	in	in	IN	O	22	mark
21	you	you	PRP	O	22	nsubj
22	giving	give	VBG	O	19	advcl
23	her	she	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
24	$	$	$	MONEY	25	dep
25	10,000	10,000	CD	MONEY	22	dobj
26	in	in	IN	O	30	case
27	left	leave	VBN	O	30	amod
28	over	over	RP	O	27	compound:prt
29	campaign	campaign	NN	O	30	compound
30	funds	fund	NNS	O	25	nmod
31	thinking	think	VBG	O	12	xcomp
32	she	she	PRP	O	37	nsubj
33	was	be	VBD	O	37	cop
34	a	a	DT	O	37	det
35	Crisis	Crisis	NNP	O	37	compound
36	Pregnancy	Pregnancy	NNP	O	37	compound
37	Center	Center	NNP	O	31	ccomp
38	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	5	mark
2	you	you	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	could	could	MD	O	5	aux
4	only	only	RB	O	5	advmod
5	feel	feel	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	frustration	frustration	NN	O	5	dobj
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	weariness	weariness	NN	O	7	conj
10	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
11	we	we	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	feel	feel	VBP	O	5	ccomp
13	from	from	IN	O	14	case
14	this	this	DT	O	12	nmod
15	on	on	IN	O	17	dep
16	-	-	:	O	17	punct
17	going	go	VBG	O	5	dep
18	situation	situation	NN	O	17	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	then	then	RB	O	3	advmod
3	went	go	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	see	see	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	my	my	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	attorney	attorney	NN	O	5	dobj
8	William	William	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
9	D.	D.	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
10	Mercer	Mercer	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Jr.	Jr.	NNP	PERSON	7	dep
12	,	,	,	O	7	punct
13	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	14	punct
14	352.392.1665	352.392.1665	CD	NUMBER	7	appos
15	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	14	punct
16	who	who	WP	O	17	nsubj
17	negotiated	negotiate	VBD	O	7	acl:relcl
18	me	I	PRP	O	17	dobj
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	pay	pay	VB	O	17	xcomp
21	them	they	PRP	O	20	dobj
22	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	24	punct
23	which	which	WDT	O	24	nsubj
24	tripled	triple	VBD	O	7	dep
25	my	my	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
26	original	original	JJ	O	27	amod
27	fee	fee	NN	O	24	dobj
28	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	24	punct
29	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
30	have	have	VBP	O	3	conj
31	the	the	DT	O	32	det
32	case	case	NN	O	30	dobj
33	dropped	drop	VBD	O	32	acl:relcl
34	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	35	punct
35	C03-13549	c03-13549	NN	O	33	dep
36	,	,	,	O	35	punct
37	OFFICER	officer	NN	O	35	appos
38	:	:	:	O	35	punct
39	Glen	Glen	NNP	PERSON	40	compound
40	Baker	Baker	NNP	PERSON	35	dep
41	<	<	JJR	O	40	dep
42	352.334.2400	352.334.2400	CD	NUMBER	43	nummod
43	>	>	JJR	O	35	dep
44	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	35	punct
45	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	mark
2	we	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	contemplate	contemplate	VBP	O	21	advcl
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	unspeakable	unspeakable	JJ	O	6	amod
6	events	event	NNS	O	3	dobj
7	that	that	WDT	O	10	nsubj
8	have	have	VBP	O	10	aux
9	allegedly	allegedly	RB	O	10	advmod
10	taken	take	VBN	O	6	acl:relcl
11	place	place	NN	O	10	dobj
12	in	in	IN	O	17	case
13	a	a	DT	O	17	det
14	state	state	NN	O	17	compound
15	-	-	:	O	14	punct
16	operated	operate	VBN	O	14	amod
17	facility	facility	NN	O	10	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	21	punct
19	we	we	PRP	O	21	nsubj
20	should	should	MD	O	21	aux
21	bear	bear	VB	O	0	ROOT
22	in	in	IN	O	23	case
23	mind	mind	NN	O	21	nmod
24	what	what	WDT	O	26	dobj
25	imprisonment	imprisonment	NN	O	26	nsubj
26	is	be	VBZ	O	23	acl:relcl
27	all	all	DT	O	28	dep
28	about	about	RB	O	26	advmod
29	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	Please	please	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	let	let	VB	O	1	xcomp
3	me	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	know	know	VB	O	2	ccomp
5	if	if	IN	O	12	mark
6	we	we	PRP	O	12	nsubj
7	can	can	MD	O	12	aux
8	be	be	VB	O	12	cop
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	any	any	DT	O	12	det
11	more	more	JJR	O	12	amod
12	assistance	assistance	NN	O	4	advcl
13	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Hope	Hope	NNP	O	9	nsubj
2	you	you	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	would	would	MD	O	4	aux
4	let	let	VB	O	1	acl:relcl
5	me	I	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	know	know	VB	O	4	ccomp
7	ASAP	asap	RB	O	6	advmod
8	.	.	.	O	4	punct
9	Thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	you	you	PRP	O	9	dobj
11	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Commissioner	Commissioner	NNP	O	7	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	5	case
3	Education	Education	NNP	O	5	compound
4	Jim	Jim	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Horne	Horne	NNP	PERSON	1	nmod
6	has	have	VBZ	O	7	aux
7	asked	ask	VBN	O	0	ROOT
8	our	we	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	office	office	NN	O	7	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	respond	respond	VB	O	9	acl
12	to	to	TO	O	16	case
13	the	the	DT	O	16	det
14	recent	recent	JJ	O	16	amod
15	electronic	electronic	JJ	O	16	amod
16	mail	mail	NN	O	11	nmod
17	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
18	you	you	PRP	O	19	nsubj
19	sent	send	VBD	O	11	ccomp
20	to	to	TO	O	22	case
21	his	he	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
22	office	office	NN	O	19	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	7	nsubj
2	certainly	certainly	RB	O	7	advmod
3	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
4	n't	not	RB	O	7	neg
5	''	''	''	O	7	punct
6	just	just	RB	O	7	advmod
7	politics	politics	NNS	O	0	ROOT
8	''	''	''	O	7	punct
9	for	for	IN	O	11	case
10	my	my	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	mother	mother	NN	O	7	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	my	my	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
14	family	family	NN	O	11	conj
15	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	10	advmod
2	if	if	IN	O	10	mark
3	I	I	PRP	O	10	nsubj
4	who	who	WP	O	8	nsubj
5	am	be	VBP	O	8	cop
6	an	a	DT	O	8	det
7	average	average	JJ	O	8	amod
8	person	person	NN	O	3	acl:relcl
9	can	can	MD	O	10	aux
10	do	do	VB	O	14	advcl
11	it	it	PRP	O	10	dobj
12	it	it	PRP	O	14	nsubj
13	will	will	MD	O	14	aux
14	give	give	VB	O	0	ROOT
15	many	many	JJ	O	16	amod
16	people	people	NNS	O	14	iobj
17	incentive	incentive	NN	O	14	dobj
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	hope	hope	NN	O	17	conj
20	that	that	IN	O	24	mark
21	they	they	PRP	O	24	nsubj
22	also	also	RB	O	24	advmod
23	can	can	MD	O	24	aux
24	do	do	VB	O	14	ccomp
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	same	same	JJ	O	24	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	What	what	WP	O	5	dobj
2	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	do	do	VBP	O	5	aux
4	n't	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	understand	understand	VB	O	6	csubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	why	why	WRB	O	12	advmod
8	you	you	PRP	O	12	nsubj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	your	you	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	brother	brother	NN	O	8	conj
12	keep	keep	VB	O	6	advcl
13	trying	try	VBG	O	12	xcomp
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	do	do	VB	O	13	xcomp
16	things	thing	NNS	O	15	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	help	help	VB	O	15	xcomp
19	our	we	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	society	society	NN	O	18	dobj
21	-	-	:	O	6	punct
22	if	if	IN	O	26	mark
23	you	you	PRP	O	26	nsubj
24	would	would	MD	O	26	aux
25	simply	simply	RB	O	26	advmod
26	do	do	VB	O	42	advcl
27	nothing	nothing	NN	O	26	dobj
28	,	,	,	O	26	punct
29	as	as	IN	O	34	mark
30	the	the	DT	O	32	det
31	liberal	liberal	JJ	O	32	amod
32	democrats	democrat	NNS	O	34	nsubjpass
33	are	be	VBP	O	34	auxpass
34	known	know	VBN	O	26	advcl
35	for	for	IN	O	34	nmod
36	,	,	,	O	42	punct
37	then	then	RB	O	38	advmod
38	it	it	PRP	O	42	nsubj
39	will	will	MD	O	42	aux
40	be	be	VB	O	42	cop
41	less	less	RBR	O	42	advmod
42	easy	easy	JJ	O	6	parataxis
43	for	for	IN	O	44	case
44	some	some	DT	O	42	nmod
45	to	to	TO	O	46	mark
46	criticize	criticize	VB	O	42	xcomp
47	-	-	:	O	46	punct
48	your	you	PRP$	O	49	nmod:poss
49	efforts	effort	NNS	O	46	dobj
50	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	3	det
2	Advent	Advent	NNP	O	3	compound
3	Season	season	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	our	we	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	sponsors	sponsor	NNS	O	3	dep
6	are	be	VBP	O	7	aux
7	selling	sell	VBG	O	0	ROOT
8	goods	goods	NNS	O	7	dobj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	services	service	NNS	O	8	conj
11	you	you	PRP	O	14	nsubj
12	do	do	VBP	O	14	aux
13	n't	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	want	want	VB	O	8	acl:relcl
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	miss	miss	VB	O	14	xcomp
17	!	!	.	O	7	punct

1	a	a	DT	O	3	det
2	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	3	punct
3	Direct	direct	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	above	above	IN	O	6	case
5	ground	ground	NN	O	6	compound
6	corridor	corridor	NN	O	3	nmod
7	leading	lead	VBG	O	3	acl
8	from	from	IN	O	21	mark
9	the	the	DT	O	17	det
10	Port	Port	NNP	O	17	dep
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	Miami	Miami	NNP	LOCATION	13	compound
13	Bridge	Bridge	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
14	above	above	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	FEC	FEC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	nmod
17	railway	railway	NN	O	21	nsubj
18	right	right	RB	O	19	advmod
19	away	away	RB	O	20	advmod
20	West	west	JJ	O	17	amod
21	connecting	connect	VBG	O	7	advcl
22	with	with	IN	O	23	case
23	I-95	i-95	NN	O	21	nmod
24	/	/	:	O	25	punct
25	SR836	sr836	NN	O	23	dep
26	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Your	you	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
2	local	local	JJ	O	4	amod
3	school	school	NN	O	4	compound
4	system	system	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
6	responsible	responsible	JJ	O	0	ROOT
7	for	for	IN	O	11	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	students	student	NNS	O	11	nmod:poss
10	'	'	POS	O	9	case
11	education	education	NN	O	6	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	all	all	DT	O	14	det
14	activites	activite	NNS	O	11	conj
15	related	relate	VBN	O	14	acl
16	to	to	TO	O	17	case
17	that	that	DT	O	15	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Family	Family	NNP	O	2	compound
2	problems	problem	NNS	O	6	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	6	cop
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	worst	worst	JJS	O	6	amod
6	problems	problem	NNS	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	have	have	VB	O	6	acl
9	...	...	:	O	6	punct
10	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Governor	governor	NN	O	5	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	5	punct
3	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	've	have	VBP	O	5	aux
5	spoken	speak	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	with	with	IN	O	7	case
7	Renee	Renee	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod
8	twice	twice	RB	O	10	advmod
9	this	this	DT	DATE	10	det
10	week	week	NN	DATE	7	nmod:tmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	let	let	VB	O	7	acl
13	her	she	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	know	know	VB	O	12	ccomp
15	what	what	WP	O	17	nsubj
16	's	be	VBZ	O	17	aux
17	going	go	VBG	O	14	ccomp
18	on	on	IN	O	19	case
19	etc	etc	NN	O	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	>>	>>	NN	O	3	compound
2	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Panzer	Panzer	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	founder	founder	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	President	president	NN	O	6	conj
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	Hospice	Hospice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
11	Patients	Patients	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	Alliance	Alliance	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	nmod
13	:	:	:	O	6	punct
14	a	a	DT	O	21	det
15	nurse	nurse	NN	O	17	compound
16	,	,	,	O	17	punct
17	whistleblower	whistleblower	NN	O	21	compound
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	ardent	ardent	JJ	O	17	conj
20	patient	patient	NN	O	21	compound
21	advocate	advocate	NN	O	24	nsubj
22	,	,	,	O	21	punct
23	Ron	Ron	NNP	PERSON	21	appos
24	authored	author	VBD	O	6	parataxis
25	the	the	DT	O	30	det
26	Hospice	Hospice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	compound
27	Patients	Patients	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	30	compound
28	Alliance	Alliance	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	compound
29	Family	Family	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	compound
30	Guide	Guide	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	dobj
31	to	to	TO	ORGANIZATION	33	case
32	Hospice	Hospice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	33	compound
33	Care	Care	NNP	ORGANIZATION	30	nmod
34	and	and	CC	O	30	cc
35	most	most	JJS	O	30	conj
36	of	of	IN	O	38	case
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	articles	article	NNS	O	35	nmod
39	on	on	IN	O	41	case
40	the	the	DT	O	41	det
41	website	website	NN	O	24	nmod
42	at	at	IN	O	43	case
43	<	<	JJR	O	24	nmod
44	http://www.hospicepatients.org/	http://www.hospicepatients.org/	CD	NUMBER	46	nummod
45	>	>	JJR	O	46	amod
46	www.hospicepatients.org	www.hospicepatients.org	NN	O	43	dep

1	Starvation	starvation	NN	O	3	dep
2	,	,	,	O	3	punct
3	denied	deny	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	medical	medical	JJ	O	5	amod
5	attention	attention	NN	O	3	nsubj
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	physical	physical	JJ	O	10	amod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	mental	mental	JJ	O	7	conj
10	abuse	abuse	NN	O	5	appos
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	human	human	JJ	O	13	amod
13	rights	rights	NNS	O	10	appos
14	as	as	RB	O	10	cc
15	well	well	RB	O	14	mwe
16	as	as	IN	O	14	mwe
17	civil	civil	JJ	O	18	amod
18	rights	rights	NNS	O	10	conj
19	violations	violation	NNS	O	23	nsubj
20	were	be	VBD	O	23	cop
21	just	just	RB	O	23	advmod
22	a	a	DT	O	23	advmod
23	few	few	JJ	O	18	acl:relcl
24	of	of	IN	O	26	case
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	contributors	contributor	NNS	O	23	nmod
27	to	to	TO	O	30	case
28	my	my	PRP$	O	30	nmod:poss
29	medical	medical	JJ	O	30	amod
30	demise	demise	NN	O	23	nmod
31	and	and	CC	O	23	cc
32	should	should	MD	O	36	dep
33	all	all	DT	O	36	nsubjpass
34	have	have	VBP	O	36	aux
35	been	be	VBN	O	36	auxpass
36	documented	document	VBN	O	23	conj
37	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	2	2	LS	NUMBER	16	dep
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct
3	In	in	IN	O	7	case
4	Bill	Bill	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Vogel	Vogel	NNP	PERSON	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	opinion	opinion	NN	O	16	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	16	punct
9	the	the	DT	O	14	det
10	St.	St.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
11	Lucie	Lucie	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
12	County	County	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
13	School	School	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
14	District	District	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	nsubj
15	was	be	VBD	O	16	aux
16	going	go	VBG	O	0	ROOT
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	lose	lose	VB	O	16	xcomp
19	several	several	JJ	O	20	amod
20	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	18	dobj
21	to	to	TO	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	same	same	JJ	O	24	amod
24	problem	problem	NN	O	18	nmod
25	my	my	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
26	wife	wife	NN	O	28	nsubj
27	was	be	VBD	O	28	aux
28	encountering	encounter	VBG	O	24	acl:relcl
29	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	3	mark
2	there	there	EX	O	3	expl
3	is	be	VBZ	O	24	advcl
4	any	any	DT	O	5	det
5	way	way	NN	O	3	nsubj
6	I	I	PRP	O	10	nsubj
7	can	can	MD	O	10	aux
8	be	be	VB	O	10	cop
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	assistance	assistance	NN	O	5	acl:relcl
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	or	or	CC	O	10	cc
13	you	you	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	need	need	VBP	O	10	conj
15	me	I	PRP	O	14	dobj
16	for	for	IN	O	18	case
17	any	any	DT	O	18	det
18	volunteer	volunteer	NN	O	14	nmod
19	or	or	CC	O	18	cc
20	special	special	JJ	O	21	amod
21	projects	project	NNS	O	18	conj
22	,	,	,	O	24	punct
23	I	I	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	'm	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
25	always	always	RB	O	24	advmod
26	available	available	JJ	O	24	xcomp
27	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
2	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
3	be	be	VB	O	5	cop
4	very	very	RB	O	5	advmod
5	glad	glad	JJ	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	support	support	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	you	you	PRP	O	7	dobj
9	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Good	good	JJ	O	2	amod
2	luck	luck	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	with	with	IN	O	5	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	legislature	legislature	NN	O	2	nmod
6	this	this	DT	O	7	det
7	session	session	NN	O	5	dep
8	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	the	the	DT	O	2	det
2	caseloads	caseload	NNS	O	4	nsubj
3	have	have	VBP	O	4	aux
4	dropped	drop	VBN	O	8	ccomp
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	guardians	guardian	NNS	O	8	nsubj
8	have	have	VBP	O	0	ROOT
9	some	some	DT	O	10	det
10	things	thing	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	explain	explain	VB	O	8	ccomp
13	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	incident	incident	NN	O	9	nsubj
3	you	you	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	recounted	recount	VBD	O	9	parataxis
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	perfect	perfect	JJ	O	9	amod
9	example	example	NN	O	0	ROOT
10	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Thanks	thanks	NNS	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	4	mark
2	you	you	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	aux
4	considering	consider	VBG	O	11	advcl
5	widespread	widespread	JJ	O	6	amod
6	change	change	NN	O	4	dobj
7	,	,	,	O	11	punct
8	this	this	DT	O	11	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	time	time	NN	O	0	ROOT
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	sooner	sooner	RBR	O	11	advmod
14	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
15	always	always	RB	O	16	advmod
16	better	better	JJR	O	11	dep
17	than	than	IN	O	18	case
18	later	later	RB	O	16	advcl
19	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	2	neg
2	only	only	RB	O	3	dep
3	is	be	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	6	mark
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	problem	problem	NN	O	3	dep
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	way	way	NN	O	14	dep
11	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	school	school	NN	O	14	nsubj
14	makes	make	VBZ	O	6	dep
15	academics	academic	NNS	O	14	iobj
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	backseat	backseat	NN	O	14	dobj
18	to	to	TO	O	19	case
19	sports	sport	NNS	O	17	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	especially	especially	RB	O	19	advmod
22	football	football	NN	O	19	dep
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	nsubj
2	Email	email	VB	O	0	ROOT
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
4	an	a	DT	O	5	det
5	invitation	invitation	NN	O	2	ccomp
6	to	to	TO	O	9	case
7	our	we	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
8	annual	annual	JJ	SET	9	amod
9	meeting	meeting	NN	O	5	nmod
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	Kissimmee	Kissimmee	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	5	punct
13	sponsored	sponsor	VBN	O	5	acl
14	by	by	IN	O	19	case
15	the	the	DT	O	19	det
16	Family	Family	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
17	Care	Care	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
18	Council	Council	NNP	ORGANIZATION	19	compound
19	District	District	NNP	ORGANIZATION	13	nmod
20	seven	seven	CD	NUMBER	19	nummod
21	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Shelly	Shelly	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Brantley	Brantley	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	Susan	Susan	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	Kemper	Kemper	NNP	PERSON	3	dobj
6	from	from	IN	O	3	nmod

1	Our	we	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
2	law	law	NN	O	4	compound
3	enforcement	enforcement	NN	O	4	compound
4	agents	agent	NNS	O	6	nsubj
5	annually	annually	RB	SET	6	advmod
6	join	join	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	forces	force	NNS	O	6	dobj
8	with	with	IN	O	11	case
9	local	local	JJ	O	11	amod
10	law	law	NN	O	11	compound
11	enforcement	enforcement	NN	O	7	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	16	case
13	Daytona	Daytona	NNP	LOCATION	16	compound
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	Panama	Panama	NNP	LOCATION	13	conj
16	City	City	NNP	LOCATION	11	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	combat	combat	VB	O	6	advcl
19	underage	underage	JJ	O	20	amod
20	drinking	drinking	NN	O	18	dobj
21	and	and	CC	O	20	cc
22	false	false	JJ	O	24	amod
23	identification	identification	NN	O	24	compound
24	activity	activity	NN	O	20	conj
25	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Good	good	JJ	O	2	amod
2	afternoon	afternoon	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	!	!	.	O	2	punct

1	May	May	NNP	DATE	2	compound
2	God	God	NNP	O	3	nsubj
3	Bless	bless	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	your	you	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	family	family	NN	O	3	dobj
6	,	,	,	O	3	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
8	guide	guide	NN	O	11	dep
9	our	we	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
10	great	great	JJ	O	11	amod
11	President	President	NNP	O	3	conj
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	just	just	RB	O	3	advmod
3	want	want	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	say	say	VB	O	3	xcomp

1	As	as	IN	O	3	case
2	for	for	IN	O	3	case
3	me	I	PRP	O	8	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
6	am	be	VBP	O	8	cop
7	quite	quite	RB	O	8	advmod
8	proud	proud	JJ	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
10	be	be	VB	O	11	auxpass
11	numbered	number	VBN	O	8	xcomp
12	among	among	IN	O	13	case
13	those	those	DT	O	11	nmod
14	supposedly	supposedly	RB	O	11	advmod
15	''	''	''	O	11	punct
16	ignorant	ignorant	JJ	O	11	xcomp
17	...	...	:	O	16	punct
18	shallow	shallow	JJ	O	20	amod
19	political	political	JJ	O	20	amod
20	opportunists	opportunist	NNS	O	16	dep
21	or	or	CC	O	20	cc
22	marionettes	marionette	NNS	O	20	conj
23	beholden	beholden	JJ	O	20	amod
24	to	to	TO	O	27	case
25	unseen	unseen	JJ	O	26	amod
26	dastardly	dastardly	JJ	O	27	amod
27	interests	interest	NNS	O	23	nmod
28	''	''	''	O	27	punct
29	who	who	WP	O	30	nsubj
30	helped	help	VBD	O	27	acl:relcl
31	form	form	VB	O	30	xcomp
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	consensus	consensus	NN	O	31	dobj
34	,	,	,	O	31	punct
35	bi	bi	SYM	O	38	dep
36	-	-	:	O	38	punct
37	partisan	partisan	JJ	O	38	amod
38	plan	plan	NN	O	31	dep
39	for	for	IN	O	41	case
40	Everglades	everglade	NNS	LOCATION	41	compound
41	restoration	restoration	NN	O	11	nmod
42	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	you	you	PRP	O	1	dobj
3	for	for	IN	O	5	case
4	your	you	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	attention	attention	NN	O	1	nmod
6	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	4	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	State	State	NNP	O	4	nsubj
4	saves	save	VBZ	O	13	advcl
5	Cypress	Cypress	NNP	LOCATION	6	compound
6	Gardens	Gardens	NNP	LOCATION	4	dobj
7	,	,	,	O	13	punct
8	you	you	PRP	O	13	nsubj
9	will	will	MD	O	13	aux
10	not	not	RB	O	13	neg
11	only	only	RB	O	13	advmod
12	be	be	VB	O	13	aux
13	saving	save	VBG	O	0	ROOT
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	Gardens	Gardens	NNPS	LOCATION	13	dobj
16	,	,	,	O	13	punct
17	but	but	CC	O	13	cc
18	you	you	PRP	O	21	nsubj
19	will	will	MD	O	21	aux
20	also	also	RB	O	21	advmod
21	be	be	VB	O	13	conj
22	giving	give	VBG	O	21	xcomp
23	thousands	thousand	NNS	O	22	iobj
24	of	of	IN	O	25	case
25	people	people	NNS	O	23	nmod
26	in	in	IN	O	28	case
27	that	that	DT	O	28	det
28	county	county	NN	O	25	nmod
29	renewed	renew	VBN	O	30	amod
30	hope	hope	NN	O	22	dobj
31	in	in	IN	O	33	case
32	man	man	NN	O	33	compound
33	kind	kind	NN	O	30	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Send	send	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	them	they	PRP	O	1	dobj
3	home	home	NN	O	1	advmod
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	HBIF	hbif	NN	ORGANIZATION	11	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	which	which	WDT	O	6	nsubj
4	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	non	non	JJ	O	1	acl:relcl
7	-	-	:	O	6	punct
8	profit	profit	NN	O	9	compound
9	organization	organization	NN	O	6	dep
10	,	,	,	O	1	punct
11	provides	provide	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
12	bilingual	bilingual	JJ	O	13	amod
13	services	service	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	help	help	VB	O	11	xcomp
16	people	people	NNS	O	17	nsubj
17	start	start	VB	O	15	ccomp
18	their	they	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
19	own	own	JJ	O	20	amod
20	businesses	business	NNS	O	17	dobj
21	,	,	,	O	15	punct
22	help	help	NN	O	15	conj
23	struggling	struggle	VBG	O	22	xcomp
24	business	business	NN	O	25	compound
25	owners	owner	NNS	O	23	dobj
26	who	who	WP	O	29	nsubj
27	are	be	VBP	O	29	cop
28	at	at	IN	O	29	case
29	risk	risk	NN	O	23	dep
30	of	of	IN	O	31	mark
31	closing	close	VBG	O	29	acl
32	their	they	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
33	doors	door	NNS	O	31	dobj
34	,	,	,	O	23	punct
35	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
36	help	help	VB	O	15	conj
37	successful	successful	JJ	O	39	amod
38	business	business	NN	O	39	compound
39	owners	owner	NNS	O	40	nsubj
40	expand	expand	VBP	O	36	ccomp
41	their	they	PRP$	O	42	nmod:poss
42	businesses	business	NNS	O	40	dobj
43	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	First	first	RB	ORDINAL	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	hope	hope	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	things	thing	NNS	O	7	nsubj
6	are	be	VBP	O	7	aux
7	going	go	VBG	O	4	ccomp
8	well	well	RB	O	7	advmod
9	in	in	IN	O	12	case
10	your	you	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
11	new	new	JJ	O	12	amod
12	position	position	NN	O	7	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Affordable	affordable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	4	mark
2	you	you	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	aux
4	running	run	VBG	O	12	advcl
5	Windows	Windows	NNP	MISC	6	nsubj
6	Me	I	PRP	MISC	4	xcomp
7	or	or	CC	MISC	6	cc
8	Windows	Windows	NNP	MISC	9	compound
9	XP	xp	NN	MISC	6	conj
10	,	,	,	O	12	punct
11	we	we	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	recommend	recommend	VBP	O	0	ROOT
13	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
14	you	you	PRP	O	16	nsubj
15	temporarily	temporarily	RB	O	16	advmod
16	turn	turn	VB	O	12	ccomp
17	off	off	RP	O	16	compound:prt
18	System	System	NNP	O	19	compound
19	Restore	Restore	NNP	O	16	dobj
20	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	have	have	VBP	O	3	aux
3	publicized	publicize	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	this	this	DT	O	3	dobj
5	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	$	$	$	MONEY	14	nsubjpass
3	30	30	CD	MONEY	4	compound
4	million	million	CD	MONEY	2	nummod
5	lost	lose	VBN	O	2	acl
6	in	in	IN	O	11	case
7	Governor	Governor	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	budget	budget	NN	O	11	compound
11	request	request	NN	O	5	nmod
12	02-03	02-03	CD	NUMBER	5	nmod:tmod
13	was	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
14	slated	slate	VBN	O	0	ROOT
15	for	for	IN	O	16	case
16	consumers	consumer	NNS	O	14	nmod
17	on	on	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	wait	wait	NN	O	20	compound
20	list	list	NN	O	16	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	====================================================	====================================================	NN	O	8	nmod
2	''	''	''	O	1	punct
3	Among	among	IN	O	1	case
4	my	my	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	people	people	NNS	O	8	nsubj
6	are	be	VBP	O	8	cop
7	wicked	wicked	JJ	O	8	amod
8	men	man	NNS	O	0	ROOT
9	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
10	lie	lie	VBP	O	8	acl:relcl
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	wait	wait	NN	O	10	nmod
13	like	like	IN	O	14	case
14	men	man	NNS	O	12	nmod
15	who	who	WP	O	16	nsubj
16	snare	snare	VBP	O	14	acl:relcl
17	birds	bird	NNS	O	16	dobj
18	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
19	like	like	IN	O	20	case
20	those	those	DT	O	12	conj
21	who	who	WP	O	22	nsubj
22	set	set	VBP	O	20	acl:relcl
23	traps	trap	NNS	O	22	dobj
24	to	to	TO	O	25	mark
25	catch	catch	VB	O	22	xcomp
26	men	man	NNS	O	25	dobj
27	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Somehow	somehow	RB	O	3	advmod
2	he	he	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	gets	get	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	thoughtful	thoughtful	JJ	O	3	xcomp
5	,	,	,	O	3	punct
6	sitting	sit	VBG	O	3	xcomp
7	by	by	IN	O	8	case
8	himself	himself	PRP	O	6	nmod
9	so	so	RB	O	10	advmod
10	much	much	RB	O	6	advmod
11	,	,	,	O	3	punct
12	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
13	thinks	think	VBZ	O	3	conj
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	strangest	strangest	JJS	O	16	amod
16	things	thing	NNS	O	13	dobj
17	you	you	PRP	O	19	nsubj
18	ever	ever	RB	O	19	advmod
19	heard	hear	VBD	O	16	acl:relcl
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Should	should	MD	O	3	aux
2	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	share	share	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	or	or	CC	O	3	cc
6	censor	censor	VB	O	3	conj
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	share	share	VB	O	6	conj
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	or	or	CC	O	6	cc
11	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	share	share	VB	O	6	conj
13	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	More	more	RBR	O	2	advmod
2	importantly	importantly	RB	O	7	advmod
3	,	,	,	O	7	punct
4	I	I	PRP	O	7	nsubj
5	will	will	MD	O	7	aux
6	be	be	VB	O	7	cop
7	able	able	JJ	O	0	ROOT
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	help	help	VB	O	7	xcomp
10	set	set	VB	O	9	xcomp
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	policies	policy	NNS	O	10	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	ensure	ensure	VB	O	10	xcomp
15	that	that	IN	O	17	mark
16	BCC	bcc	NN	ORGANIZATION	17	nsubj
17	produces	produce	VBZ	O	14	ccomp
18	quality	quality	NN	O	19	compound
19	graduates	graduate	NNS	O	17	dobj
20	for	for	IN	O	22	case
21	our	we	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
22	workforce	workforce	NN	O	19	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	would	would	MD	O	3	aux
3	like	like	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	know	know	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	our	we	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	plan	plan	NN	O	5	dobj
8	of	of	IN	O	9	case
9	action	action	NN	O	7	nmod
10	before	before	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	DATE	12	det
12	end	end	NN	DATE	5	nmod
13	of	of	IN	DATE	15	case
14	the	the	DT	DATE	15	det
15	year	year	NN	DATE	12	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	'll	will	MD	O	3	aux
3	have	have	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	more	more	RBR	O	3	dobj
5	tomorrow	tomorrow	NN	DATE	3	nmod:tmod
6	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	need	need	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	to	to	TO	O	4	mark
4	ensure	ensure	VB	O	2	xcomp
5	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
6	we	we	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	prepare	prepare	VBP	O	4	ccomp
8	her	she	PRP$	O	7	dobj
9	with	with	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	services	service	NNS	O	7	nmod
12	that	that	IN	O	14	mark
13	she	she	PRP	O	14	nsubj
14	needs	need	VBZ	O	7	ccomp
15	now	now	RB	DATE	14	advmod
16	that	that	IN	O	18	mark
17	we	we	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	are	be	VBP	O	14	ccomp
19	still	still	RB	O	18	advmod
20	around	around	RB	O	18	advmod
21	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	One	one	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
2	major	major	JJ	O	3	amod
3	issue	issue	NN	O	8	nsubj
4	we	we	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	requested	request	VBD	O	3	acl:relcl
6	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
7	your	you	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	help	help	NN	O	0	ROOT
9	in	in	IN	O	10	mark
10	obtaining	obtain	VBG	O	8	acl
11	an	a	DT	O	16	det
12	additional	additional	JJ	O	16	amod
13	VA	VA	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
14	Regional	Regional	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
15	Claims	Claims	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
16	Office	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	dobj
17	here	here	RB	O	19	advmod
18	in	in	IN	O	19	case
19	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	cut	cut	VB	O	10	advcl
22	down	down	RP	O	21	compound:prt
23	on	on	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	long	long	JJ	O	26	amod
26	delays	delay	NNS	O	21	nmod
27	in	in	IN	O	29	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	VA	VA	NNP	LOCATION	26	nmod
30	looking	look	VBG	O	29	acl
31	at	at	IN	O	32	case
32	claims	claim	NNS	O	30	nmod
33	here	here	RB	O	30	advmod
34	in	in	IN	O	35	case
35	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	30	nmod
36	,	,	,	O	8	punct
37	sometimes	sometimes	RB	O	42	advmod
38	,	,	,	O	42	punct
39	the	the	DT	O	40	det
40	Veteran	Veteran	NNP	O	42	nsubj
41	has	have	VBZ	O	42	aux
42	passed	pass	VBN	O	8	parataxis
43	away	away	RP	O	42	compound:prt
44	before	before	IN	O	48	mark
45	their	they	PRP$	O	46	nmod:poss
46	claim	claim	NN	O	48	nsubjpass
47	is	be	VBZ	O	48	auxpass
48	looked	look	VBN	O	42	advcl
49	at	at	IN	O	48	nmod
50	,	,	,	O	8	punct
51	the	the	DT	O	53	det
52	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	53	compound
53	Veterans	Veterans	NNP	O	54	nsubj
54	deserve	deserve	VB	O	8	parataxis
55	better	better	JJR	O	54	dobj
56	than	than	IN	O	57	case
57	this	this	DT	O	54	nmod
58	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Good	good	JJ	O	2	amod
2	morning	morning	NN	O	0	ROOT
3	!	!	.	O	2	punct

1	Last	last	JJ	DATE	3	amod
2	year	year	NN	DATE	3	compound
3	Miami	Miami	NNP	LOCATION	0	ROOT
4	-	-	:	LOCATION	3	punct
5	Dade	Dade	NNP	LOCATION	6	compound
6	County	County	NNP	LOCATION	7	nsubj
7	had	have	VBD	O	3	parataxis
8	an	a	DT	O	11	det
9	estimated	estimate	VBN	O	11	amod
10	1,500	1,500	CD	NUMBER	11	nummod
11	admissions	admission	NNS	O	7	dobj
12	for	for	IN	O	15	case
13	Sickle	Sickle	NNP	O	15	compound
14	Cell	cell	NN	O	15	compound
15	patients	patient	NNS	O	11	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
17	these	these	DT	O	18	det
18	patients	patient	NNS	O	19	nsubj
19	spent	spend	VBD	O	7	conj
20	12,000	12,000	CD	DURATION	21	nummod
21	days	day	NNS	DURATION	19	nmod:tmod
22	in	in	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	hospital	hospital	NN	O	19	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Please	please	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	eliminate	eliminate	VB	O	1	xcomp
3	8	8	CD	NUMBER	4	nummod
4	petitions	petition	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	from	from	IN	O	7	case
6	that	that	DT	O	7	det
7	list	list	NN	O	2	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	performance	performance	NN	O	10	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	7	case
4	the	the	DT	O	7	det
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	Florida	Florida	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	compound
7	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
8	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	9	case
9	Corrections	Corrections	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	7	nmod
10	continues	continue	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	decline	decline	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	,	,	,	O	10	punct
14	while	while	IN	O	26	mark
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	corruption	corruption	NN	O	26	nsubj
17	within	within	IN	O	18	case
18	management	management	NN	O	16	nmod
19	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	problems	problem	NNS	O	16	conj
22	caused	cause	VBN	O	21	acl
23	by	by	IN	O	25	case
24	that	that	DT	O	25	det
25	corruption	corruption	NN	O	22	nmod
26	continue	continue	VBP	O	10	advcl
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	increase	increase	VB	O	26	xcomp
29	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Several	several	JJ	DATE	2	amod
2	months	month	NNS	DATE	5	advmod
3	ago	ago	IN	DATE	2	case
4	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	turned	turn	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	in	in	RP	O	5	compound:prt
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	name	name	NN	O	5	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	R.Jay	R.Jay	NNP	PERSON	11	compound
11	Taylor	Taylor	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	Palmetto	Palmetto	NNP	O	11	nmod
14	for	for	IN	O	15	case
15	consideration	consideration	NN	O	13	nmod
16	to	to	TO	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	Board	Board	NNP	O	5	nmod
19	of	of	IN	O	24	case
20	the	the	DT	O	24	det
21	Florida	Florida	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	compound
22	Housing	Housing	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	compound
23	Finance	Finance	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	compound
24	Corp.	Corp.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Therefore	therefore	RB	O	4	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	ask	ask	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	you	you	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	veto	veto	VB	O	4	xcomp
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	bill	bill	NN	O	7	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	allow	allow	VB	O	9	acl
12	anyone	anyone	NN	O	11	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	fly	fly	VB	O	11	xcomp
15	a	a	DT	O	16	det
16	flag	flag	NN	O	14	dobj
17	any	any	DT	O	18	det
18	way	way	NN	O	16	dep
19	they	they	PRP	O	20	nsubj
20	choose	choose	VBP	O	16	acl:relcl
21	,	,	,	O	4	punct
22	if	if	IN	O	24	mark
23	they	they	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	live	live	VBP	O	4	advcl
25	in	in	IN	O	29	case
26	a	a	DT	O	29	det
27	Deed	deed	NN	O	29	compound
28	Restricted	Restricted	NNP	O	29	compound
29	Community	Community	NNP	O	24	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Second	second	RB	ORDINAL	23	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	23	punct
3	even	even	RB	O	7	advmod
4	if	if	IN	O	7	mark
5	DEP	dep	NN	ORGANIZATION	7	nsubj
6	could	could	MD	O	7	aux
7	justify	justify	VB	O	23	advcl
8	using	use	VBG	O	7	xcomp
9	its	its	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	method	method	NN	O	8	dobj
11	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
12	accurately	accurately	RB	O	13	advmod
13	assess	assess	VB	O	10	acl
14	water	water	NN	O	15	compound
15	quality	quality	NN	O	13	dobj
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	Everglades	Everglades	NNPS	LOCATION	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	23	punct
20	this	this	DT	O	22	det
21	averaging	averaging	NN	O	22	compound
22	method	method	NN	O	23	nsubj
23	underestimates	underestimate	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	damage	damage	NN	O	26	compound
26	spreading	spreading	NN	O	23	dobj
27	in	in	IN	O	30	case
28	biologically	biologically	RB	O	29	advmod
29	important	important	JJ	O	30	amod
30	areas	area	NNS	O	26	nmod
31	of	of	IN	O	33	case
32	the	the	DT	O	33	det
33	Everglades	Everglades	NNPS	LOCATION	30	nmod
34	through	through	IN	O	36	case
35	statistical	statistical	JJ	O	36	amod
36	dilution	dilution	NN	O	23	nmod
37	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	Who	who	WP	O	3	nsubj
2	will	will	MD	O	3	aux
3	determine	determine	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	what	what	WP	O	6	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
6	severe	severe	JJ	O	3	ccomp
7	enough	enough	RB	O	6	advmod
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	make	make	VB	O	6	xcomp
10	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	public	public	JJ	O	9	xcomp
12	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	Your	you	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	stand	stand	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	for	for	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	truth	truth	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	that	that	WDT	O	11	nsubj
8	's	be	VBZ	O	11	cop
9	just	just	RB	O	11	advmod
10	as	as	IN	O	11	case
11	real	real	JJ	O	6	acl:relcl
12	as	as	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	law	law	NN	O	11	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	gravity	gravity	NN	O	14	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	6	punct
18	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
19	those	those	DT	O	6	conj
20	who	who	WP	O	21	nsubj
21	oppose	oppose	VBP	O	19	acl:relcl
22	it	it	PRP	O	24	nsubjpass
23	are	be	VBP	O	24	auxpass
24	destined	destine	VBN	O	21	ccomp
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	fall	fall	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	you	you	PRP	O	1	dobj
3	for	for	IN	O	4	mark
4	writing	write	VBG	O	1	advcl
5	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	have	have	VBP	O	3	aux
3	progressed	progress	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
6	have	have	VBP	O	3	conj
7	a	a	DT	O	9	det
8	long	long	JJ	O	9	amod
9	way	way	NN	O	6	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	go	go	VB	O	9	acl
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	would	would	MD	O	3	aux
3	need	need	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	Amtrak	Amtrak	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	dobj
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	haul	haul	VB	O	3	xcomp
7	our	we	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
8	trains	train	NNS	O	6	dobj
9	over	over	IN	O	13	case
10	its	its	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
11	Northeast	Northeast	NNP	O	13	compound
12	Corridor	Corridor	NNP	O	13	compound
13	Line	Line	NNP	O	6	nmod
14	between	between	IN	O	17	case
15	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
16	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
17	City	City	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	Washington	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	21	compound
20	,	,	,	LOCATION	21	punct
21	DC	DC	NNP	LOCATION	17	conj
22	with	with	IN	O	25	case
23	its	its	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
24	electric	electric	JJ	O	25	amod
25	locomotives	locomotive	NNS	O	17	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	6	punct
27	as	as	RB	O	6	cc
28	well	well	RB	O	27	mwe
29	as	as	IN	O	27	mwe
30	maintain	maintain	VB	O	6	conj
31	our	we	PRP$	O	32	nmod:poss
32	equipment	equipment	NN	O	30	dobj
33	in	in	IN	O	35	case
34	New	New	NNP	LOCATION	35	compound
35	York	York	NNP	LOCATION	30	nmod
36	,	,	,	O	35	punct
37	Washington	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	35	conj
38	,	,	,	O	35	punct
39	and	and	CC	O	35	cc
40	possibly	possibly	RB	O	41	advmod
41	Philadelphia	Philadelphia	NNP	LOCATION	35	conj
42	,	,	,	O	41	punct
43	PA	pa	NN	LOCATION	41	appos
44	;	;	:	O	3	punct
45	however	however	RB	O	49	advmod
46	Amtrak	Amtrak	NNP	ORGANIZATION	49	nsubjpass
47	would	would	MD	O	49	aux
48	be	be	VB	O	49	auxpass
49	paid	pay	VBN	O	3	parataxis
50	for	for	IN	O	52	case
51	its	its	PRP$	O	52	nmod:poss
52	services	service	NNS	O	49	nmod
53	,	,	,	O	49	punct
54	thus	thus	RB	O	55	advmod
55	making	make	VBG	O	49	xcomp
56	Beacon	Beacon	NNP	LOCATION	57	compound
57	Park	Park	NNP	LOCATION	59	nsubj
58	fully	fully	RB	O	59	advmod
59	responsible	responsible	JJ	O	55	xcomp
60	for	for	IN	O	62	case
61	all	all	DT	O	62	det
62	costs	cost	NNS	O	59	nmod
63	involved	involve	VBN	O	62	acl
64	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	BlackBerry.net	blackberry.net	NN	O	0	ROOT
2	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	1	punct

1	Are	be	VBP	O	3	aux
2	you	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	meeting	meet	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	with	with	IN	O	6	case
5	John	John	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Agwunobi	Agwunobi	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	Shelly	Shelly	NNP	PERSON	9	compound
9	Brantly	Brantly	NNP	PERSON	6	conj
10	while	while	IN	O	12	case
11	in	in	IN	O	12	case
12	Tallahassee	Tallahassee	NNP	LOCATION	3	nmod
13	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	__________________________________________	__________________________________________	NN	O	2	compound
2	NetZero	NetZero	NNP	ORGANIZATION	0	ROOT
3	-	-	:	O	2	punct
4	Defenders	defender	NNS	O	2	dep
5	of	of	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	Free	Free	NNP	MISC	8	compound
8	World	World	NNP	MISC	4	nmod
9	Get	get	VB	MISC	4	dep
10	your	you	PRP$	MISC	13	nmod:poss
11	FREE	FREE	NNP	MISC	13	compound
12	Internet	Internet	NNP	MISC	13	compound
13	Access	access	NN	MISC	9	dobj
14	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
15	Email	email	VB	O	9	conj
16	at	at	IN	O	17	case
17	http://www.netzero.net/download/index.html	http://www.netzero.net/download/index.html	NN	O	15	nmod
18	__________________________________________	__________________________________________	CD	NUMBER	17	nummod

1	Can	can	MD	O	3	aux
2	you	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	recommend	recommend	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	how	how	WRB	O	7	advmod
5	we	we	PRP	O	7	nsubj
6	can	can	MD	O	7	aux
7	get	get	VB	O	3	ccomp
8	funding	fund	VBG	O	7	xcomp
9	for	for	IN	O	10	case
10	transportation	transportation	NN	O	8	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
12	lodging	lodging	NN	O	10	conj
13	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	are	be	VBP	O	4	cop
3	very	very	RB	O	4	advmod
4	beneficial	beneficial	JJ	O	0	ROOT
5	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Paul	Paul	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
2	Nashville	Nashville	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
3	Orlando	Orlando	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
4	Philadelphia	Philadelphia	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
5	Phoenix	Phoenix	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
6	Pittsburgh	Pittsburgh	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
7	Portland	Portland	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
8	Raleigh/Durham	Raleigh/Durham	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
9	Sacramento	Sacramento	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
10	St.	St.	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
11	Louis	Louis	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
12	San	San	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
13	Antonio	Antonio	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
14	San	San	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
15	Francisco	Francisco	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
16	San	San	NNP	LOCATION	17	compound
17	Jose	Jose	NNP	LOCATION	0	ROOT

1	But	but	CC	O	4	cc
2	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	can	can	MD	O	4	aux
4	remeber	remeber	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	whole	whole	JJ	O	7	amod
7	idea	idea	NN	O	4	dobj
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	stories	story	NNS	O	7	conj
10	behind	behind	IN	O	11	case
11	this	this	DT	O	4	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	lesson	lesson	NN	O	11	appos
15	that	that	WDT	O	17	nsubj
16	was	be	VBD	O	17	aux
17	trying	try	VBG	O	14	acl:relcl
18	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
19	be	be	VB	O	20	auxpass
20	taught	teach	VBN	O	17	xcomp
21	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	time	time	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	the	the	DT	O	8	det
5	FBI	FBI	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	U.S.	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	5	conj
8	Attorney	Attorney	NNP	O	9	nsubj
9	explain	explain	VB	O	3	acl:relcl
10	to	to	TO	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	public	public	JJ	O	9	nmod
13	why	why	WRB	O	12	dep
14	?	?	.	O	3	punct

1	Testing	test	VBG	O	0	ROOT
2	for	for	IN	O	4	case
3	Learning	Learning	NNP	O	4	compound
4	Disabilities	Disabilities	NNPS	O	1	nmod
5	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	plus	plus	CC	O	4	advmod
2	that	that	DT	O	4	nsubj
3	would	would	MD	O	4	aux
4	breake	breake	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	our	we	PRP$	O	4	dobj
6	by	by	IN	O	7	case
7	laws	law	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	you	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	Lee	Lee	NNP	PERSON	1	xcomp
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Well	well	RB	O	17	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	17	punct
3	Governor	governor	NN	O	17	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	as	as	IN	O	7	mark
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	mother	mother	NN	O	3	dep
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	teacher	teacher	NN	O	7	appos
11	,	,	,	O	7	punct
12	grandmother	grandmother	NN	O	7	appos
13	...	...	:	O	7	punct
14	I	I	PRP	O	7	dep
15	will	will	MD	O	17	aux
16	still	still	RB	O	17	advmod
17	say	say	VB	O	0	ROOT
18	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
19	even	even	RB	O	20	advmod
20	today	today	NN	DATE	17	dep
21	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	My	my	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	group	group	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	given	give	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	responsibility	responsibility	NN	O	4	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	mark
8	finding	find	VBG	O	6	acl
9	out	out	RP	O	8	compound:prt
10	exactly	exactly	RB	O	11	advmod
11	how	how	WRB	O	13	advmod
12	we	we	PRP	O	13	nsubj
13	elect	elect	VBP	O	8	ccomp
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	State	state	NN	O	16	compound
16	Governor	governor	NN	O	13	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	outspoken	outspoken	JJ	O	3	amod
3	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	14	nsubj
4	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
5	a	a	DT	O	8	det
6	very	very	RB	O	7	advmod
7	few	few	JJ	O	8	amod
8	parents	parent	NNS	O	3	conj
9	of	of	IN	O	11	case
10	this	this	DT	O	11	det
11	school	school	NN	O	8	nmod
12	would	would	MD	O	14	aux
13	rather	rather	RB	O	14	advmod
14	remain	remain	VB	O	0	ROOT
15	staus	staus	JJ	O	16	amod
16	quo	quo	NN	O	14	xcomp
17	with	with	IN	O	22	case
18	a	a	DT	O	22	det
19	D	d	NN	O	22	compound
20	or	or	CC	O	19	cc
21	F	f	NN	O	19	conj
22	rating	rating	NN	O	14	nmod
23	than	than	IN	O	14	dep
24	assist	assist	VB	O	14	dep
25	me	I	PRP	O	24	dobj
26	in	in	IN	O	27	mark
27	continuing	continue	VBG	O	24	advcl
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	efforts	effort	NNS	O	27	dobj
30	I	I	PRP	O	32	nsubj
31	have	have	VBP	O	32	aux
32	begun	begin	VBN	O	29	acl:relcl
33	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	are	be	VBP	O	3	aux
3	counting	count	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	on	on	IN	O	6	case
5	your	you	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	support	support	NN	O	3	nmod
7	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	And	and	CC	O	4	cc
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	you	you	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	need	need	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	explain	explain	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	to	to	TO	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	press	press	NN	O	6	nmod
10	the	the	DT	O	13	det
11	special	special	JJ	O	13	amod
12	relationship	relationship	NN	O	13	compound
13	individuals	individual	NNS	O	19	nsubj
14	associated	associate	VBN	O	13	acl
15	with	with	IN	O	17	case
16	this	this	DT	O	17	det
17	case	case	NN	O	14	nmod
18	have	have	VBP	O	19	aux
19	had	have	VBN	O	9	acl:relcl
20	,	,	,	O	6	punct
21	or	or	CC	O	6	cc
22	do	do	VB	O	23	aux
23	have	have	VB	O	6	conj
24	to	to	TO	O	27	case
25	the	the	DT	O	27	det
26	Hospice	Hospice	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	compound
27	Board	Board	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	4	det
2	Family	Family	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
3	Care	Care	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	compound
4	Council	Council	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nsubj
5	feels	feel	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	there	there	EX	O	7	expl
7	are	be	VBP	O	5	ccomp
8	several	several	JJ	O	9	amod
9	avenues	avenue	NNS	O	7	nsubj
10	available	available	JJ	O	9	amod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	accomplish	accomplish	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	goal	goal	NN	O	12	dobj
15	of	of	IN	O	16	mark
16	reducing	reduce	VBG	O	14	acl
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	deficit	deficit	NN	O	16	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	have	have	VBP	O	4	aux
3	only	only	RB	O	4	advmod
4	received	receive	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	2	2	CD	NUMBER	4	dobj
6	that	that	WDT	O	9	nsubj
7	will	will	MD	O	9	aux
8	be	be	VB	O	9	aux
9	attending	attend	VBG	O	5	acl:relcl
10	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Tim	Tim	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
3	also	also	RB	O	5	advmod
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	candidate	candidate	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	for	for	IN	O	8	case
7	an	a	DT	O	8	det
8	appointment	appointment	NN	O	5	nmod
9	as	as	IN	O	12	case
10	Leon	Leon	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
11	county	county	NN	O	12	compound
12	judge	judge	NN	O	8	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	legislation	legislation	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	in	in	IN	O	5	case
4	no	no	DT	O	5	neg
5	way	way	NN	O	2	nmod
6	prevents	prevent	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
7	an	a	DT	O	8	det
8	individual	individual	JJ	O	6	dobj
9	from	from	IN	O	10	mark
10	protesting	protest	VBG	O	6	advcl
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	approval	approval	NN	O	10	dobj
13	of	of	IN	O	17	case
14	a	a	DT	O	17	det
15	specific	specific	JJ	O	17	amod
16	development	development	NN	O	17	compound
17	order	order	NN	O	12	nmod
18	approved	approve	VBN	O	17	acl
19	under	under	IN	O	22	case
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	variance	variance	NN	O	22	compound
22	standard	standard	NN	O	18	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	6	nsubj
2	are	be	VBP	O	6	cop
3	really	really	RB	O	6	advmod
4	at	at	IN	O	6	case
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	crossroads	crossroads	NNS	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	19	mark
8	NWFL	nwfl	NN	ORGANIZATION	19	nsubj
9	.	.	.	O	8	punct
10	Losing	lose	VBG	O	8	dep
11	our	we	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	seat	seat	NN	O	10	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	case
14	JAX	JAX	NNP	O	10	nmod
15	would	would	MD	O	19	aux
16	be	be	VB	O	19	cop
17	a	a	DT	O	19	det
18	tremendous	tremendous	JJ	O	19	amod
19	setback	setback	NN	O	6	advcl
20	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Screening	screen	VBG	O	0	ROOT
2	each	each	DT	O	4	det
3	enrolling	enrol	VBG	O	4	amod
4	child	child	NN	O	1	dobj
5	for	for	IN	O	7	case
6	developmental	developmental	JJ	O	7	amod
7	abilities	ability	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	so	so	RB	O	2	advmod
2	now	now	RB	DATE	3	dep
3	its	its	PRP$	O	0	ROOT
4	like	like	IN	O	5	mark
5	starting	start	VBG	O	3	acl
6	all	all	DT	O	7	dep
7	over	over	RP	O	5	advmod
8	again	again	RB	O	5	advmod
9	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	We	we	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	presented	present	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	several	several	JJ	O	4	amod
4	issues	issue	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	If	if	IN	O	7	mark
2	those	those	DT	O	3	det
3	tests	test	NNS	O	7	nsubjpass
4	are	be	VBP	O	7	auxpass
5	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
6	all	all	DT	O	7	advmod
7	passed	pass	VBN	O	26	advcl
8	in	in	IN	O	11	case
9	a	a	DT	O	11	det
10	certain	certain	JJ	O	11	amod
11	period	period	NN	O	7	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	time	time	NN	O	11	nmod
14	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
15	teacher	teacher	NN	O	19	nsubj
16	can	can	MD	O	19	aux
17	no	no	RB	O	18	neg
18	longer	longer	RB	O	19	advmod
19	receive	receive	VB	O	7	ccomp
20	fulltime	fulltime	JJ	O	22	amod
21	teacher	teacher	NN	O	22	compound
22	status	status	NN	O	19	dobj
23	,	,	,	O	26	punct
24	much	much	RB	O	25	advmod
25	less	less	JJR	O	26	advmod
26	maintain	maintain	VB	O	0	ROOT
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	benefits	benefit	NNS	O	26	dobj
29	.	.	.	O	26	punct

1	Private	private	JJ	O	2	amod
2	Message	message	NN	O	12	dep
3	from	from	IN	O	8	case
4	J.	J.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
5	C.	C.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
6	Bowman	Bowman	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
7	Office	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	Number	Number	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
9	850-922-6398	850-922-6398	CD	ORGANIZATION	12	dep
10	DOE	DOE	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
11	Office	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	compound
12	Number	Number	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	dep
13	850-487-6555	850-487-6555	CD	NUMBER	14	nummod
14	Cell	cell	NN	O	12	dep
15	Phone	Phone	NNP	O	16	compound
16	Number	Number	NNP	O	14	dep
17	850-591-6398	850-591-6398	CD	NUMBER	0	ROOT

1	''	''	''	O	11	punct
2	It	it	PRP	O	6	nsubj
3	's	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	dumb	dumb	JJ	O	6	amod
6	idea	idea	NN	O	11	ccomp
7	,	,	,	O	11	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	11	nsubj
9	we	we	PRP	O	11	advmod
10	've	have	VBP	O	11	aux
11	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
12	as	as	RB	O	13	advmod
13	much	much	JJ	O	11	advcl
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	''	''	''	O	13	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	4	amod
4	time	time	NN	O	8	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	IRCC	ircc	NN	ORGANIZATION	8	nsubj
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	aux
8	planning	plan	VBG	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	offer	offer	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	four	four	CD	DURATION	10	dobj
13	-	-	:	DURATION	8	punct
14	week	week	NN	DURATION	16	compound
15	crash	crash	NN	O	16	compound
16	course	course	NN	O	21	nsubj
17	this	this	DT	DATE	18	det
18	summer	summer	NN	DATE	16	nmod:tmod
19	to	to	TO	O	20	case
20	60	60	CD	NUMBER	16	nmod
21	wo	will	MD	O	8	parataxis
22	...	...	:	O	8	punct
23	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	5	mark
2	being	be	VBG	O	5	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	lead	lead	JJ	O	5	amod
5	investor	investor	NN	O	12	advcl
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	these	these	DT	O	8	det
8	projects	project	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	12	punct
10	Golden	Golden	NNP	O	11	compound
11	LEAF	LEAF	NNP	O	12	nsubj
12	will	will	MD	O	0	ROOT
13	leverage	leverage	NN	O	12	dobj
14	an	a	DT	O	20	det
15	estimated	estimate	VBN	O	20	amod
16	$	$	$	MONEY	20	dep
17	150	150	CD	MONEY	20	compound
18	million	million	CD	MONEY	20	compound
19	to	to	TO	O	20	dep
20	$	$	$	MONEY	12	xcomp
21	200	200	CD	MONEY	22	compound
22	million	million	CD	MONEY	20	nummod
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	total	total	JJ	O	25	amod
25	investments	investment	NNS	O	20	nmod
26	in	in	IN	O	27	case
27	new	new	JJ	O	25	nmod
28	and	and	CC	O	25	cc
29	emerging	emerge	VBG	O	30	amod
30	companies	company	NNS	O	25	conj
31	in	in	IN	O	34	case
32	the	the	DT	O	34	det
33	life	life	NN	O	34	compound
34	sciences	science	NNS	O	30	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	am	be	VBP	O	3	aux
3	passing	pass	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	along	along	IN	O	6	case
5	your	you	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	information	information	NN	O	3	nmod
7	regarding	regard	VBG	O	9	case
8	school	school	NN	O	9	compound
9	choice	choice	NN	O	6	nmod
10	to	to	TO	O	14	case
11	our	we	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
12	education	education	NN	O	14	compound
13	policy	policy	NN	O	14	compound
14	unit	unit	NN	O	9	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	To	to	TO	O	3	case
2	some	some	DT	O	3	det
3	degree	degree	NN	O	6	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	6	punct
5	we	we	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	believe	believe	VBP	O	0	ROOT
7	it	it	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	should	should	MD	O	6	ccomp
9	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	6	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
3	not	not	RB	O	6	neg
4	even	even	RB	O	6	advmod
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	question	question	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	before	before	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	state	state	NN	O	6	nmod
10	!	!	.	O	6	punct

1	Since	since	IN	O	3	mark
2	ADMINISTRATIUM	ADMINISTRATIUM	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nsubj
3	has	have	VBZ	O	9	advcl
4	no	no	DT	O	5	neg
5	electrons	electron	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	,	,	,	O	9	punct
7	it	it	PRP	O	9	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
9	inert	inert	JJ	O	0	ROOT
10	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	unfortunate	unfortunate	JJ	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
5	some	some	DT	O	6	det
6	one	one	CD	NUMBER	10	nsubj
7	so	so	RB	O	8	advmod
8	untrained	untrained	JJ	O	6	amod
9	would	would	MD	O	10	aux
10	seek	seek	VB	O	3	ccomp
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	exploit	exploit	VB	O	10	xcomp
13	such	such	JJ	O	14	amod
14	vulnerability	vulnerability	NN	O	12	dobj
15	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	5	det
2	primary	primary	JJ	O	5	amod
3	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
4	hot	hot	JJ	O	2	conj
5	issue	issue	NN	O	15	nsubj
6	of	of	IN	O	11	case
7	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Curenton	Curenton	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	Grand	Grand	NNP	MISC	11	compound
11	Jury	Jury	NNP	MISC	5	nmod
12	was	be	VBD	O	15	cop
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	pipeline	pipeline	NN	O	15	compound
15	issue	issue	NN	O	0	ROOT
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	failure	failure	NN	O	15	conj
19	of	of	IN	O	22	case
20	the	the	DT	O	22	det
21	primary	primary	JJ	O	22	amod
22	contractor	contractor	NN	O	18	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	15	punct
24	James	James	NNP	PERSON	25	compound
25	Finch	Finch	NNP	PERSON	15	conj
26	,	,	,	O	15	punct
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	bury	bury	VB	O	15	acl
29	that	that	IN	O	54	mark
30	sewage	sewage	NN	O	31	compound
31	pipeline	pipeline	NN	O	54	nsubj
32	as	as	IN	O	33	advmod
33	required	require	VBN	O	31	acl
34	by	by	IN	O	36	case
35	the	the	DT	O	36	det
36	contract	contract	NN	O	33	nmod
37	and	and	CC	O	36	cc
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	failure	failure	NN	O	36	conj
40	of	of	IN	O	44	case
41	county	county	NN	O	44	compound
42	and	and	CC	O	41	cc
43	state	state	NN	O	41	conj
44	officials	official	NNS	O	39	nmod
45	to	to	TO	O	46	mark
46	enforce	enforce	VB	O	33	xcomp
47	the	the	DT	O	48	det
48	requirements	requirement	NNS	O	46	dobj
49	of	of	IN	O	52	case
50	the	the	DT	O	52	det
51	contract	contract	NN	O	52	compound
52	specifications	specification	NNS	O	48	nmod
53	to	to	TO	O	54	mark
54	bury	bury	VB	O	28	ccomp
55	the	the	DT	O	56	det
56	pipeline	pipeline	NN	O	54	dobj
57	under	under	IN	O	59	case
58	the	the	DT	O	59	det
59	bottom	bottom	NN	O	54	nmod
60	of	of	IN	O	62	case
61	our	we	PRP$	O	62	nmod:poss
62	now	now	RB	DATE	59	nmod
63	-	-	:	O	59	punct
64	pristine	pristine	JJ	O	59	amod
65	St.	St.	NNP	O	68	compound
66	Andrew	Andrew	NNP	PERSON	68	compound
67	Bay	Bay	NNP	PERSON	68	compound
68	waters	water	NNS	O	59	dep
69	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	projections	projection	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
6	we	we	PRP	O	8	nsubj
7	will	will	MD	O	8	aux
8	continue	continue	VB	O	3	ccomp
9	being	be	VBG	O	12	cop
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	fastest	fastest	JJS	O	12	dep
12	growing	grow	VBG	O	8	xcomp
13	for	for	IN	O	17	case
14	the	the	DT	DURATION	17	det
15	next	next	JJ	DURATION	17	amod
16	five	five	CD	DURATION	17	nummod
17	years	year	NNS	DURATION	12	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Governor	governor	NN	O	4	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	4	punct
3	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	understand	understand	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	Louis	Louis	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Chenevert	Chenevert	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
7	mentioned	mention	VBD	O	4	ccomp
8	we	we	PRP	O	10	nsubj
9	are	be	VBP	O	10	cop
10	close	close	JJ	O	7	ccomp
11	to	to	TO	O	12	case
12	Miss.	Miss.	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	15	case
14	our	we	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	proposal	proposal	NN	O	12	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	7	punct
17	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
18	that	that	IN	O	24	mark
19	an	a	DT	O	22	det
20	interest	interest	NN	O	22	compound
21	free	free	JJ	O	22	amod
22	loan	loan	NN	O	24	nsubj
23	could	could	MD	O	24	aux
24	make	make	VB	O	7	conj
25	us	we	PRP	O	28	nsubj
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	choice	choice	NN	O	28	compound
28	site	site	NN	O	24	xcomp
29	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	recognize	recognize	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	that	that	IN	O	15	mark
4	Hardee	Hardee	NNP	LOCATION	5	compound
5	County	County	NNP	LOCATION	15	nsubj
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	more	more	JJR	O	12	amod
8	than	than	IN	O	7	dep
9	most	most	JJS	O	7	dep
10	other	other	JJ	O	12	amod
11	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	12	compound
12	counties	county	NNS	O	5	appos
13	,	,	,	O	5	punct
14	must	must	MD	O	15	aux
15	bear	bear	VB	O	2	ccomp
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	burden	burden	NN	O	15	dobj
18	imposed	impose	VBN	O	17	acl
19	on	on	IN	O	22	case
20	your	you	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
21	land	land	NN	O	22	compound
22	resources	resource	NNS	O	18	nmod
23	from	from	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	extensive	extensive	JJ	O	26	amod
26	mining	mining	NN	O	18	nmod
27	of	of	IN	O	28	case
28	phosphate	phosphate	NN	O	26	nmod
29	in	in	IN	O	31	case
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	county	county	NN	O	28	nmod
32	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	you	you	PRP	O	1	dobj
3	so	so	RB	O	4	advmod
4	much	much	RB	O	1	advmod
5	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	know	know	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	you	you	PRP	O	5	nsubj
4	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
5	do	do	VB	O	2	ccomp
6	your	you	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	best	best	JJS	O	5	dobj
8	to	to	TO	O	9	mark
9	do	do	VB	O	5	advcl
10	what	what	WP	O	12	nsubj
11	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
12	right	right	RB	O	9	ccomp
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	as	as	IN	O	17	mark
15	you	you	PRP	O	17	nsubj
16	have	have	VBP	O	17	aux
17	done	do	VBN	O	12	advcl
18	before	before	IN	O	17	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	you	you	PRP	O	1	dobj
3	very	very	RB	O	4	advmod
4	much	much	RB	O	1	advmod
5	for	for	IN	O	6	mark
6	taking	take	VBG	O	1	advcl
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	time	time	NN	O	6	dobj
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	write	write	VB	O	8	acl
11	to	to	TO	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	Florida	Florida	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
14	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	nmod
15	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	16	case
16	Representatives	Representatives	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	14	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	Just	just	RB	O	4	advmod
2	this	this	DT	DATE	4	det
3	past	past	JJ	DATE	4	amod
4	week	week	NN	DATE	7	nmod
5	we	we	PRP	O	7	nsubj
6	have	have	VBP	O	7	aux
7	had	have	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	a	a	DT	O	11	det
9	fifth	fifth	JJ	ORDINAL	11	amod
10	grader	grader	NN	O	11	compound
11	shot	shot	NN	O	7	dobj
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	head	head	NN	O	11	nmod
15	on	on	IN	O	17	case
16	her	she	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	way	way	NN	O	14	nmod
18	to	to	TO	O	19	case
19	school	school	NN	O	7	nmod
20	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
21	a	a	DT	O	25	det
22	county	county	NN	O	25	compound
23	wide	wide	JJ	O	25	amod
24	bomb	bomb	NN	O	25	compound
25	threat	threat	NN	O	19	conj
26	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	meantime	meantime	NN	O	9	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	9	punct
5	press	press	NN	O	6	compound
6	coverage	coverage	NN	O	9	nsubj
7	has	have	VBZ	O	9	aux
8	been	be	VBN	O	9	aux
9	proliferating	proliferate	VBG	O	0	ROOT
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
12	RTC	RTC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	nsubj
13	will	will	MD	O	14	aux
14	continue	continue	VB	O	9	conj
15	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
16	work	work	VB	O	14	xcomp
17	with	with	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	news	news	NN	O	20	compound
20	media	media	NNS	O	16	nmod
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	get	get	VB	O	16	xcomp
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	word	word	NN	O	22	dobj
25	out	out	IN	O	22	advmod
26	about	about	IN	O	35	mark
27	how	how	WRB	O	28	advmod
28	important	important	JJ	O	35	dep
29	the	the	DT	O	32	det
30	Transportation	transportation	NN	O	32	compound
31	Enhancements	Enhancements	NNP	O	32	compound
32	program	program	NN	O	35	nsubj
33	is	be	VBZ	O	35	cop
34	for	for	IN	O	35	case
35	communities	community	NNS	O	25	advcl
36	across	across	IN	O	38	case
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	country	country	NN	O	35	nmod
39	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	family	family	NN	O	7	nsubj
3	will	will	MD	O	7	aux
4	never	never	RB	O	7	neg
5	be	be	VB	O	7	cop
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	same	same	JJ	O	0	ROOT
8	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Remember	remember	VB	O	9	csubj
2	those	those	DT	O	3	nsubj
3	unhappy	unhappy	JJ	O	1	xcomp
4	with	with	IN	O	7	case
5	school	school	NN	O	7	compound
6	board	board	NN	O	7	compound
7	members	member	NNS	O	3	nmod
8	may	may	MD	O	9	aux
9	voice	voice	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	their	they	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	feelings	feeling	NNS	O	9	dobj
12	at	at	IN	O	14	case
13	election	election	NN	O	14	compound
14	time	time	NN	O	9	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Besides	besides	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	note	note	NN	O	8	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	5	case
5	thanks	thanks	NNS	O	3	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	8	punct
7	this	this	DT	O	8	nsubj
8	added	add	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	4	case
2	a	a	DT	O	4	det
3	hurting	hurt	VBG	O	4	amod
4	heart	heart	NN	O	0	ROOT
5	,	,	,	O	4	punct
6	Burma	burma	NN	LOCATION	4	appos

1	If	if	IN	O	7	mark
2	you	you	PRP	O	7	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	7	cop
4	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
5	the	the	DT	O	7	det
6	intended	intended	JJ	O	7	amod
7	recipient	recipient	JJ	O	14	advcl
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	you	you	PRP	O	7	appos
10	many	many	JJ	O	12	amod
11	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	copy	copy	NN	O	9	dep
13	,	,	,	O	14	punct
14	disclose	disclose	VB	O	0	ROOT
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	or	or	CC	O	14	cc
17	distribute	distribute	VB	O	14	conj
18	this	this	DT	O	19	det
19	message	message	NN	O	17	dobj
20	or	or	CC	O	19	cc
21	its	its	PRP$	O	22	nmod:poss
22	contents	contents	NNS	O	19	conj
23	to	to	TO	O	26	case
24	any	any	DT	O	26	det
25	other	other	JJ	O	26	amod
26	person	person	NN	O	17	nmod
27	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
28	any	any	DT	O	30	det
29	such	such	JJ	O	30	amod
30	actions	action	NNS	O	33	nsubj
31	may	may	MD	O	33	aux
32	be	be	VB	O	33	cop
33	unlawful	unlawful	JJ	O	14	conj
34	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	6	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	6	punct
3	maybe	maybe	RB	O	6	advmod
4	you	you	PRP	O	6	nsubj
5	could	could	MD	O	6	aux
6	drop	drop	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	MCCO	MCCO	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	office	office	NN	O	6	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	say	say	VB	O	6	xcomp
13	hello	hello	UH	O	12	dobj
14	to	to	TO	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	troops	troops	NNS	O	12	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	did	do	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	it	it	PRP	O	2	dobj
4	,	,	,	O	2	punct
5	because	because	IN	O	8	mark
6	like	like	IN	O	8	mark
7	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	told	tell	VBD	O	2	advcl
9	you	you	PRP	O	8	dobj
10	before	before	RB	O	8	advmod
11	,	,	,	O	8	punct
12	if	if	IN	O	16	mark
13	I	I	PRP	O	16	nsubj
14	can	can	MD	O	16	aux
15	not	not	RB	O	16	neg
16	advocate	advocate	VB	O	8	advcl
17	for	for	IN	O	19	case
18	my	my	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	daughter	daughter	NN	O	16	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	8	punct
21	than	than	IN	O	25	mark
22	what	what	WP	O	25	dobj
23	good	good	JJ	O	25	nsubj
24	am	be	VBP	O	25	cop
25	I	I	PRP	O	8	advcl
26	?	?	.	O	2	punct

1	Your	you	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	office	office	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	responded	respond	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	8	mark
5	murderers	murderer	NNS	O	8	nsubj
6	should	should	MD	O	8	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	seek	seek	VB	O	3	ccomp
9	refuge	refuge	NN	O	8	dobj
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	aux
3	going	go	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	tuck	tuck	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	it	it	PRP	O	5	dobj
7	away	away	RB	O	5	advmod
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	some	some	DT	O	10	det
10	corner	corner	NN	O	5	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	13	case
12	my	my	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	mind	mind	NN	O	10	nmod
14	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
15	fall	fall	VB	O	5	conj
16	victim	victim	NN	O	15	dobj
17	to	to	TO	O	19	case
18	your	you	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	whole	whole	NN	O	15	nmod
20	''	''	''	O	19	punct
21	next	next	JJ	O	3	advmod
22	''	''	''	O	3	punct
23	mentality	mentality	NN	O	3	dobj
24	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Bea	Bea	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
2	Fowler	Fowler	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	P.S.	P.S.	NNP	PERSON	0	ROOT

1	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	can	can	MD	O	4	aux
3	not	not	RB	O	4	neg
4	loose	loose	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	perspective	perspective	NN	O	4	dobj
6	that	that	IN	O	10	mark
7	Lucy	Lucy	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	reason	reason	NN	O	4	ccomp
11	for	for	IN	O	12	case
12	which	which	WDT	O	17	nmod
13	Milton	Milton	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubjpass
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	I	I	PRP	O	13	conj
16	are	be	VBP	O	17	auxpass
17	involved	involve	VBN	O	10	acl:relcl
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	this	this	DT	O	20	det
20	movement	movement	NN	O	17	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Several	several	JJ	O	6	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	4	case
3	our	we	PRP$	O	4	nmod:poss
4	members	member	NNS	O	1	nmod
5	have	have	VBP	O	6	aux
6	called	call	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	concerning	concern	VBG	O	10	case
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	misleading	misleading	JJ	O	10	amod
10	question	question	NN	O	6	nmod
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	poll	poll	NN	O	10	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Our	we	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	superintendent	superintendent	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	decided	decide	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	he	he	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	does	do	VBZ	O	3	ccomp
6	NOT	NOT	NNP	O	7	nsubj
7	want	want	VB	O	5	ccomp
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	contract	contract	NN	O	10	nsubj
10	extended	extend	VBD	O	7	ccomp
11	beyond	beyond	IN	O	14	case
12	its	its	PRP$	O	14	nmod:poss
13	current	current	JJ	DATE	14	amod
14	length	length	NN	O	10	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	Dec.	Dec.	NNP	DATE	14	appos
17	31	31	CD	DATE	16	nummod
18	,	,	,	DATE	16	punct
19	2000	2000	CD	DATE	16	nummod
20	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	You	you	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
3	I	I	PRP	O	1	conj
4	know	know	VBP	O	0	ROOT
5	more	more	JJR	O	12	amod
6	than	than	IN	O	8	mark
7	we	we	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	have	have	VBP	O	5	ccomp
9	too	too	RB	O	10	advmod
10	many	many	JJ	O	11	amod
11	problems	problem	NNS	O	8	dobj
12	students	student	NNS	O	16	nsubj
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	parents	parent	NNS	O	12	conj
15	are	be	VBP	O	16	aux
16	encountering	encounter	VBG	O	4	ccomp
17	with	with	IN	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	compliance	compliance	NN	O	16	nmod
20	by	by	IN	O	22	case
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	school	school	NN	O	16	nmod
23	on	on	IN	O	24	case
24	IEP	IEP	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	nmod
25	's	's	POS	O	24	case
26	and	and	CC	O	24	cc
27	other	other	JJ	O	29	amod
28	program	program	NN	O	29	compound
29	issues	issue	NNS	O	24	conj
30	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	am	be	VBP	O	3	aux
3	planning	plan	VBG	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	meet	meet	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	with	with	IN	O	8	case
7	Ken	Ken	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Pruitt	Pruitt	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	see	see	VB	O	5	ccomp
11	if	if	IN	O	15	mark
12	we	we	PRP	O	15	nsubj
13	can	can	MD	O	15	aux
14	possibly	possibly	RB	O	15	advmod
15	tag	tag	VB	O	10	advcl
16	on	on	IN	O	18	case
17	50	50	CD	MONEY	18	nummod
18	cents	cent	NNS	MONEY	15	nmod
19	or	or	CC	O	10	cc
20	so	so	IN	O	10	advmod
21	onto	onto	IN	O	26	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	driver	driver	NN	O	26	nmod:poss
24	's	's	POS	O	23	case
25	license	license	NN	O	26	compound
26	fee	fee	NN	O	20	nmod
27	to	to	TO	O	28	mark
28	pay	pay	VB	O	10	conj
29	for	for	IN	O	31	case
30	voter	voter	NN	O	31	compound
31	education	education	NN	O	28	nmod
32	in	in	IN	O	34	case
33	the	the	DT	DATE	34	det
34	future	future	NN	DATE	31	nmod
35	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
2	am	be	VBP	O	5	cop
3	a	a	DT	O	5	det
4	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	5	compound
5	actor	actor	NN	O	0	ROOT
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
8	this	this	DT	O	12	nsubj
9	is	be	VBZ	O	12	cop
10	an	a	DT	O	12	det
11	important	important	JJ	O	12	amod
12	issue	issue	NN	O	5	conj
13	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	you	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	much	much	RB	O	1	xcomp
4	!	!	.	O	1	punct

1	<	<	JJR	O	0	ROOT
2	<	<	JJR	O	3	amod
3	WhyThird.rtf	whythird.rtf	NN	O	6	nmod:npmod
4	>	>	JJR	O	5	nmod:npmod
5	>	>	JJR	O	3	amod
6	<	<	JJR	O	7	amod
7	<	<	JJR	O	1	dep
8	Bartke	Bartke	NNP	PERSON	1	dep
9	to	to	TO	O	12	case
10	Mallot	Mallot	NNP	PERSON	12	compound
11	Letter	Letter	NNP	O	12	compound
12	0606-02.PDF	0606-02.pdf	NN	DATE	8	nmod

1	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	just	just	RB	O	3	advmod
3	wanted	want	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	give	give	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	you	you	PRP	O	5	iobj
7	a	a	DT	O	8	det
8	brief	brief	JJ	O	5	dobj
9	update	update	VBP	O	8	acl:relcl
10	on	on	IN	O	13	case
11	our	we	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
12	continuing	continue	VBG	O	13	amod
13	saga	saga	NN	O	9	nmod
14	with	with	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	DEP	dep	NN	O	13	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct
3	.	.	.	O	1	punct
4	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	1	dep
5	,	,	,	O	1	punct
6	I	I	PRP	O	8	nsubj
7	strongly	strongly	RB	O	8	advmod
8	encourage	encourage	VBP	O	1	acl:relcl
9	you	you	PRP	O	8	dobj
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	appoint	appoint	VB	O	8	xcomp
12	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	11	dobj

1	By	by	IN	O	3	case
2	a	a	DT	O	3	det
3	majority	majority	NN	O	8	nmod
4	vote	vote	VB	O	8	csubj
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	Board	Board	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	dobj
7	has	have	VBZ	O	8	aux
8	recommended	recommend	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	11	case
10	Governor	Governor	NNP	O	11	compound
11	Bush	Bush	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
12	that	that	WDT	O	18	dobj
13	David	David	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Moore	Moore	NNP	PERSON	16	nsubjpass
15	be	be	VB	O	16	auxpass
16	appointed	appoint	VBN	O	11	acl:relcl
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	take	take	VB	O	16	xcomp
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	place	place	NN	O	18	dobj
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	Sonny	Sonny	NNP	PERSON	23	compound
23	Vergera	Vergera	NNP	PERSON	20	nmod
24	,	,	,	O	23	punct
25	his	he	PRP$	O	26	nmod:poss
26	replacement	replacement	NN	O	23	appos
27	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	abovementioned	abovementioned	JJ	O	3	amod
3	actions	action	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	violated	violate	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	Florida	Florida	NNP	LOCATION	6	compound
6	Statutes	Statutes	NNPS	O	4	dobj
7	800.03	800.03	CD	NUMBER	4	nmod:tmod
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	847.0133	847.0133	CD	NUMBER	7	nummod
10	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
11	856.02	856.02	CD	NUMBER	7	conj
12	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Say	say	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	hello	hello	UH	O	1	dobj
3	to	to	TO	O	4	case
4	Devoe	Devoe	NNP	PERSON	1	nmod
5	for	for	IN	O	6	case
6	me	I	PRP	O	4	nmod
7	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	By	by	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	way	way	NN	O	8	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	it	it	PRP	O	8	nsubjpass
6	was	be	VBD	O	8	auxpass
7	duly	duly	RB	O	8	advmod
8	noted	note	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	nationally	nationally	RB	O	8	advmod
10	when	when	WRB	O	15	advmod
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	Governor	governor	NN	O	14	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	Office	Office	NNP	O	15	nsubj
15	reacted	react	VBD	O	8	advcl
16	to	to	TO	O	17	case
17	criticism	criticism	NN	O	15	nmod
18	after	after	IN	O	21	mark
19	an	a	DT	O	20	det
20	execution	execution	NN	O	21	nsubj
21	went	go	VBD	O	15	advcl
22	awry	awry	RB	O	21	advmod
23	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	but	but	CC	O	3	cc
2	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	need	need	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	your	you	PRP$	O	5	nmod:poss
5	help	help	NN	O	3	dobj
6	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	HBIF	hbif	NN	ORGANIZATION	4	nsubjpass
2	is	be	VBZ	O	4	auxpass
3	already	already	RB	O	4	advmod
4	considered	consider	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	in	in	IN	O	10	case
6	many	many	JJ	O	10	amod
7	private	private	JJ	O	10	amod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	public	public	JJ	O	7	conj
10	arenas	arena	NNS	O	4	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
12	be	be	VB	O	15	cop
13	an	a	DT	O	15	det
14	effective	effective	JJ	O	15	amod
15	avenue	avenue	NN	O	10	acl
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	promote	promote	VB	O	15	acl
18	international	international	JJ	O	19	amod
19	business	business	NN	O	17	dobj
20	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
21	are	be	VBP	O	22	aux
22	using	use	VBG	O	4	conj
23	HBIF	hbif	NN	O	22	dobj
24	toward	toward	IN	O	26	case
25	that	that	DT	O	26	det
26	end	end	NN	O	22	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Unfortunately	unfortunately	RB	O	4	advmod
2	we	we	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	4	aux
4	having	have	VBG	O	0	ROOT
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	poor	poor	JJ	O	7	amod
7	response	response	NN	O	4	dobj
8	from	from	IN	O	10	case
9	our	we	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
10	legislators	legislator	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	!	!	.	O	4	punct

1	Congratulations	congratulation	NNS	O	0	ROOT
2	!	!	.	O	1	punct

1	From	from	IN	O	5	case
2	:	:	:	O	5	punct
3	Ferrera	Ferrera	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
4	,	,	,	O	5	punct
5	Eli	Eli	NNP	O	0	ROOT
6	>	>	JJR	O	7	amod
7	Sent	sent	NN	O	5	dep
8	:	:	:	O	5	punct
9	Wednesday	Wednesday	NNP	DATE	11	compound
10	,	,	,	TIME	11	punct
11	May	May	NNP	DATE	5	dep
12	08	08	CD	DATE	11	nummod
13	,	,	,	DATE	11	punct
14	2002	2002	CD	DATE	11	nummod
15	5:03	5:03	CD	TIME	16	nummod
16	PM	pm	NN	TIME	11	acl:relcl
17	>	>	JJR	O	16	advmod
18	To	to	TO	O	17	dep
19	:	:	:	O	16	punct
20	Shanahan	Shanahan	NNP	PERSON	22	compound
21	,	,	,	O	22	punct
22	Kathleen	Kathleen	NNP	PERSON	16	dep
23	>	>	JJR	O	24	amod
24	Cc	cc	NN	O	22	dep
25	:	:	:	O	24	punct
26	'	'	''	O	16	punct
27	jeb@jeb.org	jeb@jeb.org	NN	O	16	dep
28	'	'	''	O	27	punct
29	>	>	JJR	O	27	dep

1	2	2	LS	NUMBER	0	ROOT
2	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	With	with	IN	O	5	case
2	the	the	DT	O	5	det
3	everpresent	everpresent	JJ	O	5	amod
4	elderly	elderly	JJ	O	5	amod
5	community	community	NN	O	13	nmod
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	South	South	NNP	LOCATION	8	compound
8	Broward	Broward	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	13	punct
10	we	we	PRP	O	13	nsubjpass
11	are	be	VBP	O	13	auxpass
12	better	better	RBR	O	13	advmod
13	poised	poise	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	serve	serve	VB	O	13	xcomp
16	that	that	DT	O	17	det
17	community	community	NN	O	15	dobj
18	by	by	IN	O	19	mark
19	having	have	VBG	O	15	advcl
20	a	a	DT	O	23	compound
21	''	''	''	O	23	punct
22	community	community	NN	O	23	compound
23	representative	representative	NN	O	19	xcomp
24	''	''	''	O	13	punct
25	on	on	IN	O	27	case
26	our	we	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
27	board	board	NN	O	13	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	still	still	RB	O	4	advmod
3	would	would	MD	O	4	aux
4	like	like	VB	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	see	see	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	Tim	Tim	NNP	PERSON	6	dobj
8	appointed	appoint	VBN	O	7	acl
9	to	to	TO	O	11	case
10	that	that	DT	O	11	det
11	post	post	NN	O	8	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	thank	thank	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	you	you	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	Scott	Scott	NNP	PERSON	1	xcomp
4	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	This	this	DT	O	2	det
2	film	film	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	won	win	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	prize	prize	NN	O	3	dobj
6	at	at	IN	O	11	case
7	the	the	DT	O	11	det
8	famed	famed	JJ	O	11	amod
9	Sundance	Sundance	NNP	O	11	compound
10	Film	Film	NNP	O	11	compound
11	Festival	Festival	NNP	O	3	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	What	what	WDT	O	2	det
2	difference	difference	NN	O	5	dobj
3	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
4	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	make	make	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	if	if	IN	O	8	mark
7	you	you	PRP	O	8	nsubj
8	went	go	VBD	O	5	advcl
9	ahead	ahead	RB	O	8	advmod
10	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
11	got	get	VBD	O	8	conj
12	social	social	JJ	O	13	amod
13	services	service	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	take	take	VB	O	11	advcl
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	look	look	NN	O	15	dobj
18	at	at	IN	O	20	case
19	terrys	terry	NNS	O	20	compound
20	case	case	NN	O	15	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
22	see	see	VB	O	15	conj
23	if	if	IN	O	43	mark
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	promises	promise	NNS	O	43	nsubj
26	that	that	WDT	O	28	nsubjpass
27	were	be	VBD	O	28	auxpass
28	made	make	VBN	O	25	acl:relcl
29	dureing	duree	VBG	O	28	xcomp
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	lawsuit	lawsuit	NN	O	29	dobj
32	that	that	IN	O	40	mark
33	her	she	PRP$	O	34	nmod:poss
34	husband	husband	NN	O	40	nsubj
35	won	win	VBN	O	34	acl
36	by	by	IN	O	37	mark
37	saying	say	VBG	O	35	advcl
38	he	he	PRP	O	37	dobj
39	would	would	MD	O	40	aux
40	make	make	VB	O	29	ccomp
41	sure	sure	JJ	O	42	amod
42	terry	terry	NN	O	40	dobj
43	got	get	VBD	O	22	advcl
44	rehab	rehab	NN	O	43	dobj
45	,	,	,	O	44	punct
46	which	which	WDT	O	50	dobj
47	as	as	IN	O	48	case
48	we	we	PRP	O	50	nmod
49	all	all	DT	O	50	nsubj
50	know	know	VBP	O	44	acl:relcl
51	she	she	PRP	O	52	nsubj
52	did	do	VBD	O	50	ccomp
53	not	not	RB	O	52	neg
54	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Also	also	RB	O	2	advmod
2	got	get	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	message	message	NN	O	2	nsubj
5	loud	loud	JJ	O	4	amod
6	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
7	clear	clear	JJ	O	5	conj
8	that	that	IN	O	12	mark
9	you	you	PRP	O	12	nsubjpass
10	were	be	VBD	O	12	auxpass
11	not	not	RB	O	12	neg
12	satisfied	satisfy	VBN	O	2	dep
13	with	with	IN	O	16	case
14	this	this	DT	O	16	det
15	increase	increase	NN	O	16	compound
16	:-RRB-	:-rrb-	NN	O	12	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	People	people	NNS	O	7	nsubj
2	from	from	IN	O	3	case
3	all	all	DT	O	1	nmod
4	over	over	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	state	state	NN	O	3	nmod
7	enjoy	enjoy	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	canoing	cano	VBG	O	7	xcomp
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	rafting	raft	VBG	O	8	conj
11	on	on	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	Ichetucknee	Ichetucknee	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	was	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	largely	largely	RB	O	2	advmod
4	ho	ho	SYM	O	6	dep
5	-	-	:	O	6	punct
6	hum	hum	NN	O	2	dep
7	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	interim	interim	JJ	O	3	amod
3	Manager	Manager	NNP	O	10	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	Bill	Bill	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Moore	Moore	NNP	PERSON	3	appos
7	,	,	,	O	3	punct
8	has	have	VBZ	O	10	aux
9	since	since	IN	O	10	advmod
10	informed	inform	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	Me	I	PRP	O	10	dobj
12	that	that	IN	O	25	mark
13	NO	no	NN	O	14	compound
14	investigation	investigation	NN	O	25	nsubj
15	into	into	IN	O	18	case
16	the	the	DT	O	18	det
17	voting	voting	NN	O	18	compound
18	irregularities	irregularity	NNS	O	14	nmod
19	of	of	IN	O	21	case
20	JOHN	JOHN	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
21	CUMMINGS	CUMMINGS	NNP	PERSON	18	nmod
22	will	will	MD	O	25	aux
23	be	be	VB	O	25	cop
24	forthcoming	forthcoming	JJ	O	25	amod
25	due	due	JJ	O	10	ccomp
26	to	to	TO	O	28	case
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	fact	fact	NN	O	25	nmod
29	that	that	IN	O	40	mark
30	,	,	,	O	40	punct
31	as	as	IN	O	34	mark
32	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	33	compound
33	Moore	Moore	NNP	PERSON	34	nsubj
34	stated	state	VBD	O	40	advcl
35	,	,	,	O	40	punct
36	Richard	Richard	NNP	PERSON	37	compound
37	Crotty	Crotty	NNP	PERSON	40	nsubj
38	will	will	MD	O	40	aux
39	not	not	RB	O	40	neg
40	permit	permit	VB	O	25	ccomp
41	any	any	DT	O	42	det
42	investigation	investigation	NN	O	40	dobj
43	into	into	IN	O	45	case
44	this	this	DT	O	45	det
45	matter	matter	NN	O	40	nmod
46	to	to	TO	O	47	mark
47	avoid	avoid	VB	O	45	acl
48	the	the	DT	O	49	det
49	embarrassment	embarrassment	NN	O	47	dobj
50	it	it	PRP	O	52	nsubj
51	would	would	MD	O	52	aux
52	cause	cause	VB	O	49	acl:relcl
53	to	to	TO	O	56	case
54	Orange	Orange	NNP	ORGANIZATION	56	compound
55	County	County	NNP	ORGANIZATION	56	compound
56	Government	Government	NNP	ORGANIZATION	52	nmod
57	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Windows	Windows	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Me/XP	Me/XP	NNP	O	3	nsubj
3	uses	use	VBZ	O	23	dep
4	this	this	DT	O	5	det
5	feature	feature	NN	O	3	dobj
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	which	which	WDT	O	9	nsubjpass
8	is	be	VBZ	O	9	auxpass
9	enabled	enable	VBN	O	5	acl:relcl
10	by	by	IN	O	11	case
11	default	default	NN	O	9	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	5	punct
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	restore	restore	VB	O	3	xcomp
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	files	file	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	on	on	IN	O	19	case
18	your	you	PRP$	O	19	nmod:poss
19	computer	computer	NN	O	14	nmod
20	in	in	IN	O	21	case
21	case	case	NN	O	19	nmod
22	they	they	PRP	O	23	nsubj
23	become	become	VBP	O	0	ROOT
24	damaged	damage	VBN	O	23	xcomp
25	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	About	about	IN	O	2	case
2	DS	ds	NN	O	7	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	7	punct
4	it	it	PRP	O	7	nsubj
5	was	be	VBD	O	7	cop
6	very	very	RB	O	7	advmod
7	frustrating	frustrating	JJ	O	0	ROOT
8	for	for	IN	O	9	case
9	me	I	PRP	O	7	nmod
10	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
11	be	be	VB	O	17	cop
12	at	at	IN	O	17	case
13	Judge	Judge	NNP	O	14	compound
14	Ferguson	Ferguson	NNP	PERSON	17	nmod:poss
15	's	's	POS	O	14	case
16	court	court	NN	O	17	compound
17	room	room	NN	O	7	xcomp
18	last	last	JJ	DATE	19	amod
19	week	week	NN	DATE	7	nmod:tmod
20	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Your	you	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	note	note	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	made	make	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	big	big	JJ	O	6	amod
6	impression	impression	NN	O	3	dobj
7	at	at	IN	O	10	case
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	critical	critical	JJ	O	10	amod
10	time	time	NN	O	3	nmod
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	his	he	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	life	life	NN	O	3	nmod
14	--	--	:	O	3	punct
15	thank	thank	VB	O	3	parataxis
16	you	you	PRP	O	15	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	have	have	VBP	O	4	aux
3	already	already	RB	O	4	advmod
4	lost	lose	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	13	13	CD	MONEY	6	nummod
6	pounds	pound	NNS	MONEY	4	dobj
7	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
8	gone	go	VBN	O	4	conj
9	down	down	RB	O	8	compound:prt
10	2	2	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
11	belt	belt	NN	O	12	compound
12	notches	notch	NNS	O	8	dobj
13	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	is	be	VBZ	O	13	advcl
3	one	one	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
4	more	more	JJR	O	5	dep
5	possible	possible	JJ	O	6	amod
6	thing	thing	NN	O	2	nsubj
7	that	that	WDT	O	10	dep
8	Ginger	Ginger	NNP	O	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	papers	papers	NNS	O	6	acl:relcl
11	MIGHT	MIGHT	NNP	O	13	nsubj
12	have	have	VBP	O	13	aux
13	been	be	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	:	:	:	O	13	punct

1	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
2	would	would	MD	O	3	aux
3	like	like	VB	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	vote	vote	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	for	for	IN	O	10	case
7	Jack	Jack	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Luedke	Luedke	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	coin	coin	NN	O	5	nmod
11	from	from	IN	O	12	case
12	Jacksonville	Jacksonville	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	World	World	NNP	O	9	nsubj
2	famous	famous	JJ	O	1	amod
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	charm	charm	NN	O	2	dep
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	river	river	NN	O	5	nmod
9	captures	capture	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
10	poets	poet	NNS	O	9	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	divers	diver	NNS	O	10	appos
13	,	,	,	O	10	punct
14	swimmers	swimmer	NNS	O	10	appos
15	,	,	,	O	10	punct
16	tubers	tuber	NNS	O	10	appos
17	,	,	,	O	10	punct
18	families	family	NNS	O	10	appos
19	,	,	,	O	10	punct
20	biologists	biologist	NNS	O	10	appos
21	,	,	,	O	10	punct
22	artists	artist	NNS	O	10	appos
23	,	,	,	O	10	punct
24	photographers	photographer	NNS	O	10	appos
25	...	...	:	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	proposed	propose	VBN	O	3	amod
3	reserve	reserve	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
5	protect	protect	VB	O	0	ROOT
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	wide	wide	JJ	O	8	amod
8	range	range	NN	O	5	dobj
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	habitats	habitat	NNS	O	8	nmod
11	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	14	punct
12	including	include	VBG	O	14	case
13	seagrass	seagrass	NN	O	14	compound
14	beds	bed	NNS	O	10	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	14	punct
16	coral	coral	NN	O	17	compound
17	reefs	reef	NNS	O	14	appos
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	pinnacles	pinnacle	NNS	O	17	conj
20	,	,	,	O	17	punct
21	spawning	spawn	VBG	O	22	amod
22	grounds	grounds	NNS	O	17	conj
23	,	,	,	O	17	punct
24	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
25	hardbottoms	hardbottom	NNS	O	17	conj
26	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	14	punct
27	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
28	will	will	MD	O	29	aux
29	conserve	conserve	VB	O	5	conj
30	areas	area	NNS	O	29	dobj
31	of	of	IN	O	33	case
32	highest	highest	JJS	O	33	amod
33	biodiversity	biodiversity	NN	O	30	nmod
34	,	,	,	O	29	punct
35	thereby	thereby	RB	O	36	advmod
36	meeting	meet	VBG	O	29	advcl
37	important	important	JJ	O	39	amod
38	environmental	environmental	JJ	O	39	amod
39	goals	goal	NNS	O	36	dobj
40	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	As	as	IN	O	3	mark
2	we	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	start	start	VBP	O	13	advcl
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	implement	implement	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	the	the	DT	O	10	det
7	new	new	JJ	O	10	amod
8	federal	federal	JJ	O	10	amod
9	reform	reform	NN	O	10	compound
10	legislation	legislation	NN	O	5	dobj
11	it	it	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	is	be	VBZ	O	13	aux
13	going	go	VBG	O	0	ROOT
14	to	to	TO	O	16	mark
15	be	be	VB	O	16	cop
16	imperative	imperative	JJ	O	13	xcomp
17	that	that	IN	O	20	mark
18	we	we	PRP	O	20	nsubj
19	again	again	RB	O	20	advmod
20	spend	spend	VBP	O	16	ccomp
21	the	the	DT	O	22	det
22	money	money	NN	O	20	dobj
23	it	it	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	takes	take	VBZ	O	22	acl:relcl
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	educate	educate	VB	O	24	xcomp
27	voters	voter	NNS	O	26	dobj
28	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Tom	Tom	NNP	PERSON	7	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	state	state	NN	O	1	appos
5	is	be	VBZ	O	7	aux
6	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
7	mandating	mandate	VBG	O	0	ROOT
8	how	how	WRB	O	10	advmod
9	kids	kid	NNS	O	10	nsubj
10	learn	learn	VBP	O	7	ccomp
11	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	My	my	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
2	best	best	JJS	O	3	amod
3	wishes	wish	NNS	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	6	case
5	your	you	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	family	family	NN	O	3	nmod
7	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Governor	governor	NN	O	4	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	Katie	Katie	NNP	PERSON	1	appos
4	asked	ask	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	me	I	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	update	update	VB	O	4	xcomp
8	you	you	PRP	O	7	dobj
9	on	on	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	latest	latest	JJS	O	12	amod
12	statistics	statistics	NNS	O	7	nmod
13	on	on	IN	O	17	case
14	state	state	NN	O	17	compound
15	employee	employee	NN	O	17	compound
16	reemployment	reemployment	NN	O	17	compound
17	efforts	effort	NNS	O	12	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct
