1	Despite	despite	IN	O	3	case
2	his	he	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	infirmities	infirmity	NNS	O	8	nmod
4	,	,	,	O	8	punct
5	Chaudhry	Chaudhry	NNP	PERSON	8	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	8	aux
7	not	not	RB	O	8	neg
8	leaving	leave	VBG	O	0	ROOT
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	country	country	NN	O	8	dobj
11	without	without	IN	O	13	case
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	fight	fight	NN	O	8	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Ms	Ms	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Hands	Hands	NNPS	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	aux
4	moving	move	VBG	O	0	ROOT
5	out	out	RB	O	4	compound:prt
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	frontline	frontline	NN	O	4	nmod
9	to	to	TO	O	14	case
10	a	a	DT	O	14	det
11	new	new	JJ	O	14	amod
12	combined	combined	JJ	O	14	amod
13	Downing	Downing	NNP	ORGANIZATION	14	compound
14	Street	Street	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
15	and	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	14	cc
16	Foreign	Foreign	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
17	Office	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
18	role	role	NN	O	14	conj
19	on	on	IN	O	20	case
20	Afghanistan	Afghanistan	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Trenberth	Trenberth	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	there	there	EX	O	4	expl
4	's	be	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
5	little	little	JJ	O	6	amod
6	doubt	doubt	NN	O	4	nsubj
7	in	in	IN	O	9	case
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	mind	mind	NN	O	6	nmod
10	that	that	IN	O	15	mark
11	a	a	DT	O	13	det
12	warming	warming	NN	O	13	compound
13	climate	climate	NN	O	15	nsubj
14	is	be	VBZ	O	15	aux
15	making	make	VBG	O	4	ccomp
16	storms	storm	NNS	O	18	nsubj
17	more	more	RBR	O	18	advmod
18	hazardous	hazardous	JJ	O	15	xcomp
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	5	dep
2	that	that	IN	O	5	mark
3	he	he	PRP	O	5	nsubjpass
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	auxpass
5	bothered	bother	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	elderly	elderly	JJ	O	9	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	by	by	IN	O	5	case
5	contrast	contrast	NN	O	2	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	2	punct
7	have	have	VBP	O	9	aux
8	not	not	RB	O	9	neg
9	suffered	suffer	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	as	as	IN	O	11	case
11	badly	badly	RB	O	9	advcl
12	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	``	``	``	O	13	punct
2	That	that	DT	O	3	nsubj
3	's	be	VBZ	O	13	ccomp
4	what	what	WP	O	7	dobj
5	we	we	PRP	O	7	nsubj
6	're	be	VBP	O	7	aux
7	stressing	stress	VBG	O	3	ccomp
8	right	right	RB	DATE	9	advmod
9	now	now	RB	DATE	7	advmod
10	,	,	,	O	13	punct
11	''	''	''	O	13	punct
12	Pierce	Pierce	NNP	PERSON	13	nsubj
13	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
14	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	trees	tree	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	provide	provide	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	a	a	DT	O	6	det
5	startling	startling	JJ	O	6	amod
6	counterpoint	counterpoint	NN	O	3	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	8	case
8	color	color	NN	O	6	nmod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	contour	contour	NN	O	8	conj
11	to	to	TO	O	14	case
12	the	the	DT	O	14	det
13	uniformly	uniformly	RB	O	14	amod
14	tan	tan	NN	O	3	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	rectilinear	rectilinear	JJ	O	17	amod
17	houses	house	NNS	O	14	conj
18	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
19	walls	wall	NNS	O	17	conj
20	surrounding	surround	VBG	O	17	acl
21	them	they	PRP	O	20	dobj
22	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Last	last	JJ	DATE	2	amod
2	Sunday	Sunday	NNP	DATE	10	nmod:tmod
3	it	it	PRP	O	10	nsubj
4	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
5	well	well	RB	O	6	advmod
6	down	down	RB	O	10	advmod
7	on	on	IN	O	10	case
8	its	its	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
9	2009	2009	CD	DATE	10	nummod
10	peak	peak	NN	O	0	ROOT
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	with	with	IN	O	14	case
13	just	just	RB	O	14	advmod
14	852,000	852,000	CD	NUMBER	10	nmod
15	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Members	member	NNS	O	6	nsubj
2	of	of	IN	O	5	case
3	Micheletti	Micheletti	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
4	's	's	POS	O	3	case
5	team	team	NN	O	1	nmod
6	confirmed	confirm	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
8	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
9	was	be	VBD	O	11	cop
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	threat	threat	NN	O	6	ccomp
12	to	to	TO	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	legitimacy	legitimacy	NN	O	11	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	elections	election	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	that	that	WDT	O	20	nsubj
19	ultimately	ultimately	RB	O	20	advmod
20	persuaded	persuade	VBD	O	17	acl:relcl
21	the	the	DT	O	24	det
22	de	de	FW	O	24	amod
23	facto	facto	FW	O	22	dep
24	leader	leader	NN	O	20	dobj
25	to	to	TO	O	26	mark
26	agree	agree	VB	O	20	xcomp
27	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	``	``	``	O	20	punct
2	Please	please	VB	O	3	discourse
3	go	go	VB	O	17	csubj
4	to	to	TO	O	5	case
5	Tibet	Tibet	NNP	LOCATION	3	nmod
6	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
7	see	see	VB	O	3	conj
8	if	if	IN	O	12	mark
9	things	thing	NNS	O	12	nsubj
10	are	be	VBP	O	12	cop
11	really	really	RB	O	12	advmod
12	good	good	JJ	O	7	advcl
13	as	as	IN	O	16	case
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	Chinese	chinese	JJ	MISC	16	amod
16	government	government	NN	O	12	nmod
17	says	say	VBZ	O	20	ccomp
18	,	,	,	O	20	punct
19	''	''	''	O	20	punct
20	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
21	the	the	DT	O	24	det
22	Tibetan	Tibetan	NNP	MISC	24	compound
23	spiritual	spiritual	JJ	O	24	amod
24	leader	leader	NN	O	20	dep
25	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	government	government	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	6	cop
4	at	at	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	centre	centre	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	furious	furious	JJ	O	10	amod
10	backlash	backlash	NN	O	6	nmod
11	from	from	IN	O	12	mark
12	leading	lead	VBG	O	6	advcl
13	scientists	scientist	NNS	O	12	dobj
14	last	last	JJ	TIME	15	amod
15	night	night	NN	TIME	12	nmod:tmod
16	following	follow	VBG	O	17	case
17	its	its	PRP$	O	12	nmod
18	sacking	sack	VBG	O	17	acl
19	of	of	IN	O	24	case
20	Britain	Britain	NNP	LOCATION	24	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	top	top	JJ	O	24	amod
23	drugs	drug	NNS	O	24	compound
24	adviser	adviser	NN	O	18	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	Mail	Mail	NNP	O	5	nsubj
3	on	on	IN	O	4	case
4	Sunday	Sunday	NNP	DATE	2	nmod
5	spoke	speak	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	to	to	TO	O	7	case
7	colleagues	colleague	NNS	O	5	nmod
8	last	last	JJ	TIME	9	amod
9	night	night	NN	TIME	5	nmod:tmod
10	who	who	WP	O	11	nsubj
11	confirmed	confirm	VBD	O	5	ccomp
12	Home	Home	NNP	O	15	compound
13	Secretary	Secretary	NNP	O	15	compound
14	Alan	Alan	NNP	PERSON	15	compound
15	Johnson	Johnson	NNP	PERSON	25	nsubj
16	,	,	,	O	15	punct
17	who	who	WP	O	18	nsubj
18	dismissed	dismiss	VBD	O	15	acl:relcl
19	Prof	Prof	NNP	PERSON	20	compound
20	Nutt	Nutt	NNP	PERSON	18	dobj
21	by	by	IN	O	22	case
22	email	email	NN	O	18	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	15	punct
24	was	be	VBD	O	25	aux
25	facing	face	VBG	O	11	ccomp
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	prospect	prospect	NN	O	25	dobj
28	of	of	IN	O	30	case
29	mass	mass	NN	O	30	compound
30	resignations	resignation	NNS	O	27	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	whole	whole	JJ	O	3	amod
3	project	project	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	has	have	VBZ	O	5	aux
5	attracted	attract	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	criticism	criticism	NN	O	5	dobj
7	from	from	IN	O	9	case
8	left-wing	left-wing	JJ	O	9	amod
9	lawmakers	lawmaker	NNS	O	5	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	erstwhile	erstwhile	JJ	O	12	amod
12	members	member	NNS	O	9	conj
13	of	of	IN	O	18	case
14	the	the	DT	O	18	det
15	East	east	JJ	O	16	amod
16	German	german	JJ	O	18	amod
17	Communist	Communist	NNP	ORGANIZATION	18	compound
18	Party	Party	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	who	who	WP	O	21	nsubj
21	argue	argue	VBP	O	18	acl:relcl
22	it	it	PRP	O	25	nsubj
23	is	be	VBZ	O	25	cop
24	a	a	DT	O	25	det
25	waste	waste	NN	O	21	ccomp
26	of	of	IN	O	27	case
27	money	money	NN	O	25	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Although	although	IN	O	7	mark
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	Chinese	chinese	JJ	MISC	4	amod
4	government	government	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	7	aux
6	not	not	RB	O	7	neg
7	taken	take	VBN	O	28	advcl
8	action	action	NN	O	7	dobj
9	against	against	IN	O	10	case
10	Yuan	Yuan	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
11	or	or	CC	O	8	cc
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	publisher	publisher	NN	O	8	conj
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	nongovernmental	nongovernmental	JJ	O	17	amod
17	organization	organization	NN	O	13	appos
18	,	,	,	O	28	punct
19	the	the	DT	O	21	det
20	Chinese	chinese	JJ	ORGANIZATION	21	amod
21	Assn.	assn.	NN	ORGANIZATION	28	nsubj
22	for	for	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	Promotion	Promotion	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	nmod
25	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	27	case
26	Olympic	Olympic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	27	compound
27	Culture	Culture	NNP	ORGANIZATION	24	nmod
28	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
29	last	last	JJ	DATE	30	amod
30	week	week	NN	DATE	28	nmod:tmod
31	it	it	PRP	O	33	nsubj
32	would	would	MD	O	33	aux
33	file	file	VB	O	28	ccomp
34	a	a	DT	O	36	det
35	civil	civil	JJ	O	36	amod
36	lawsuit	lawsuit	NN	O	33	dobj
37	against	against	IN	O	40	case
38	Yuan	Yuan	NNP	PERSON	40	nmod:poss
39	's	's	POS	O	38	case
40	publisher	publisher	NN	O	33	nmod
41	,	,	,	O	40	punct
42	Beijing	Beijing	NNP	ORGANIZATION	45	compound
43	Fonghong	Fonghong	NNP	ORGANIZATION	45	compound
44	Media	Media	NNP	ORGANIZATION	45	compound
45	Co.	Co.	NNP	ORGANIZATION	40	appos
46	,	,	,	O	28	punct
47	to	to	TO	O	48	mark
48	prevent	prevent	VB	O	28	xcomp
49	publication	publication	NN	O	48	dobj
50	of	of	IN	O	52	case
51	any	any	DT	O	52	det
52	copies	copy	NNS	O	49	nmod
53	beyond	beyond	IN	O	55	case
54	the	the	DT	O	55	det
55	200,000	200,000	CD	NUMBER	48	nmod
56	in	in	IN	O	57	case
57	print	print	NN	O	48	nmod
58	in	in	IN	O	59	case
59	China	China	NNP	LOCATION	57	nmod
60	.	.	.	O	28	punct

1	Police	police	NNS	O	3	nsubj
2	have	have	VBP	O	3	aux
3	asked	ask	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	anyone	anyone	NN	O	3	dobj
5	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
6	fears	fear	VBZ	O	4	acl:relcl
7	they	they	PRP	O	10	nsubjpass
8	may	may	MD	O	10	aux
9	be	be	VB	O	10	auxpass
10	related	relate	VBN	O	6	ccomp
11	to	to	TO	O	12	case
12	one	one	CD	NUMBER	10	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	15	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	victims	victim	NNS	O	12	nmod
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	come	come	VB	O	10	xcomp
18	forward	forward	RB	O	17	advmod
19	with	with	IN	O	21	case
20	DNA	dna	NN	O	21	compound
21	samples	sample	NNS	O	17	nmod
22	so	so	IN	O	27	mark
23	that	that	IN	O	22	mwe
24	they	they	PRP	O	27	nsubj
25	can	can	MD	O	27	aux
26	eventually	eventually	RB	O	27	advmod
27	help	help	VB	O	17	advcl
28	with	with	IN	O	29	case
29	identification	identification	NN	O	27	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Tate	Tate	NNP	PERSON	5	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	Hail	Hail	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
4	Mary	Mary	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	haul	haul	NN	O	10	nsubj
6	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
7	his	he	PRP$	O	10	nmod:poss
8	second	second	JJ	ORDINAL	10	amod
9	sensational	sensational	JJ	O	10	amod
10	score	score	NN	NUMBER	0	ROOT
11	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Purchasing	Purchasing	NNP	MISC	3	compound
3	Managers	manager	NNS	MISC	5	nmod:poss
4	'	'	POS	MISC	3	case
5	Index	index	NN	MISC	6	nsubj
6	rose	rise	VBD	O	25	ccomp
7	to	to	TO	O	11	case
8	a	a	DT	O	11	det
9	seasonally	seasonally	RB	O	10	advmod
10	adjusted	adjust	VBN	O	11	amod
11	55.2	55.2	CD	NUMBER	6	nmod
12	in	in	IN	O	13	case
13	October	October	NNP	DATE	6	nmod
14	from	from	IN	O	15	case
15	54.3	54.3	CD	NUMBER	6	nmod
16	in	in	IN	O	17	case
17	September	September	NNP	DATE	6	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	25	punct
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	Federation	Federation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	nsubj
21	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	22	case
22	Logistics	Logistics	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	nmod
23	and	and	CC	ORGANIZATION	22	cc
24	Purchasing	Purchasing	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	conj
25	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
26	today	today	NN	DATE	25	nmod:tmod
27	in	in	IN	O	28	case
28	an	a	DT	O	25	nmod
29	e-mailed	e-mail	VBN	O	28	acl
30	statement	statement	NN	O	29	dobj
31	in	in	IN	O	32	case
32	Beijing	Beijing	NNP	LOCATION	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	25	punct

1	There	there	EX	O	2	expl
2	are	be	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	five	five	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
4	contested	contest	VBN	O	6	amod
5	council	council	NN	O	6	compound
6	seats	seat	NNS	O	2	nsubj
7	with	with	IN	O	9	case
8	no	no	DT	O	9	neg
9	incumbent	incumbent	JJ	O	6	nmod
10	this	this	DT	DATE	11	det
11	year	year	NN	DATE	9	dep
12	-	-	:	O	9	punct
13	two	two	CD	NUMBER	15	nummod
14	at-large	at-large	JJ	O	15	amod
15	seats	seat	NNS	O	9	dep
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	geographical	geographical	JJ	O	18	amod
18	Districts	Districts	NNPS	O	15	conj
19	A	A	NNP	O	18	appos
20	,	,	,	O	9	punct
21	F	f	NN	O	9	conj
22	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
23	G.	G.	NNP	O	9	conj

1	Twice	twice	RB	O	4	advmod
2	they	they	PRP	O	4	nsubjpass
3	were	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	struck	strike	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	by	by	IN	O	7	case
6	bono	bono	FW	O	7	compound
7	waves	wave	NNS	O	4	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	4	punct
9	which	which	WDT	O	10	nsubj
10	upended	upend	VBD	O	4	ccomp
11	their	they	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	boat	boat	NN	O	10	dobj
13	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
14	swallowed	swallow	VBD	O	10	conj
15	their	they	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
16	belongings	belongings	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	``	``	``	O	21	punct
2	You	you	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
4	n't	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	ask	ask	VB	O	21	ccomp
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	baker	baker	NN	O	5	dobj
8	what	what	WDT	O	10	dep
9	drives	drive	NNS	O	10	dep
10	him	he	PRP	O	7	acl:relcl
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	get	get	VB	O	5	xcomp
13	up	up	RB	O	12	advmod
14	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
15	bake	bake	VB	O	12	conj
16	his	he	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	bread	bread	NN	O	15	dobj
18	,	,	,	O	21	punct
19	''	''	''	O	21	punct
20	she	she	PRP	O	21	nsubj
21	says	say	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
22	.	.	.	O	21	punct

1	Message	message	NN	O	12	nsubj
2	in	in	IN	O	4	case
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	battle	battle	NN	O	1	nmod
5	:	:	:	O	4	punct
6	Gov.	Gov.	NNP	O	8	compound
7	Arnold	Arnold	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Schwarzenegger	Schwarzenegger	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	people	people	NNS	O	4	dep
11	are	be	VBP	O	12	aux
12	sticking	stick	VBG	O	0	ROOT
13	to	to	TO	O	15	case
14	their	they	PRP$	O	15	nmod:poss
15	story	story	NN	O	12	nmod
16	about	about	IN	O	23	mark
17	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
18	veto	veto	NN	O	19	compound
19	message	message	NN	O	23	nsubj
20	for	for	IN	O	22	case
21	a	a	DT	O	22	det
22	bill	bill	NN	O	19	nmod
23	sponsored	sponsor	VBN	O	12	advcl
24	by	by	IN	O	28	case
25	state	state	NN	O	28	compound
26	Assemblyman	Assemblyman	NNP	O	28	compound
27	Tom	Tom	NNP	PERSON	28	compound
28	Ammiano	Ammiano	NNP	PERSON	23	nmod
29	,	,	,	O	28	punct
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	one	one	CD	NUMBER	28	appos
32	with	with	IN	O	35	case
33	a	a	DT	O	35	det
34	word	word	NN	O	35	compound
35	puzzle	puzzle	NN	O	31	nmod
36	that	that	WDT	O	37	nsubj
37	spelled	spell	VBD	O	31	acl:relcl
38	out	out	RP	O	37	compound:prt
39	``	``	``	O	40	punct
40	F	f	NN	O	37	dobj
41	-	-	:	O	40	punct
42	you	you	PRP	O	40	dep
43	.	.	.	O	12	punct
44	''	''	''	O	12	punct

1	Not	not	RB	O	4	dep
2	sure	sure	JJ	O	1	dep
3	she	she	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	knows	know	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	her	she	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	way	way	NN	O	4	dobj
7	around	around	IN	O	9	case
8	an	a	DT	O	9	det
9	engine	engine	NN	O	4	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	4	punct
11	but	but	CC	O	4	cc
12	King	King	NNP	O	26	nsubj
13	-	-	:	O	12	punct
14	who	who	WP	O	17	nsubj
15	most	most	RBS	O	16	advmod
16	recently	recently	RB	DATE	17	advmod
17	ran	run	VBD	O	12	acl:relcl
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	bus	bus	NN	O	20	compound
20	system	system	NN	O	23	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	PR	pr	NN	O	23	compound
23	division	division	NN	O	17	dobj
24	-	-	:	O	12	punct
25	sure	sure	JJ	O	26	advmod
26	knows	know	VBZ	O	4	conj
27	the	the	DT	O	29	det
28	political	political	JJ	O	29	amod
29	byways	byway	NNS	O	26	dobj
30	of	of	IN	O	33	case
31	the	the	DT	O	33	det
32	East	East	NNP	LOCATION	33	compound
33	Bay	Bay	NNP	LOCATION	29	nmod
34	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	When	when	WRB	O	7	advmod
2	sectarian	sectarian	JJ	O	3	amod
3	violence	violence	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	was	be	VBD	O	7	cop
5	at	at	IN	O	7	case
6	its	its	PRP$	O	7	nmod:poss
7	peak	peak	NN	O	10	advcl
8	,	,	,	O	10	punct
9	he	he	PRP	O	10	nsubj
10	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	people	people	NNS	O	17	nsubj
13	in	in	IN	O	14	case
14	Baghdad	Baghdad	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod
15	were	be	VBD	O	17	cop
16	not	not	RB	O	17	neg
17	interested	interested	JJ	O	10	parataxis
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	his	he	PRP$	O	20	nmod:poss
20	work	work	NN	O	17	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	10	punct
22	so	so	RB	O	10	advmod
23	he	he	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	left	leave	VBD	O	10	parataxis
25	for	for	IN	O	26	case
26	Dubai	Dubai	NNP	LOCATION	24	nmod
27	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
28	the	the	DT	O	30	det
29	northern	northern	JJ	O	30	amod
30	city	city	NN	O	26	conj
31	of	of	IN	O	32	case
32	Erbil	Erbil	NNP	LOCATION	30	nmod
33	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	Concerns	concern	NNS	O	4	nsubjpass
2	have	have	VBP	O	4	aux
3	been	be	VBN	O	4	auxpass
4	raised	raise	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	about	about	IN	O	8	case
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	possible	possible	JJ	O	8	amod
8	repetition	repetition	NN	O	4	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	15	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	ballot-box	ballot-box	JJ	O	12	amod
12	stuffing	stuffing	NN	O	15	compound
13	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
14	distorted	distorted	JJ	O	12	conj
15	tallies	tally	NNS	O	8	nmod
16	in	in	IN	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	second	second	JJ	ORDINAL	19	amod
19	round	round	NN	O	4	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	came	come	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	off	off	RP	O	2	compound:prt
4	like	like	IN	O	7	case
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	generational	generational	JJ	O	7	amod
7	anthem	anthem	NN	O	2	nmod
8	:	:	:	O	2	punct

1	``	``	``	O	17	punct
2	It	it	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	4	cop
4	important	important	JJ	O	17	ccomp
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	have	have	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	an	a	DT	O	11	det
8	honest	honest	JJ	O	11	amod
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	open	open	JJ	O	8	conj
11	debate	debate	NN	O	6	dobj
12	about	about	IN	O	13	case
13	drugs	drug	NNS	O	11	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	17	punct
15	''	''	''	O	17	punct
16	Vaz	Vaz	NNP	PERSON	17	nsubj
17	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
18	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	``	``	``	O	6	punct
2	We	we	PRP	O	6	nsubj
3	do	do	VBP	O	6	aux
4	n't	not	RB	O	6	neg
5	ever	ever	RB	O	6	advmod
6	want	want	VB	O	0	ROOT
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	suspend	suspend	VB	O	6	xcomp
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	case	case	NN	O	8	dobj
11	prematurely	prematurely	RB	O	10	dep
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	when	when	WRB	O	17	advmod
14	there	there	EX	O	17	expl
15	may	may	MD	O	17	aux
16	be	be	VB	O	17	cop
17	someone	someone	NN	O	11	dep
18	out	out	IN	O	19	case
19	there	there	RB	O	17	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	17	punct
21	...	...	:	O	11	punct
22	But	but	CC	O	24	cc
23	hope	hope	NN	O	24	nsubj
24	gets	get	VBZ	O	11	parataxis
25	less	less	JJR	O	24	dobj
26	every	every	DT	SET	27	det
27	day	day	NN	SET	25	dep
28	.	.	.	O	11	punct
29	My	my	PRP$	O	31	nmod:poss
30	hope	hope	NN	O	31	compound
31	today	today	NN	DATE	32	nsubj
32	is	be	VBZ	O	6	ccomp
33	not	not	RB	O	32	neg
34	what	what	WP	O	36	dobj
35	it	it	PRP	O	36	nsubj
36	was	be	VBD	O	32	ccomp
37	yesterday	yesterday	NN	DATE	36	nmod:tmod
38	.	.	.	O	6	punct
39	''	''	''	O	6	punct

1	She	she	PRP	O	6	nsubj
2	's	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
3	an	a	DT	O	6	det
4	old-school	old-school	JJ	O	6	amod
5	TV	tv	NN	O	6	compound
6	kid	kid	NN	O	0	ROOT
7	drawn	draw	VBN	O	6	acl
8	with	with	IN	O	10	case
9	new-school	new-school	JJ	O	10	amod
10	ambiguities	ambiguity	NNS	O	7	nmod
11	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	2	case
2	India	India	NNP	LOCATION	10	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	10	punct
4	the	the	DT	O	7	det
5	widening	widen	VBG	O	7	amod
6	Maoist	Maoist	NNP	MISC	7	compound
7	insurgency	insurgency	NN	O	10	nsubj
8	is	be	VBZ	O	10	cop
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	moment	moment	NN	O	0	ROOT
11	of	of	IN	O	12	mark
12	reckoning	reckon	VBG	O	10	acl
13	for	for	IN	O	17	case
14	the	the	DT	O	15	det
15	country	country	NN	O	17	nmod:poss
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	democracy	democracy	NN	O	12	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
19	has	have	VBZ	O	20	aux
20	ignited	ignite	VBN	O	10	conj
21	a	a	DT	O	23	det
22	sharp	sharp	JJ	O	23	amod
23	debate	debate	NN	O	20	dobj
24	about	about	IN	O	28	mark
25	where	where	WRB	O	28	advmod
26	it	it	PRP	O	28	nsubj
27	has	have	VBZ	O	28	aux
28	failed	fail	VBN	O	20	advcl
29	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	follows	follow	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	program	program	NN	O	7	nmod:poss
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	poor	poor	JJ	O	7	amod
7	returns	return	NNS	O	2	dobj
8	this	this	DT	DATE	9	det
9	year	year	NN	DATE	7	dep
10	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	``	``	``	O	32	punct
2	We	we	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	need	need	VBP	O	32	ccomp
4	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
5	be	be	VB	O	6	cop
6	careful	careful	JJ	O	3	xcomp
7	that	that	IN	O	11	mark
8	when	when	WRB	O	11	advmod
9	these	these	DT	O	10	det
10	split-ups	split-up	NNS	O	11	nsubj
11	occur	occur	VBP	O	6	ccomp
12	,	,	,	O	6	punct
13	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	prime	prime	JJ	O	16	amod
16	cuts	cut	NNS	O	19	nsubjpass
17	are	be	VBP	O	19	auxpass
18	not	not	RB	O	19	neg
19	offered	offer	VBN	O	6	ccomp
20	to	to	TO	O	22	case
21	private	private	JJ	O	22	amod
22	investors	investor	NNS	O	19	nmod
23	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	scraps	scrap	NNS	O	26	nsubj
26	left	leave	VBD	O	19	conj
27	to	to	TO	O	28	case
28	taxpayers	taxpayer	NNS	O	26	nmod
29	,	,	,	O	32	punct
30	''	''	''	O	32	punct
31	he	he	PRP	O	32	nsubj
32	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
33	.	.	.	O	32	punct

1	Olson	Olson	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	the	the	DT	O	5	det
4	State	State	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	7	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	7	aux
7	taking	take	VBG	O	2	ccomp
8	a	a	DT	O	10	det
9	new	new	JJ	O	10	amod
10	look	look	NN	O	7	dobj
11	at	at	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	case	case	NN	O	7	nmod
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	South	South	NNP	LOCATION	2	compound
2	Korea	Korea	NNP	LOCATION	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	exports	export	NNS	O	5	nsubj
5	fell	fall	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	less	less	JJR	O	5	dobj
7	than	than	IN	O	8	case
8	economists	economist	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	estimated	estimate	VBN	O	8	amod
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	October	October	NNP	DATE	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	8	punct
13	adding	add	VBG	O	8	acl
14	to	to	TO	O	15	case
15	signs	sign	NNS	O	13	nmod
16	that	that	IN	O	19	mark
17	trade	trade	NN	O	19	nsubj
18	may	may	MD	O	19	aux
19	start	start	VB	O	8	dep
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	rebound	rebind	VB	O	19	xcomp
22	from	from	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	slump	slump	NN	O	21	nmod
25	triggered	trigger	VBN	O	24	acl
26	by	by	IN	O	30	case
27	the	the	DT	O	30	det
28	global	global	JJ	O	30	amod
29	financial	financial	JJ	O	30	amod
30	crisis	crisis	NN	O	25	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	For	for	IN	O	2	case
2	watchdogs	watchdog	NNS	O	13	nmod
3	of	of	IN	O	7	case
4	the	the	DT	O	5	det
5	bay	bay	NN	O	7	nmod:poss
6	's	's	POS	O	5	case
7	ecosystem	ecosystem	NN	O	2	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
9	wildlife	wildlife	NN	O	7	conj
10	,	,	,	O	13	punct
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	incident	incident	NN	O	13	nsubj
13	brought	bring	VBN	O	0	ROOT
14	back	back	RB	O	13	compound:prt
15	memories	memory	NNS	O	13	dobj
16	of	of	IN	O	22	case
17	the	the	DT	O	22	det
18	disastrous	disastrous	JJ	O	22	amod
19	2007	2007	CD	DATE	18	nmod:tmod
20	Cosco	Cosco	NNP	O	22	compound
21	Busan	Busan	NNP	O	22	compound
22	incident	incident	NN	O	15	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	22	punct
24	which	which	WDT	O	25	nsubj
25	dumped	dump	VBD	O	22	acl:relcl
26	nearly	nearly	RB	O	27	advmod
27	60,000	60,000	CD	NUMBER	28	nummod
28	gallons	gallon	NNS	O	25	dobj
29	of	of	IN	O	31	case
30	bunker	bunker	NN	O	31	compound
31	fuel	fuel	NN	O	28	nmod
32	,	,	,	O	25	punct
33	killing	kill	VBG	O	25	dep
34	thousands	thousand	NNS	O	33	dobj
35	of	of	IN	O	36	case
36	birds	bird	NNS	O	34	nmod
37	and	and	CC	O	33	cc
38	fouling	foul	VBG	O	33	conj
39	sensitive	sensitive	JJ	O	40	amod
40	shorelines	shoreline	NNS	O	38	dobj
41	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Miliband	Miliband	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	departure	departure	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	for	for	IN	O	5	case
5	Europe	Europe	NNP	LOCATION	3	nmod
6	would	would	MD	O	7	aux
7	increase	increase	VB	O	0	ROOT
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	chances	chance	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	of	of	IN	O	11	case
11	one	one	CD	NUMBER	9	nmod
12	of	of	IN	O	18	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	prime	prime	JJ	O	15	amod
15	minister	minister	NN	O	18	nmod:poss
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	chosen	choose	VBN	O	18	amod
18	candidates	candidate	NNS	O	11	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	11	punct
20	Ed	Ed	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
21	Balls	Balls	NNP	PERSON	11	conj
22	or	or	CC	O	11	cc
23	Ed	Ed	NNP	PERSON	24	compound
24	Miliband	Miliband	NNP	PERSON	11	conj
25	,	,	,	O	24	punct
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	28	amod
28	secretary	secretary	NN	O	30	nmod:poss
29	's	's	POS	O	28	case
30	brother	brother	NN	O	24	appos
31	,	,	,	O	24	punct
32	winning	win	VBG	O	24	acl
33	a	a	DT	O	35	det
34	leadership	leadership	NN	O	35	compound
35	contest	contest	NN	O	32	dobj
36	if	if	IN	O	39	mark
37	Labour	labour	NN	ORGANIZATION	39	nsubjpass
38	is	be	VBZ	O	39	auxpass
39	defeated	defeat	VBN	O	32	advcl
40	at	at	IN	O	43	case
41	the	the	DT	O	43	det
42	general	general	JJ	O	43	amod
43	election	election	NN	O	39	nmod
44	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Take	take	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	poverty-driven	poverty-driven	JJ	O	4	amod
4	frustration	frustration	NN	O	1	dobj
5	of	of	IN	O	7	case
6	inner-city	inner-city	JJ	O	7	amod
7	Richmond	Richmond	NNP	LOCATION	4	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	4	punct
9	a	a	DT	O	12	det
10	youth	youth	NN	O	12	compound
11	street	street	NN	O	12	compound
12	culture	culture	NN	O	4	appos
13	that	that	WDT	O	14	nsubj
14	glorifies	glorify	VBZ	O	12	acl:relcl
15	thugs	thug	NNS	O	14	dobj
16	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
17	applauds	applaud	VBZ	O	14	conj
18	degradation	degradation	NN	O	17	dobj
19	of	of	IN	O	20	case
20	women	woman	NNS	O	18	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	18	punct
22	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	desensitization	desensitization	NN	O	18	conj
25	of	of	IN	O	27	case
26	young	young	JJ	O	27	amod
27	men	man	NNS	O	24	nmod
28	through	through	IN	O	31	case
29	violent	violent	JJ	O	31	amod
30	video	video	NN	O	31	compound
31	games	game	NNS	O	17	nmod
32	,	,	,	O	31	punct
33	music	music	NN	O	31	conj
34	and	and	CC	O	31	cc
35	language	language	NN	O	31	conj
36	,	,	,	O	1	punct
37	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
38	you	you	PRP	O	39	nsubj
39	have	have	VBP	O	1	conj
40	a	a	DT	O	41	det
41	template	template	NN	O	39	dobj
42	for	for	IN	O	43	case
43	trouble	trouble	NN	O	41	nmod
44	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	4	det
2	Downing	Downing	NNP	LOCATION	4	compound
3	Street	Street	NNP	LOCATION	4	compound
4	staffer	staffer	NN	O	5	nsubj
5	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	:	:	:	O	5	punct
7	``	``	``	O	5	punct
8	This	this	DT	O	11	nsubjpass
9	is	be	VBZ	O	11	aux
10	being	be	VBG	O	11	auxpass
11	taken	take	VBN	O	5	ccomp
12	very	very	RB	O	13	advmod
13	seriously	seriously	RB	O	16	dep
14	.	.	.	O	13	punct
15	Diplomatic	diplomatic	JJ	O	16	amod
16	channels	channel	NNS	O	22	dep
17	in	in	IN	O	20	case
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	Foreign	Foreign	NNP	ORGANIZATION	20	compound
20	Office	Office	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	nmod
21	are	be	VBP	O	22	aux
22	working	work	VBG	O	11	dep
23	behind	behind	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	scenes	scene	NNS	O	22	nmod
26	on	on	IN	O	29	case
27	David	David	NNP	PERSON	29	nmod:poss
28	's	's	POS	O	27	case
29	behalf	behalf	NN	O	25	nmod
30	.	.	.	O	5	punct
31	''	''	''	O	5	punct

1	``	``	``	O	30	punct
2	But	but	CC	O	30	cc
3	because	because	IN	O	6	mark
4	banks	bank	NNS	O	6	nsubj
5	have	have	VBP	O	6	aux
6	expanded	expand	VBN	O	30	advcl
7	their	they	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
8	profit	profit	NN	O	9	compound
9	margins	margin	NNS	O	6	dobj
10	by	by	IN	O	13	case
11	at	at	IN	O	12	case
12	least	least	JJS	O	13	nmod:npmod
13	one	one	CD	NUMBER	6	nmod
14	per	per	IN	O	15	case
15	cent	cent	NN	O	13	nmod
16	for	for	IN	O	17	case
17	mortgages	mortgage	NNS	O	15	nmod
18	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
19	two	two	CD	NUMBER	13	conj
20	per	per	IN	O	21	case
21	cent	cent	NN	O	19	nmod
22	on	on	IN	O	24	case
23	business	business	NN	O	24	compound
24	loans	loan	NNS	O	6	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	30	punct
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	RBA	rba	NNS	ORGANIZATION	30	nsubj
28	will	will	MD	O	30	aux
29	not	not	RB	O	30	neg
30	want	want	VB	O	0	ROOT
31	to	to	TO	O	32	mark
32	raise	raise	VB	O	30	xcomp
33	the	the	DT	O	35	det
34	cash	cash	NN	O	35	compound
35	rate	rate	NN	O	44	nsubj
36	too	too	RB	O	37	advmod
37	high	high	JJ	O	44	dep
38	because	because	IN	O	42	mark
39	what	what	WP	O	42	nmod
40	it	it	PRP	O	42	nsubj
41	really	really	RB	O	42	advmod
42	focuses	focus	VBZ	O	44	dep
43	on	on	IN	O	39	case
44	is	be	VBZ	O	32	xcomp
45	what	what	WP	O	48	dobj
46	borrowers	borrower	NNS	O	48	nsubj
47	are	be	VBP	O	48	aux
48	paying	pay	VBG	O	44	dep
49	.	.	.	O	44	punct
50	The	the	DT	O	52	det
51	`	`	``	O	52	punct
52	new	new	JJ	O	59	nsubj
53	neutral	neutral	JJ	O	52	amod
54	'	'	''	O	59	punct
55	is	be	VBZ	O	59	cop
56	probably	probably	RB	O	59	advmod
57	now	now	RB	DATE	59	advmod
58	between	between	IN	O	59	amod
59	4	4	CD	NUMBER	30	ccomp
60	and	and	CC	NUMBER	59	cc
61	5	5	CD	NUMBER	59	conj
62	per	per	IN	O	63	case
63	cent	cent	NN	O	59	nmod
64	.	.	.	O	30	punct
65	''	''	''	O	30	punct

1	Environment	Environment	NNP	O	3	compound
2	Commissioner	Commissioner	NNP	O	3	compound
3	Ebgebike	Ebgebike	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
4	says	say	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	funding	funding	NN	O	7	nsubj
6	is	be	VBZ	O	7	cop
7	critical	critical	JJ	O	4	ccomp
8	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
9	appeals	appeal	NNS	O	14	nsubj
10	for	for	IN	O	12	case
11	international	international	JJ	O	12	amod
12	help	help	NN	O	9	nmod
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	deal	deal	VB	O	4	conj
15	with	with	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	situation	situation	NN	O	14	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Today	today	NN	DATE	3	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	figure	figure	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	compares	compare	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	with	with	IN	O	8	case
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	record-low	record-low	JJ	O	8	amod
8	38.8	38.8	CD	NUMBER	4	nmod
9	in	in	IN	O	10	case
10	November	November	NNP	DATE	8	nmod
11	last	last	JJ	DATE	12	amod
12	year	year	NN	DATE	4	nmod:tmod
13	,	,	,	O	4	punct
14	when	when	WRB	O	23	advmod
15	recessions	recession	NNS	O	23	nsubj
16	in	in	IN	O	18	case
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	U.S.	U.S.	NNP	LOCATION	15	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	Europe	Europe	NNP	LOCATION	18	conj
21	and	and	CC	O	18	cc
22	Japan	Japan	NNP	LOCATION	18	conj
23	sent	send	VBD	O	4	advcl
24	export	export	NN	O	25	compound
25	orders	order	NNS	O	23	dobj
26	plunging	plunge	VBG	O	25	acl
27	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Corben	Corben	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	is	be	VBZ	O	3	cop
3	part	part	NN	O	0	ROOT
4	of	of	IN	O	9	case
5	the	the	DT	O	9	det
6	Eastern	Eastern	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
7	Suburbs	Suburbs	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	compound
8	social	social	JJ	O	9	amod
9	set	set	NN	O	3	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
11	works	work	VBZ	O	3	conj
12	in	in	IN	O	15	case
13	the	the	DT	O	15	det
14	finance	finance	NN	O	15	compound
15	sector	sector	NN	O	11	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	``	``	``	O	23	punct
2	It	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	would	would	MD	O	5	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	5	cop
5	difficult	difficult	JJ	O	23	ccomp
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	detain	detain	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	another	another	DT	O	9	det
9	person	person	NN	O	7	dobj
10	while	while	IN	O	11	mark
11	removing	remove	VBG	O	7	advcl
12	their	they	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	clothes	clothes	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	and	and	CC	O	13	cc
15	one	one	CD	NUMBER	18	nmod:poss
16	's	's	POS	O	15	case
17	own	own	JJ	O	18	amod
18	clothing	clothing	NN	O	13	conj
19	,	,	,	O	23	punct
20	''	''	''	O	23	punct
21	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	22	compound
22	Cavanagh	Cavanagh	NNP	PERSON	23	nsubj
23	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
24	.	.	.	O	23	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	anti-naxal	anti-naxal	JJ	O	3	amod
3	plan	plan	NN	O	5	nsubj
4	also	also	RB	O	5	advmod
5	includes	include	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
6	Rs	rs	NN	O	9	compound
7	7,300	7,300	CD	NUMBER	9	nummod
8	crore	crore	NN	O	9	compound
9	package	package	NN	O	5	dobj
10	for	for	IN	O	11	mark
11	unleashing	unleash	VBG	O	9	acl
12	developmental	developmental	JJ	O	13	amod
13	works	work	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	in	in	IN	O	15	case
15	areas	area	NNS	O	11	nmod
16	cleared	clear	VBD	O	15	acl
17	off	off	RP	O	16	compound:prt
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	Left-wing	left-wing	JJ	MISC	20	amod
20	extremists	extremist	NNS	O	16	dobj
21	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Forest	forest	NN	O	2	compound
2	children	child	NNS	O	8	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	they	they	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	say	say	VBP	O	8	parataxis
6	,	,	,	O	5	punct
7	must	must	MD	O	8	aux
8	grow	grow	VB	O	0	ROOT
9	up	up	RP	O	8	compound:prt
10	fast	fast	RB	O	8	advmod
11	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	4	nsubj
2	had	have	VBD	O	4	aux
3	already	already	RB	O	4	advmod
4	hired	hire	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	people	people	NNS	O	4	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	compile	compile	VB	O	4	dep
8	archival	archival	JJ	O	9	amod
9	research	research	NN	O	7	dobj
10	on	on	IN	O	11	case
11	cars	car	NNS	O	7	nmod
12	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	take	take	VB	O	7	conj
15	oral	oral	JJ	O	16	amod
16	histories	history	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	from	from	IN	O	20	case
18	important	important	JJ	O	20	amod
19	automotive	automotive	JJ	O	20	amod
20	figures	figure	NNS	O	14	nmod
21	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Adipic	adipic	JJ	O	2	amod
2	acid	acid	NN	O	5	nsubjpass
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	auxpass
4	primarily	primarily	RB	O	5	advmod
5	used	use	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	in	in	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	production	production	NN	O	5	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	nylon	nylon	NN	O	8	nmod
11	6-6	6-6	CD	NUMBER	10	nummod
12	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
13	for	for	IN	O	16	case
14	manufacturing	manufacture	VBG	O	16	amod
15	polyurethane	polyurethane	NN	O	16	compound
16	foam	foam	NN	O	8	conj
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	polyester	polyester	NN	O	19	compound
19	resins	resin	NNS	O	16	conj
20	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	group	group	NN	O	30	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	popular	popular	JJ	O	6	amod
5	football	football	NN	O	6	compound
6	players	player	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	and	and	CC	O	6	cc
8	cheerleaders	cheerleader	NNS	O	6	conj
9	-	-	:	O	6	punct
10	notably	notably	RB	O	15	advmod
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	school	school	NN	O	15	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	First	first	JJ	ORDINAL	15	amod
15	Couple	couple	NN	O	6	dep
16	,	,	,	O	15	punct
17	Quinn	Quinn	NNP	PERSON	15	conj
18	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	20	punct
19	Dianna	Dianna	NNP	PERSON	20	compound
20	Agron	Agron	NNP	PERSON	17	appos
21	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	20	punct
22	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
23	Finn	Finn	NNP	O	15	conj
24	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	26	punct
25	Cory	Cory	NNP	PERSON	26	compound
26	Monteith	Monteith	NNP	PERSON	23	appos
27	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	26	punct
28	-	-	:	O	6	punct
29	have	have	VBP	O	30	aux
30	joined	join	VBN	O	0	ROOT
31	the	the	DT	O	34	det
32	much-scorned	much-scorned	JJ	O	34	amod
33	glee	glee	NN	O	34	compound
34	club	club	NN	O	30	dobj
35	,	,	,	O	30	punct
36	and	and	CC	O	30	cc
37	their	they	PRP$	O	38	nmod:poss
38	friends	friend	NNS	O	52	nsubj
39	and	and	CC	O	38	cc
40	coaches	coach	NNS	O	38	conj
41	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	38	punct
42	including	include	VBG	O	49	case
43	Jane	Jane	NNP	PERSON	44	compound
44	Lynch	Lynch	NNP	PERSON	49	nmod:poss
45	's	's	POS	O	44	case
46	fabulously	fabulously	RB	O	47	advmod
47	demonic	demonic	JJ	O	49	amod
48	cheerleader	cheerleader	NN	O	49	compound
49	leader	leader	NN	O	38	nmod
50	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	38	punct
51	are	be	VBP	O	52	aux
52	tormenting	torment	VBG	O	30	conj
53	them	they	PRP	O	52	dobj
54	.	.	.	O	30	punct

1	``	``	``	O	15	punct
2	We	we	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	are	be	VBP	O	5	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	commenting	comment	VBG	O	15	ccomp
6	until	until	IN	O	9	mark
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	UAW	UAW	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	nsubj
9	announces	announce	VBZ	O	5	advcl
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	final	final	JJ	O	12	amod
12	results	result	NNS	O	9	dobj
13	,	,	,	O	15	punct
14	''	''	''	O	15	punct
15	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	Marcey	Marcey	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Evans	Evans	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	Ford	Ford	NNP	ORGANIZATION	21	compound
21	spokeswoman	spokeswoman	NN	O	17	appos
22	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	From	from	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	4	amod
4	moments	moment	NNS	O	6	nmod
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	arrived	arrive	VBD	O	20	ccomp
7	in	in	IN	O	8	case
8	Washington	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	6	nmod
9	on	on	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	DATE	11	det
11	day	day	NN	DATE	6	nmod
12	after	after	IN	O	16	case
13	his	he	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
14	Sept.	Sept.	NNP	DATE	16	compound
15	24	24	CD	DATE	16	nummod
16	appointment	appointment	NN	O	6	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	20	punct
18	Kirk	Kirk	NNP	PERSON	20	nsubj
19	has	have	VBZ	O	20	aux
20	remained	remain	VBN	O	0	ROOT
21	deferential	deferential	JJ	O	20	xcomp
22	to	to	TO	O	25	case
23	his	he	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
24	former	former	JJ	O	25	amod
25	boss	boss	NN	O	21	nmod
26	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	3	case
2	other	other	JJ	O	3	amod
3	reports	report	NNS	O	18	nmod
4	this	this	DT	DATE	5	det
5	week	week	NN	DATE	18	nmod:tmod
6	,	,	,	O	18	punct
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	number	number	NN	O	18	nsubjpass
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	contracts	contract	NNS	O	8	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	buy	buy	VB	O	10	acl
13	previously	previously	RB	DATE	14	advmod
14	owned	own	VBN	O	15	amod
15	homes	home	NNS	O	12	dobj
16	were	be	VBD	O	18	auxpass
17	little	little	RB	O	18	advmod
18	changed	change	VBN	O	0	ROOT
19	in	in	IN	O	20	case
20	September	September	NNP	DATE	18	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	18	punct
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	24	amod
24	time	time	NN	O	18	dobj
25	in	in	IN	O	27	case
26	eight	eight	CD	DURATION	27	nummod
27	months	month	NNS	DURATION	18	nmod
28	they	they	PRP	O	31	nsubj
29	did	do	VBD	O	31	aux
30	n't	not	RB	O	31	neg
31	increase	increase	VB	O	27	acl:relcl
32	,	,	,	O	18	punct
33	according	accord	VBG	O	37	case
34	to	to	TO	O	33	mwe
35	the	the	DT	O	37	det
36	survey	survey	NN	O	37	compound
37	median	median	NN	O	18	nmod
38	.	.	.	O	18	punct

1	Murray	Murray	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
3	Cantwell	Cantwell	NNP	PERSON	1	conj
4	described	describe	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	him	he	PRP	O	4	dobj
6	as	as	IN	O	9	case
7	an	a	DT	O	9	det
8	``	``	``	O	9	punct
9	asset	asset	NN	O	4	nmod
10	to	to	TO	O	12	case
11	his	he	PRP$	O	12	nmod:poss
12	community	community	NN	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	friends	friend	NNS	O	12	conj
15	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
16	family	family	NN	O	12	conj
17	,	,	,	O	9	punct
18	''	''	''	O	9	punct
19	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
20	like	like	IN	O	21	case
21	Hastings	Hastings	NNP	PERSON	23	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	23	punct
23	asked	ask	VBD	O	4	conj
24	that	that	IN	O	27	mark
25	immigration	immigration	NN	O	26	compound
26	authorities	authority	NNS	O	27	nsubj
27	give	give	VBP	O	23	ccomp
28	Chaudhry	Chaudhry	NNP	PERSON	27	iobj
29	full	full	JJ	O	30	amod
30	consideration	consideration	NN	O	27	dobj
31	in	in	IN	O	33	case
32	his	he	PRP$	O	33	nmod:poss
33	request	request	NN	O	30	nmod
34	for	for	IN	O	35	case
35	citizenship	citizenship	NN	O	33	nmod
36	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	On	on	IN	O	2	case
2	Friday	Friday	NNP	DATE	6	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	6	punct
4	Mr.	Mr.	NNP	O	5	compound
5	Yushchenko	Yushchenko	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
6	criticized	criticize	VBD	O	0	ROOT
7	Ms.	Ms.	NNP	O	8	compound
8	Tymoshenko	Tymoshenko	NNP	PERSON	6	dobj
9	,	,	,	O	6	punct
10	saying	say	VBG	O	6	advcl
11	he	he	PRP	O	13	nsubj
12	had	have	VBD	O	13	aux
13	ordered	order	VBN	O	10	ccomp
14	an	a	DT	O	15	det
15	inquiry	inquiry	NN	O	13	dobj
16	into	into	IN	O	27	mark
17	why	why	WRB	O	27	advmod
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	country	country	NN	O	27	nsubjpass
20	was	be	VBD	O	27	auxpass
21	not	not	RB	O	27	neg
22	,	,	,	O	25	punct
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	his	he	PRP$	O	25	nmod:poss
25	opinion	opinion	NN	O	27	dep
26	,	,	,	O	25	punct
27	prepared	prepare	VBN	O	13	advcl
28	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	seven	seven	CD	NUMBER	3	nummod
3	aspirants	aspirant	NNS	O	9	nsubj
4	for	for	IN	O	8	case
5	M.J.	M.J.	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	Khan	Khan	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod:poss
7	's	's	POS	O	6	case
8	seat	seat	NN	O	3	nmod
9	reflect	reflect	VBP	O	0	ROOT
10	that	that	IN	O	11	case
11	diversity	diversity	NN	O	9	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Among	among	IN	O	2	case
2	them	they	PRP	O	5	nmod
3	are	be	VBP	O	5	cop
4	1,000	1,000	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	pages	page	NNS	O	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	dossier	dossier	NN	O	5	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	10	case
10	Sascha	Sascha	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
11	Anderson	Anderson	NNP	PERSON	5	nsubj
12	,	,	,	O	11	punct
13	an	a	DT	O	15	det
14	avant-garde	avant-garde	JJ	O	15	amod
15	artist	artist	NN	O	11	appos
16	who	who	WP	O	20	nsubj
17	was	be	VBD	O	20	cop
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	service	service	NN	O	15	acl:relcl
21	of	of	IN	O	23	case
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	Stasi	stasi	NN	LOCATION	20	nmod
24	but	but	CC	O	20	cc
25	always	always	RB	O	26	advmod
26	denied	deny	VBD	O	20	conj
27	any	any	DT	O	29	det
28	deep	deep	JJ	O	29	amod
29	involvement	involvement	NN	O	26	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	At	at	IN	O	3	case
2	the	the	DT	O	3	det
3	height	height	NN	O	10	nmod
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	his	he	PRP$	O	6	nmod:poss
6	career	career	NN	O	3	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	10	punct
8	Madoff	Madoff	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubjpass
9	was	be	VBD	O	10	auxpass
10	regarded	regard	VBN	O	24	ccomp
11	as	as	IN	O	14	case
12	a	a	DT	O	14	det
13	financial	financial	JJ	O	14	amod
14	genius	genius	NN	O	10	nmod
15	,	,	,	O	10	punct
16	he	he	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	even	even	RB	O	18	advmod
18	served	serve	VBD	O	10	parataxis
19	as	as	IN	O	20	case
20	chairman	chairman	NN	O	18	nmod
21	of	of	IN	O	22	case
22	NASDAQ	NASDAQ	NNP	MISC	20	nmod
23	,	,	,	O	24	punct
24	reports	report	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
25	CBS	CBS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	29	compound
26	News	News	NNP	ORGANIZATION	29	compound
27	correspondent	correspondent	NN	O	29	compound
28	Randall	Randall	NNP	PERSON	29	compound
29	Pinkston	Pinkston	NNP	PERSON	24	nsubj
30	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	Born	bear	VBN	O	14	advcl
2	between	between	IN	O	3	case
3	1978	1978	CD	DATE	1	nmod
4	and	and	CC	DATE	3	cc
5	the	the	DT	DATE	6	det
6	turn	turn	NN	DATE	3	conj
7	of	of	IN	DATE	9	case
8	this	this	DT	DATE	9	det
9	century	century	NN	DATE	6	nmod
10	,	,	,	O	14	punct
11	millennials	millennial	NNS	O	14	nsubjpass
12	are	be	VBP	O	14	auxpass
13	not	not	RB	O	14	neg
14	worked	work	VBN	O	0	ROOT
15	up	up	RP	O	14	compound:prt
16	over	over	IN	O	19	case
17	the	the	DT	O	19	det
18	culture	culture	NN	O	19	compound
19	wars	war	NNS	O	14	nmod
20	that	that	WDT	O	22	nsubj
21	have	have	VBP	O	22	aux
22	raged	rage	VBN	O	19	acl:relcl
23	since	since	IN	O	26	case
24	the	the	DT	O	26	det
25	Reagan	Reagan	NNP	PERSON	26	compound
26	era	era	NN	O	22	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	14	punct

1	During	during	IN	O	4	case
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	worst	worst	JJS	O	4	amod
4	years	year	NNS	DURATION	7	nmod
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
8	,	,	,	O	11	punct
9	it	it	PRP	O	11	nsubj
10	was	be	VBD	O	11	cop
11	difficult	difficult	JJ	O	7	dep
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	buy	buy	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	plants	plant	NNS	O	13	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	11	punct
16	so	so	IN	O	7	dep
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	family	family	NN	O	19	nsubj
19	used	use	VBD	O	7	parataxis
20	clippings	clipping	NNS	O	19	dobj
21	to	to	TO	O	22	mark
22	fill	fill	VB	O	19	advcl
23	out	out	RP	O	22	compound:prt
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	garden	garden	NN	O	22	dobj
26	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	``	``	``	O	15	punct
2	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	felt	feel	VBD	O	15	ccomp
4	she	she	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	did	do	VBD	O	3	ccomp
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	best	best	JJS	O	5	dobj
8	in	in	IN	O	9	mark
9	talking	talk	VBG	O	5	advcl
10	about	about	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	issues	issue	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	15	punct
14	''	''	''	O	15	punct
15	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	Aguirre	Aguirre	NNP	PERSON	15	nsubj
17	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	Ministers	Ministers	NNP	O	2	nsubj
2	say	say	VBP	O	0	ROOT
3	they	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	want	want	VBP	O	2	ccomp
5	a	a	DT	O	7	det
6	better	better	JJR	O	7	amod
7	deal	deal	NN	O	4	dobj
8	for	for	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	consumer	consumer	NN	O	7	nmod
11	with	with	IN	O	15	case
12	an	a	DT	O	15	det
13	invigorated	invigorated	JJ	O	15	amod
14	mortgage	mortgage	NN	O	15	compound
15	market	market	NN	O	10	nmod
16	and	and	CC	O	15	cc
17	more	more	JJR	O	18	amod
18	competition	competition	NN	O	15	conj
19	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Sonora	Sonora	NNP	LOCATION	10	nsubjpass
2	,	,	,	O	10	punct
3	like	like	IN	O	4	case
4	much	much	JJ	O	10	nmod
5	of	of	IN	O	6	case
6	Mexico	Mexico	NNP	LOCATION	4	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	10	punct
8	has	have	VBZ	O	10	aux
9	been	be	VBN	O	10	auxpass
10	hit	hit	VBN	O	0	ROOT
11	by	by	IN	O	13	case
12	a	a	DT	O	13	det
13	wave	wave	NN	O	10	nmod
14	of	of	IN	O	15	case
15	killings	killing	NNS	O	13	nmod
16	tied	tie	VBN	O	15	acl
17	to	to	TO	O	19	case
18	drug-trafficking	drug-trafficking	JJ	O	19	amod
19	gangs	gang	NNS	O	16	nmod
20	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	Coast	Coast	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	Guard	Guard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nsubj
4	identified	identify	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	its	its	PRP$	O	8	nmod:poss
6	seven	seven	CD	NUMBER	8	nummod
7	missing	miss	VBG	O	8	amod
8	personnel	personnel	NNS	O	4	dobj
9	as	as	IN	O	14	case
10	Lt.	Lt.	NNP	O	14	compound
11	Cmdr.	Cmdr.	NNP	O	14	compound
12	Che	Che	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
13	J.	J.	NNP	PERSON	14	compound
14	Barnes	Barnes	NNP	PERSON	8	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	Capay	Capay	NNP	LOCATION	14	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	14	punct
18	California	California	NNP	LOCATION	14	appos
19	,	,	,	O	18	punct
20	aircraft	aircraft	NN	O	21	compound
21	commander	commander	NN	O	18	appos
22	;	;	:	O	18	punct
23	Lt.	Lt.	NNP	O	26	compound
24	Adam	Adam	NNP	PERSON	26	compound
25	W.	W.	NNP	PERSON	26	compound
26	Bryant	Bryant	NNP	PERSON	18	dep
27	of	of	IN	O	30	case
28	Crewe	Crewe	NNP	LOCATION	30	compound
29	,	,	,	O	30	punct
30	Virginia	Virginia	NNP	LOCATION	26	nmod
31	,	,	,	O	30	punct
32	co-pilot	co-pilot	NNS	O	30	appos
33	;	;	:	O	18	punct
34	Chief	Chief	NNP	O	39	compound
35	Petty	Petty	NNP	O	39	compound
36	Officer	Officer	NNP	O	39	compound
37	John	John	NNP	PERSON	39	compound
38	F.	F.	NNP	PERSON	39	compound
39	Seidman	Seidman	NNP	PERSON	18	dep
40	of	of	IN	O	43	case
41	Stockton	Stockton	NNP	LOCATION	43	compound
42	,	,	,	O	43	punct
43	California	California	NNP	LOCATION	39	nmod
44	,	,	,	O	43	punct
45	flight	flight	NN	O	46	compound
46	engineer	engineer	NN	O	43	appos
47	;	;	:	O	18	punct
48	Petty	Petty	NNP	O	54	compound
49	Officer	Officer	NNP	O	54	compound
50	2nd	2nd	JJ	ORDINAL	54	amod
51	Class	class	NN	O	54	compound
52	Carl	Carl	NNP	PERSON	54	compound
53	P.	P.	NNP	PERSON	54	compound
54	Grigonis	Grigonis	NNP	PERSON	18	dep
55	of	of	IN	O	56	case
56	Mayfield	Mayfield	NNP	LOCATION	54	nmod
57	Heights	Heights	NNP	LOCATION	61	dep
58	,	,	,	O	57	punct
59	Ohio	Ohio	NNP	LOCATION	57	dep
60	,	,	,	O	57	punct
61	navigator	navigator	NN	O	54	dep
62	;	;	:	O	18	punct
63	Petty	Petty	NNP	O	69	compound
64	Officer	Officer	NNP	O	69	compound
65	2nd	2nd	JJ	ORDINAL	69	amod
66	Class	class	NN	O	69	compound
67	Monica	Monica	NNP	PERSON	69	compound
68	L.	L.	NNP	PERSON	69	compound
69	Beacham	Beacham	NNP	PERSON	18	dep
70	of	of	IN	O	71	case
71	Decaturville	Decaturville	NNP	LOCATION	69	nmod
72	,	,	,	O	14	punct
73	Tennessee	Tennessee	NNP	LOCATION	14	appos
74	,	,	,	O	73	punct
75	radio	radio	NN	O	76	compound
76	operator	operator	NN	O	73	appos
77	;	;	:	O	14	punct
78	Petty	Petty	NNP	O	84	compound
79	Officer	Officer	NNP	O	84	compound
80	2nd	2nd	JJ	ORDINAL	84	amod
81	Class	class	NN	O	84	compound
82	Jason	Jason	NNP	PERSON	84	compound
83	S.	S.	NNP	PERSON	84	compound
84	Moletzsky	Moletzsky	NNP	PERSON	14	dep
85	of	of	IN	O	86	case
86	Norristown	Norristown	NNP	LOCATION	84	nmod
87	,	,	,	O	14	punct
88	Pennsylvania	Pennsylvania	NNP	LOCATION	14	appos
89	,	,	,	O	88	punct
90	air	air	NN	O	91	compound
91	crew	crew	NN	O	88	appos
92	;	;	:	O	4	punct
93	Petty	Petty	NNP	O	94	compound
94	Officer	Officer	NNP	O	95	nsubj
95	3rd	3rd	VBD	ORDINAL	4	parataxis
96	Class	Class	NNP	O	100	compound
97	Danny	Danny	NNP	PERSON	100	compound
98	R.	R.	NNP	PERSON	100	compound
99	Kreder	Kreder	NNP	PERSON	100	compound
100	II	II	NNP	PERSON	95	dobj
101	of	of	IN	O	103	case
102	Elm	Elm	NNP	LOCATION	103	compound
103	Mott	Mott	NNP	LOCATION	100	nmod
104	,	,	,	O	103	punct
105	Texas	Texas	NNP	LOCATION	103	appos
106	,	,	,	O	105	punct
107	drop	drop	NN	O	108	compound
108	master	master	NN	O	105	appos
109	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Johnson	Johnson	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	teachers	teacher	NNS	O	1	conj
4	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
5	students	student	NNS	O	1	conj
6	at	at	IN	O	8	dep
7	least	least	JJS	O	6	mwe
8	partially	partially	RB	O	9	advmod
9	blame	blame	VB	O	0	ROOT
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	attack	attack	NN	O	9	dobj
12	on	on	IN	O	14	case
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	lack	lack	NN	O	9	nmod
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	lighting	lighting	NN	O	14	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	9	punct
18	sturdy	sturdy	JJ	O	19	amod
19	fencing	fencing	NN	O	9	dobj
20	or	or	CC	O	19	cc
21	security	security	NN	O	22	compound
22	cameras	camera	NNS	O	19	conj
23	on	on	IN	O	25	case
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	courtyard	courtyard	NN	O	19	nmod
26	,	,	,	O	25	punct
27	which	which	WDT	O	28	nsubj
28	abuts	abut	VBZ	O	25	acl:relcl
29	a	a	DT	O	31	det
30	rough	rough	JJ	O	31	amod
31	neighborhood	neighborhood	NN	O	28	dobj
32	on	on	IN	O	35	case
33	the	the	DT	O	35	det
34	northern	northern	JJ	O	35	amod
35	end	end	NN	O	28	nmod
36	of	of	IN	O	38	case
37	the	the	DT	O	38	det
38	campus	campus	NN	O	35	nmod
39	on	on	IN	O	41	case
40	23rd	23rd	JJ	ORDINAL	41	amod
41	Street	street	NN	O	38	nmod
42	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	governor	governor	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	insisted	insist	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	last	last	JJ	DATE	5	amod
5	summer	summer	NN	DATE	3	nmod:tmod
6	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	wanted	want	VBD	O	3	ccomp
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	ban	ban	NN	O	7	dobj
10	because	because	IN	O	16	mark
11	party	party	NN	O	12	compound
12	bosses	boss	NNS	O	16	nsubj
13	should	should	MD	O	16	aux
14	n't	not	RB	O	16	neg
15	be	be	VB	O	16	aux
16	slating	slate	VBG	O	7	advcl
17	candidates	candidate	NNS	O	16	dobj
18	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	draft	draft	NN	O	3	compound
3	amendment	amendment	NN	O	4	nsubj
4	echoed	echo	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	Communist	Communist	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	compound
6	Party	Party	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	dobj
7	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	8	case
8	China	China	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	nmod
9	-LRB-	-lrb-	-LRB-	O	10	punct
10	CPC	CPC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	6	appos
11	-RRB-	-rrb-	-RRB-	O	10	punct
12	Central	Central	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
13	Committee	Committee	NNP	ORGANIZATION	17	compound
14	General	General	NNP	O	17	compound
15	Secretary	Secretary	NNP	O	17	compound
16	Hu	Hu	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Jintao	Jintao	NNP	PERSON	6	dep
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	who	who	WP	O	20	nsubj
20	proposed	propose	VBD	O	17	acl:relcl
21	in	in	IN	O	23	case
22	a	a	DT	O	23	det
23	report	report	NN	O	20	nmod
24	to	to	TO	O	29	case
25	the	the	DT	O	29	det
26	17th	17th	JJ	ORDINAL	29	amod
27	CPC	CPC	NNP	ORGANIZATION	29	compound
28	National	National	NNP	ORGANIZATION	29	compound
29	Congress	Congress	NNP	ORGANIZATION	23	nmod
30	in	in	IN	O	31	case
31	October	October	NNP	DATE	29	nmod
32	2007	2007	CD	DATE	31	nummod
33	that	that	WDT	O	39	dobj
34	rural	rural	JJ	O	37	amod
35	and	and	CC	O	34	cc
36	urban	urban	JJ	O	34	conj
37	areas	area	NNS	O	39	nsubj
38	should	should	MD	O	39	aux
39	have	have	VB	O	20	ccomp
40	equal	equal	JJ	O	41	amod
41	rights	rights	NNS	O	39	dobj
42	in	in	IN	O	43	case
43	election	election	NN	O	41	nmod
44	of	of	IN	O	45	case
45	lawmakers	lawmaker	NNS	O	43	nmod
46	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	``	``	``	O	20	punct
2	What	what	WP	O	5	nsubjpass
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	being	be	VBG	O	5	auxpass
5	looked	look	VBD	O	8	nsubj
6	at	at	IN	O	7	case
7	seriously	seriously	RB	O	5	advmod
8	is	be	VBZ	O	20	ccomp
9	whether	whether	IN	O	11	mark
10	we	we	PRP	O	11	nsubj
11	need	need	VBP	O	8	ccomp
12	further	further	JJ	O	13	amod
13	increases	increase	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	in	in	IN	O	15	mark
15	spending	spend	VBG	O	11	advcl
16	next	next	JJ	DATE	17	amod
17	year	year	NN	DATE	15	nmod:tmod
18	,	,	,	O	20	punct
19	''	''	''	O	20	punct
20	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
21	a	a	DT	O	23	det
22	Labour	labour	NN	ORGANIZATION	23	compound
23	source	source	NN	O	20	nsubj
24	.	.	.	O	20	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	4	det
2	large	large	JJ	O	4	amod
3	debris	debris	NN	O	4	compound
4	field	field	NN	O	7	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	7	aux
6	been	be	VBN	O	7	cop
7	located	located	JJ	O	16	ccomp
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	and	and	CC	O	7	cc
10	debris	debris	NN	O	13	nsubjpass
11	has	have	VBZ	O	13	aux
12	been	be	VBN	O	13	auxpass
13	collected	collect	VBN	O	7	conj
14	,	,	,	O	16	punct
15	he	he	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
17	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	``	``	``	O	37	punct
2	They	they	PRP	O	4	nsubj
3	were	be	VBD	O	4	aux
4	searching	search	VBG	O	37	ccomp
5	for	for	IN	O	8	case
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	possible	possible	JJ	O	8	amod
8	person	person	NN	O	4	nmod
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	water	water	NN	O	8	nmod
12	who	who	WP	O	14	nsubjpass
13	was	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
14	reported	report	VBN	O	11	acl:relcl
15	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
16	have	have	VB	O	17	aux
17	gotten	get	VBN	O	14	xcomp
18	in	in	IN	O	20	case
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	dinghy	dinghy	NN	O	17	nmod
21	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
22	attempted	attempt	VBN	O	17	conj
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	row	row	VB	O	22	xcomp
25	to	to	TO	O	28	case
26	Catalina	Catalina	NNP	LOCATION	28	compound
27	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	28	punct
28	Island	Island	NNP	O	24	nmod
29	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	28	punct
30	,	,	,	O	37	punct
31	''	''	''	O	37	punct
32	Coast	Coast	NNP	ORGANIZATION	36	compound
33	Guard	Guard	NNP	ORGANIZATION	36	compound
34	Capt.	Capt.	NNP	O	36	compound
35	Thomas	Thomas	NNP	PERSON	36	compound
36	Farris	Farris	NNP	PERSON	37	nsubj
37	told	tell	VBD	O	0	ROOT
38	reporters	reporter	NNS	O	37	dobj
39	Friday	Friday	NNP	DATE	37	nmod:tmod
40	.	.	.	O	37	punct

1	What	what	WDT	O	2	nsubj
2	ensued	ensue	VBD	O	5	csubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	5	cop
4	21/2	21/2	CD	NUMBER	5	nummod
5	hours	hour	NNS	DURATION	0	ROOT
6	of	of	IN	O	7	case
7	beatings	beating	NNS	O	5	nmod
8	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
9	raping	rape	VBG	O	5	conj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	at	at	IN	O	12	case
12	times	time	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	with	with	IN	O	16	case
14	a	a	DT	O	16	det
15	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	16	amod
16	object	object	NN	O	9	nmod
17	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	``	``	``	O	8	punct
2	One	one	CD	NUMBER	8	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	6	case
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	key	key	JJ	O	6	amod
6	qualifications	qualification	NNS	O	2	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	8	aux
8	having	have	VBG	O	0	ROOT
9	clout	clout	NN	O	8	dobj
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	America	America	NNP	LOCATION	9	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	11	punct
13	David	David	NNP	PERSON	14	nsubj
14	has	have	VBZ	O	11	acl:relcl
15	a	a	DT	O	18	det
16	very	very	RB	O	17	advmod
17	good	good	JJ	O	18	amod
18	relationship	relationship	NN	O	14	dobj
19	with	with	IN	O	21	case
20	Hillary	Hillary	NNP	PERSON	21	compound
21	Clinton	Clinton	NNP	PERSON	18	nmod
22	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	25	punct
23	the	the	DT	O	25	det
24	US	US	NNP	LOCATION	25	compound
25	secretary	secretary	NN	O	21	nmod
26	of	of	IN	O	27	case
27	state	state	NN	O	25	nmod
28	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	27	punct
29	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
30	is	be	VBZ	O	32	auxpass
31	highly	highly	RB	O	32	advmod
32	regarded	regard	VBN	O	14	conj
33	in	in	IN	O	34	case
34	Washington	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
35	,	,	,	O	8	punct
36	so	so	RB	O	8	advmod
37	he	he	PRP	O	41	nsubjpass
38	is	be	VBZ	O	41	auxpass
39	very	very	RB	O	41	advmod
40	well	well	RB	O	41	advmod
41	placed	place	VBN	O	8	parataxis
42	.	.	.	O	8	punct
43	''	''	''	O	8	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	gain	gain	NN	O	6	nsubj
3	would	would	MD	O	6	aux
4	be	be	VB	O	6	cop
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	fifth	fifth	JJ	ORDINAL	0	ROOT
7	in	in	IN	O	11	case
8	the	the	DT	DURATION	11	det
9	past	past	JJ	DURATION	11	amod
10	six	six	CD	DURATION	11	nummod
11	months	month	NNS	DURATION	6	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	7	cc
2	most	most	JJS	O	7	nsubj
3	of	of	IN	O	5	case
4	those	those	DT	O	5	det
5	relatives	relative	NNS	O	2	nmod
6	had	have	VBD	O	7	aux
7	died	die	VBN	O	0	ROOT
8	peacefully	peacefully	RB	O	7	advmod
9	,	,	,	O	7	punct
10	perhaps	perhaps	RB	O	7	advmod
11	in	in	IN	O	13	case
12	their	they	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
13	sleep	sleep	NN	O	7	nmod
14	or	or	CC	O	13	cc
15	in	in	IN	O	17	case
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	loving	loving	JJ	O	13	conj
18	embrace	embrace	VBP	O	17	acl:relcl
19	.	.	.	O	7	punct

1	Lost	lose	VBN	O	10	csubj
2	in	in	IN	O	6	case
3	last	last	JJ	DATE	4	amod
4	week	week	NN	DATE	6	nmod:tmod
5	's	's	POS	O	4	case
6	furore	furore	NN	O	1	nmod
7	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
8	Nutt	Nutt	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod:poss
9	's	's	POS	O	8	case
10	comments	comment	NNS	O	0	ROOT
11	about	about	IN	O	12	case
12	ketamine	ketamine	NN	O	10	nmod
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	which	which	WDT	O	16	dobj
15	he	he	PRP	O	16	nsubj
16	suggested	suggest	VBD	O	12	acl:relcl
17	in	in	IN	O	18	case
18	evidence	evidence	NN	O	16	nmod
19	to	to	TO	O	21	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	Commons	Commons	NNPS	MISC	16	nmod
22	home	home	NN	O	23	compound
23	affairs	affair	NNS	O	16	dobj
24	select	select	JJ	O	25	amod
25	committee	committee	NN	O	28	nsubjpass
26	should	should	MD	O	28	aux
27	be	be	VB	O	28	auxpass
28	upgraded	upgrade	VBN	O	23	acl:relcl
29	from	from	IN	O	33	case
30	a	a	DT	O	33	det
31	class	class	NN	O	33	compound
32	C	c	NN	O	33	compound
33	drug	drug	NN	O	28	nmod
34	because	because	IN	O	40	mark
35	of	of	IN	O	37	case
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	harm	harm	NN	O	40	nmod
38	it	it	PRP	O	40	nsubj
39	can	can	MD	O	40	aux
40	do	do	VB	O	28	advcl
41	to	to	TO	O	42	case
42	users	user	NNS	O	40	nmod
43	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nsubj
4	endorses	endorse	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	extension	extension	NN	O	4	dobj
7	,	,	,	O	4	punct
8	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
9	lawmakers	lawmaker	NNS	O	11	nsubjpass
10	are	be	VBP	O	11	auxpass
11	expected	expect	VBN	O	4	conj
12	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
13	vote	vote	VB	O	11	xcomp
14	on	on	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	measure	measure	NN	O	13	nmod
17	this	this	DT	DATE	18	det
18	week	week	NN	DATE	13	nmod:tmod
19	,	,	,	O	11	punct
20	according	accord	VBG	O	26	case
21	to	to	TO	O	20	mwe
22	Senate	Senate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	compound
23	Majority	Majority	NNP	O	26	compound
24	Leader	Leader	NNP	O	26	compound
25	Harry	Harry	NNP	PERSON	26	compound
26	Reid	Reid	NNP	PERSON	11	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	``	``	``	O	41	punct
2	I	I	PRP	O	3	nsubj
3	have	have	VBP	O	41	ccomp
4	friends	friend	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	who	who	WP	O	6	nsubj
6	go	go	VBP	O	4	acl:relcl
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	school	school	NN	O	6	xcomp
9	in	in	IN	O	10	case
10	Concord	Concord	NNP	LOCATION	8	nmod
11	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
12	say	say	VB	O	8	conj
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	`	`	``	O	12	punct
15	Are	be	VBP	O	12	dep
16	n't	not	RB	O	15	nsubj
17	you	you	PRP	O	18	nsubj
18	scared	scare	VBD	O	15	dep
19	to	to	TO	O	20	mark
20	go	go	VB	O	18	xcomp
21	to	to	TO	O	23	case
22	Richmond	Richmond	NNP	LOCATION	23	compound
23	High	High	NNP	O	20	nmod
24	?	?	.	O	18	punct
25	'	'	''	O	18	punct
26	And	and	CC	O	3	cc
27	I	I	PRP	O	28	nsubj
28	say	say	VBP	O	3	conj
29	,	,	,	O	28	punct
30	no	no	DT	O	28	dobj
31	-	-	:	O	30	punct
32	you	you	PRP	O	34	nsubj
33	can	can	MD	O	34	aux
34	do	do	VB	O	30	dep
35	very	very	RB	O	34	advmod
36	well	well	RB	O	37	advmod
37	academically	academically	RB	O	35	advcl
38	here	here	RB	O	34	advmod
39	,	,	,	O	41	punct
40	''	''	''	O	41	punct
41	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
42	junior	junior	NN	O	41	dobj
43	Vanessa	Vanessa	NNP	PERSON	44	compound
44	Bejarano	Bejarano	NNP	PERSON	41	nsubj
45	.	.	.	O	41	punct

1	After	after	IN	O	5	mark
2	police	police	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	did	do	VBD	O	5	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	oppose	oppose	VB	O	10	advcl
6	bail	bail	NN	O	5	dobj
7	,	,	,	O	10	punct
8	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	9	compound
9	Zdenkowski	Zdenkowski	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
10	set	set	VBD	O	0	ROOT
11	it	it	PRP	O	10	dobj
12	at	at	IN	O	14	case
13	$	$	$	MONEY	14	dep
14	10,000	10,000	CD	MONEY	10	nmod
15	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
16	imposed	impose	VBN	O	10	conj
17	strict	strict	JJ	O	18	amod
18	conditions	condition	NNS	O	16	dobj
19	on	on	IN	O	22	case
20	Corben	Corben	NNP	PERSON	22	nmod:poss
21	's	's	POS	O	20	case
22	freedom	freedom	NN	O	16	nmod
23	.	.	.	O	10	punct

1	CIT	CIT	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nsubj
2	also	also	RB	O	3	advmod
3	said	say	VBD	O	17	dep
4	it	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	reached	reach	VBD	O	3	ccomp
6	an	a	DT	O	7	det
7	agreement	agreement	NN	O	5	dobj
8	with	with	IN	O	10	case
9	Goldman	Goldman	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	compound
10	Sachs	Sachs	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	keep	keep	VB	O	5	advcl
13	a	a	DT	O	15	det
14	credit	credit	NN	O	15	compound
15	line	line	NN	O	16	nsubj
16	open	open	JJ	O	12	xcomp
17	should	should	MD	O	0	ROOT
18	the	the	DT	O	20	det
19	lender	lender	NN	O	20	compound
20	file	file	NN	O	17	nsubj
21	for	for	IN	O	23	case
22	court	court	NN	O	23	compound
23	protection	protection	NN	O	20	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	17	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	1939	1939	CD	DATE	5	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	5	punct
4	he	he	PRP	O	5	nsubj
5	received	receive	VBD	O	0	ROOT
6	a	a	DT	O	7	det
7	doctorate	doctorate	NN	O	5	dobj
8	in	in	IN	O	9	case
9	aviation	aviation	NN	O	5	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	9	cc
11	mathematics	mathematics	NN	O	9	conj
12	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Li	Li	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Xiaofeng	Xiaofeng	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	appointed	appoint	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	chief	chief	JJ	O	6	amod
6	procurator	procurator	NN	O	4	dobj
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	military	military	JJ	O	10	amod
10	procuratorate	procuratorate	NN	O	6	nmod
11	under	under	IN	O	16	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	People	people	NNS	ORGANIZATION	16	nmod:poss
14	's	's	POS	ORGANIZATION	13	case
15	Liberation	Liberation	NNP	ORGANIZATION	16	compound
16	Army	Army	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	replace	replace	VB	O	4	advcl
19	Gao	Gao	NNP	PERSON	20	compound
20	Laifu	Laifu	NNP	PERSON	18	dobj
21	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	CBS	CBS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	News	News	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	nsubj
3	chief	chief	JJ	O	7	amod
4	political	political	JJ	O	7	amod
5	consultant	consultant	NN	O	7	compound
6	Marc	Marc	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Ambinder	Ambinder	NNP	PERSON	2	dep
8	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	Republicans	republican	NNS	ORGANIZATION	11	nsubj
10	will	will	MD	O	11	aux
11	derive	derive	VB	O	8	ccomp
12	two	two	CD	NUMBER	13	nummod
13	lessons	lesson	NNS	O	11	dobj
14	from	from	IN	O	16	case
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	results	result	NNS	O	11	nmod
17	of	of	IN	O	19	case
18	this	this	DT	O	19	det
19	race	race	NN	O	16	nmod
20	:	:	:	O	8	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	response	response	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	has	have	VBZ	O	4	aux
4	been	be	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	mark
6	edge	edge	VB	O	4	xcomp
7	into	into	IN	O	10	case
8	more	more	JJR	O	10	amod
9	public	public	JJ	O	10	amod
10	discussions	discussion	NNS	O	6	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	while	while	IN	O	13	mark
13	remaining	remain	VBG	O	10	dep
14	on	on	IN	O	17	case
15	the	the	DT	O	17	det
16	cautious	cautious	JJ	O	17	amod
17	course	course	NN	O	13	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Iraq	Iraq	NNP	LOCATION	4	nmod:poss
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	topiary	topiary	JJ	O	4	amod
4	gardens	garden	NNS	O	11	nsubj
5	,	,	,	O	7	punct
6	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	said	say	VBD	O	11	parataxis
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	are	be	VBP	O	11	aux
10	just	just	RB	O	11	advmod
11	beginning	begin	VBG	O	0	ROOT
12	.	.	.	O	11	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	announcement	announcement	NN	O	3	nsubj
3	comes	come	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	after	after	IN	O	9	mark
5	a	a	DT	O	8	det
6	Siena	Siena	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
7	College	College	NNP	ORGANIZATION	8	compound
8	poll	poll	NN	O	9	nsubj
9	found	find	VBD	O	3	advcl
10	she	she	PRP	O	14	nsubj
11	was	be	VBD	O	14	cop
12	in	in	IN	O	14	case
13	third	third	JJ	ORDINAL	14	amod
14	place	place	NN	O	9	ccomp
15	with	with	IN	O	17	case
16	20	20	CD	PERCENT	17	nummod
17	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	14	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	vote	vote	NN	O	17	nmod
21	in	in	IN	O	24	case
22	the	the	DT	O	24	det
23	heavily-Republican	heavily-republican	JJ	MISC	24	amod
24	district	district	NN	O	20	nmod
25	,	,	,	O	14	punct
26	while	while	IN	O	35	mark
27	Hoffman	Hoffman	NNP	PERSON	35	nsubj
28	and	and	CC	O	27	cc
29	Democratic	democratic	JJ	MISC	32	amod
30	nominee	nominee	NN	O	32	compound
31	Bill	Bill	NNP	PERSON	32	compound
32	Owens	Owens	NNP	PERSON	27	conj
33	were	be	VBD	O	35	cop
34	too	too	RB	O	35	advmod
35	close	close	JJ	O	14	advcl
36	to	to	TO	O	37	mark
37	call	call	VB	O	35	xcomp
38	,	,	,	O	37	punct
39	with	with	IN	O	41	case
40	35	35	CD	PERCENT	41	nummod
41	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	37	nmod
42	and	and	CC	O	41	cc
43	36	36	CD	PERCENT	44	nummod
44	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	41	conj
45	,	,	,	O	37	punct
46	respectively	respectively	RB	O	37	advmod
47	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Arias	Arias	NNP	PERSON	6	nsubj
2	and	and	CC	O	1	cc
3	the	the	DT	O	4	det
4	OAS	OAS	NNP	ORGANIZATION	1	conj
5	had	have	VBD	O	6	aux
6	laid	lay	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	groundwork	groundwork	NN	O	6	dobj
9	for	for	IN	O	11	case
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	deal	deal	NN	O	8	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	6	punct
13	but	but	CC	O	6	cc
14	the	the	DT	O	17	det
15	main	main	JJ	O	17	amod
16	sticking	sticking	NN	O	17	compound
17	point	point	NN	O	23	nsubj
18	--	--	:	O	21	punct
19	Zelaya	Zelaya	NNP	PERSON	21	nmod:poss
20	's	's	POS	O	19	case
21	reinstatement	reinstatement	NN	O	17	dep
22	--	--	:	O	21	punct
23	seemed	seem	VBD	O	6	conj
24	insurmountable	insurmountable	JJ	O	23	xcomp
25	as	as	IN	O	31	mark
26	the	the	DT	O	29	det
27	de	de	FW	O	29	amod
28	facto	facto	FW	O	27	dep
29	government	government	NN	O	31	nsubj
30	consistently	consistently	RB	O	31	advmod
31	balked	balk	VBD	O	23	advcl
32	.	.	.	O	6	punct

1	Early	early	RB	O	2	advmod
2	indications	indication	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	were	be	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	injured	injure	VBN	O	7	nsubj
7	had	have	VBD	O	3	ccomp
8	spinal	spinal	JJ	O	9	amod
9	injuries	injury	NNS	O	7	dobj
10	,	,	,	O	9	punct
11	broken	broken	JJ	O	12	amod
12	legs	leg	NNS	O	9	appos
13	,	,	,	O	12	punct
14	ankles	ankle	NNS	O	12	appos
15	,	,	,	O	12	punct
16	a	a	DT	O	17	det
17	possible	possible	JJ	O	12	appos
18	dislocated	dislocate	VBN	O	17	acl
19	shoulder	shoulder	NN	O	18	dobj
20	,	,	,	O	19	punct
21	trauma	trauma	NN	O	19	conj
22	and	and	CC	O	19	cc
23	cuts	cut	NNS	O	19	conj
24	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	It	it	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	32	ccomp
3	a	a	DT	O	4	det
4	guard	guard	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	was	be	VBD	O	6	aux
6	giving	give	VBG	O	2	ccomp
7	the	the	DT	O	9	det
8	suspect	suspect	JJ	O	9	amod
9	water	water	NN	O	6	dobj
10	when	when	WRB	O	12	advmod
11	he	he	PRP	O	12	nsubj
12	grabbed	grab	VBD	O	9	acl:relcl
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	guard	guard	NN	O	17	nmod:poss
15	's	's	POS	O	14	case
16	personal	personal	JJ	O	17	amod
17	weapon	weapon	NN	O	12	dobj
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	shot	shot	NN	O	17	appos
20	and	and	CC	O	12	cc
21	wounded	wound	VBD	O	12	conj
22	the	the	DT	O	23	det
23	guard	guard	NN	O	21	dobj
24	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
25	then	then	RB	O	26	advmod
26	shot	shoot	VBD	O	2	conj
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	investigator	investigator	NN	O	26	dobj
29	,	,	,	O	32	punct
30	the	the	DT	O	31	det
31	statement	statement	NN	O	32	nsubj
32	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
33	.	.	.	O	32	punct

1	Cook	Cook	NNP	PERSON	9	nsubj
2	,	,	,	O	1	punct
3	a	a	DT	O	6	det
4	retired	retired	JJ	O	6	amod
5	parole	parole	NN	O	6	compound
6	officer	officer	NN	O	1	appos
7	,	,	,	O	1	punct
8	has	have	VBZ	O	9	aux
9	joined	join	VBN	O	0	ROOT
10	forces	force	NNS	O	9	dobj
11	with	with	IN	O	12	case
12	candidates	candidate	NNS	O	9	nmod
13	in	in	IN	O	16	case
14	two	two	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
15	other	other	JJ	O	16	amod
16	races	race	NNS	O	12	nmod
17	to	to	TO	O	18	mark
18	form	form	VB	O	9	advcl
19	a	a	DT	O	22	det
20	``	``	``	O	22	punct
21	Progressive	Progressive	NNP	O	22	compound
22	Coalition	Coalition	NNP	O	18	dobj
23	''	''	''	O	22	punct
24	for	for	IN	O	26	case
25	City	City	NNP	ORGANIZATION	26	compound
26	Council	Council	NNP	ORGANIZATION	22	nmod
27	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	comments	comment	NNS	O	3	nsubj
3	came	come	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	in	in	IN	O	6	case
5	an	a	DT	O	6	det
6	address	address	NN	O	3	nmod
7	to	to	TO	O	9	case
8	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	9	amod
9	journalists	journalist	NNS	O	3	nmod
10	in	in	IN	O	11	case
11	Tokyo	Tokyo	NNP	LOCATION	9	nmod
12	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	NINETEEN	nineteen	CD	NUMBER	2	nummod
2	partygoers	partygoer	NNS	O	4	nsubjpass
3	were	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	taken	take	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	to	to	TO	O	6	case
6	hospital	hospital	NN	O	4	nmod
7	with	with	IN	O	9	case
8	serious	serious	JJ	O	9	amod
9	injuries	injury	NNS	O	4	nmod
10	after	after	IN	O	13	mark
11	a	a	DT	O	12	det
12	balcony	balcony	NN	O	13	nsubj
13	collapsed	collapse	VBD	O	4	advcl
14	at	at	IN	O	17	case
15	a	a	DT	O	17	det
16	Halloween	Halloween	NNP	DATE	17	compound
17	party	party	NN	O	13	nmod
18	in	in	IN	O	19	case
19	Perth	Perth	NNP	LOCATION	17	nmod
20	last	last	JJ	TIME	21	amod
21	night	night	NN	TIME	13	nmod:tmod
22	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	book	book	NN	O	4	nmod:poss
3	's	's	POS	O	2	case
4	publication	publication	NN	O	6	nsubj
5	has	have	VBZ	O	6	aux
6	stung	sting	VBN	O	0	ROOT
7	many	many	JJ	O	10	amod
8	Chinese	chinese	JJ	MISC	10	amod
9	sports	sport	NNS	O	10	compound
10	fans	fan	NNS	O	6	dobj
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	one	one	CD	NUMBER	15	nsubj
13	of	of	IN	O	14	case
14	whom	whom	WP	O	12	nmod
15	wrote	write	VBD	O	10	acl:relcl
16	plaintively	plaintively	RB	O	15	advmod
17	on	on	IN	O	19	case
18	a	a	DT	O	19	det
19	sports	sport	NNS	O	16	nmod
20	Internet	internet	NN	MISC	22	compound
21	bulletin	bulletin	NN	O	22	compound
22	board	board	NN	O	15	dobj
23	:	:	:	O	22	punct
24	``	``	``	O	22	punct
25	Even	even	RB	O	34	advmod
26	if	if	IN	O	34	mark
27	some	some	DT	O	34	nsubj
28	of	of	IN	O	30	case
29	the	the	DT	O	30	det
30	things	thing	NNS	O	27	nmod
31	he	he	PRP	O	32	nsubj
32	said	say	VBD	O	30	acl:relcl
33	were	be	VBD	O	34	cop
34	true	true	JJ	O	38	dep
35	,	,	,	O	38	punct
36	did	do	VBD	O	38	aux
37	he	he	PRP	O	38	nsubj
38	have	have	VB	O	22	dep
39	to	to	TO	O	40	mark
40	reveal	reveal	VB	O	38	xcomp
41	them	they	PRP	O	40	dobj
42	?	?	.	O	38	punct
43	''	''	''	O	22	punct

1	While	while	IN	O	3	mark
2	CIT	CIT	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	nsubj
3	said	say	VBD	O	19	advcl
4	it	it	PRP	O	7	nsubj
5	's	be	VBZ	O	7	aux
6	still	still	RB	O	7	advmod
7	counting	count	VBG	O	3	ccomp
8	the	the	DT	O	11	advmod
9	more	more	JJR	O	11	advmod
10	than	than	IN	O	9	mwe
11	150,000	150,000	CD	NUMBER	12	nummod
12	ballots	ballot	NNS	O	7	dobj
13	,	,	,	O	19	punct
14	bond	bond	NN	O	18	compound
15	and	and	CC	O	14	cc
16	credit-default	credit-default	NN	O	14	conj
17	swap	swap	NN	O	18	compound
18	prices	price	NNS	O	19	nsubj
19	show	show	VBP	O	0	ROOT
20	that	that	IN	O	23	mark
21	investors	investor	NNS	O	23	nsubj
22	are	be	VBP	O	23	aux
23	betting	bet	VBG	O	19	ccomp
24	the	the	DT	O	25	det
25	lender	lender	NN	O	27	nsubj
26	will	will	MD	O	27	aux
27	file	file	VB	O	23	ccomp
28	for	for	IN	O	30	case
29	court	court	NN	O	30	compound
30	protection	protection	NN	O	27	nmod
31	.	.	.	O	19	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	addition	addition	NN	O	8	nmod
3	,	,	,	O	8	punct
4	about	about	IN	O	6	case
5	100,000	100,000	CD	NUMBER	6	nummod
6	people	people	NNS	O	8	nmod
7	annually	annually	RB	SET	8	advmod
8	apply	apply	VBP	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	see	see	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	their	they	PRP$	O	13	nmod:poss
12	own	own	JJ	O	13	amod
13	files	file	NNS	O	10	dobj
14	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	A	a	DT	O	2	det
2	search	search	NN	O	5	nsubj
3	was	be	VBD	O	5	aux
4	also	also	RB	O	5	advmod
5	continuing	continue	VBG	O	16	ccomp
6	Saturday	Saturday	NNP	DATE	5	dobj
7	for	for	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	missing	miss	VBG	O	10	amod
10	boater	boater	NN	O	6	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	10	punct
12	David	David	NNP	PERSON	13	compound
13	Jines	Jines	NNP	PERSON	10	appos
14	,	,	,	O	16	punct
15	Castillo	Castillo	NNP	PERSON	16	nsubj
16	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
17	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Catch	catch	VB	O	0	ROOT
2	our	we	PRP$	O	3	nmod:poss
3	blog	blog	NN	O	1	dobj
4	at	at	IN	O	5	case
5	www.sfgate.com/matierandross	www.sfgate.com/matierandross	NN	O	1	nmod
6	.	.	.	O	1	punct

1	His	he	PRP$	O	2	nmod:poss
2	body	body	NN	O	4	nsubjpass
3	was	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	discovered	discover	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	last	last	JJ	DATE	6	amod
6	Tuesday	Tuesday	NNP	DATE	4	nmod:tmod
7	at	at	IN	DATE	9	case
8	about	about	IN	DATE	9	case
9	8pm	8pm	NN	DATE	4	nmod
10	.	.	.	DATE	4	punct

1	However	however	RB	O	9	advmod
2	,	,	,	O	9	punct
3	neither	neither	CC	O	4	cc:preconj
4	electoral	electoral	JJ	O	9	nsubj
5	nor	nor	CC	O	4	cc
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	constitution	constitution	NN	O	4	conj
8	specifically	specifically	RB	O	9	advmod
9	address	address	VBP	O	0	ROOT
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	issue	issue	NN	O	9	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	14	case
13	a	a	DT	O	14	det
14	candidate	candidate	NN	O	11	nmod
15	who	who	WP	O	19	nsubj
16	does	do	VBZ	O	19	aux
17	not	not	RB	O	19	neg
18	formally	formally	RB	O	19	advmod
19	withdraw	withdraw	VB	O	14	acl:relcl
20	but	but	CC	O	9	cc
21	urges	urge	VBZ	O	9	conj
22	supporters	supporter	NNS	O	21	dobj
23	to	to	TO	O	24	case
24	boycott	boycott	NN	O	21	nmod
25	the	the	DT	O	26	det
26	polls	poll	NNS	O	24	dep
27	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	Kirk	Kirk	NNP	PERSON	4	nsubj
2	``	``	``	O	4	punct
3	has	have	VBZ	O	4	aux
4	fit	fit	VBN	O	13	ccomp
5	in	in	IN	O	4	nmod
6	,	,	,	O	4	punct
7	seamlessly	seamlessly	RB	O	8	advmod
8	and	and	CC	O	4	advmod
9	superbly	superbly	RB	O	8	advmod
10	,	,	,	O	13	punct
11	''	''	''	O	13	punct
12	Kerry	Kerry	NNP	PERSON	13	nsubj
13	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
14	.	.	.	O	13	punct

1	Senate	Senate	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	compound
2	Democrats	Democrats	NNPS	O	3	nsubj
3	want	want	VBP	O	0	ROOT
4	to	to	TO	O	5	mark
5	extend	extend	VB	O	3	xcomp
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	credit	credit	NN	O	5	dobj
8	through	through	IN	O	9	case
9	April	April	NNP	DATE	5	nmod
10	and	and	CC	O	5	cc
11	expand	expand	VB	O	5	conj
12	it	it	PRP	O	11	dobj
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	allow	allow	VB	O	11	xcomp
15	higher-income	higher-income	JJ	O	16	amod
16	Americans	Americans	NNPS	MISC	14	dobj
17	and	and	CC	O	16	cc
18	some	some	DT	O	16	conj
19	who	who	WP	O	24	dobj
20	already	already	RB	O	22	advmod
21	own	own	JJ	O	22	amod
22	homes	home	NNS	O	24	nsubj
23	to	to	TO	O	24	mark
24	qualify	qualify	VB	O	18	acl:relcl
25	for	for	IN	O	27	case
26	the	the	DT	O	27	det
27	incentive	incentive	NN	O	24	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	other	other	JJ	O	3	amod
3	candidates	candidate	NNS	O	8	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	6	punct
5	he	he	PRP	O	6	nsubj
6	said	say	VBD	O	8	parataxis
7	,	,	,	O	6	punct
8	seemed	seem	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	pander	pander	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	at	at	IN	O	12	case
12	times	time	NNS	O	10	nmod
13	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	8	cc
2	the	the	DT	O	4	det
3	Middle	Middle	NNP	LOCATION	4	compound
4	East	East	NNP	LOCATION	8	nsubj
5	is	be	VBZ	O	8	cop
6	a	a	DT	O	8	det
7	growing	grow	VBG	O	8	amod
8	market	market	NN	O	0	ROOT
9	so	so	IN	O	12	mark
10	it	it	PRP	O	12	nsubj
11	would	would	MD	O	12	aux
12	make	make	VB	O	8	dep
13	sense	sense	NN	O	12	dobj
14	for	for	IN	O	15	case
15	them	they	PRP	O	13	nmod
16	to	to	TO	O	17	mark
17	try	try	VB	O	12	advcl
18	it	it	PRP	O	17	dobj
19	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	``	``	``	O	5	punct
2	They	they	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	were	be	VBD	O	5	cop
4	just	just	RB	O	5	advmod
5	stronger	stronger	JJR	O	0	ROOT
6	.	.	.	O	5	punct
7	They	they	PRP	O	5	parataxis
8	had	have	VBD	O	7	dep
9	more	more	JJR	O	10	amod
10	people	people	NNS	O	8	dobj
11	.	.	.	O	5	punct
12	''	''	''	O	5	punct

1	``	``	``	O	24	punct
2	I	I	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	will	will	MD	O	5	aux
4	not	not	RB	O	5	neg
5	say	say	VB	O	24	ccomp
6	anything	anything	NN	O	5	dobj
7	that	that	WDT	O	10	nsubj
8	could	could	MD	O	10	aux
9	-LSB-	-lsb-	-LRB-	O	10	punct
10	put	put	VB	O	6	acl:relcl
11	-RSB-	-rsb-	-RRB-	O	12	punct
12	any	any	DT	O	10	nmod
13	of	of	IN	O	16	case
14	my	my	PRP$	O	16	nmod:poss
15	British	british	JJ	MISC	16	amod
16	colleagues	colleague	NNS	O	12	nmod
17	in	in	IN	O	20	case
18	a	a	DT	O	20	det
19	difficult	difficult	JJ	O	20	amod
20	position	position	NN	O	10	nmod
21	,	,	,	O	24	punct
22	''	''	''	O	24	punct
23	he	he	PRP	O	24	nsubj
24	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
25	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	Li	Li	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	spoke	speak	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	during	during	IN	O	5	case
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	meeting	meeting	NN	O	2	nmod
6	with	with	IN	O	8	case
7	Anna	Anna	NNP	PERSON	8	compound
8	Bligh	Bligh	NNP	PERSON	2	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	8	punct
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	premier	premier	NN	O	8	appos
12	of	of	IN	O	15	case
13	Australia	Australia	NNP	LOCATION	15	nmod:poss
14	's	's	POS	O	13	case
15	state	state	NN	O	11	nmod
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	Queensland	Queensland	NNP	LOCATION	15	nmod
18	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	latest	latest	JJS	O	3	amod
3	data	datum	NNS	O	4	nsubj
4	adds	add	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	fuel	fuel	NN	O	4	dobj
6	to	to	TO	O	8	case
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	reports	report	NNS	O	4	nmod
9	that	that	IN	O	16	mark
10	the	the	DT	O	14	det
11	over-stretched	over-stretched	JJ	O	14	amod
12	well-heeled	well-heeled	JJ	O	14	amod
13	middle	middle	JJ	O	14	amod
14	classes	class	NNS	O	16	nsubj
15	are	be	VBP	O	16	aux
16	turning	turn	VBG	O	4	ccomp
17	to	to	TO	O	19	case
18	the	the	DT	O	19	det
19	stimulant	stimulant	NN	O	16	nmod
20	to	to	TO	O	22	case
21	``	``	``	O	22	punct
22	power	power	NN	O	16	nmod
23	them	they	PRP	O	22	dep
24	up	up	RP	O	16	advmod
25	''	''	''	O	24	punct
26	over	over	IN	O	28	case
27	hectic	hectic	JJ	O	28	amod
28	weekends	weekend	NNS	SET	24	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	``	``	``	O	3	punct
2	But	but	CC	O	3	cc
3	will	will	MD	O	0	ROOT
4	it	it	PRP	O	3	dobj
5	pick	pick	VB	O	3	dep
6	back	back	RB	O	7	advmod
7	up	up	RB	O	5	advmod
8	to	to	TO	O	11	dep
9	above	above	IN	O	11	case
10	normal	normal	JJ	O	11	amod
11	activity	activity	NN	O	16	dep
12	?	?	.	O	11	punct
13	No	no	DT	O	14	neg
14	one	one	NN	NUMBER	16	nsubj
15	can	can	MD	O	16	aux
16	say	say	VB	O	7	advcl
17	.	.	.	O	3	punct
18	''	''	''	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	accords	accord	NNS	O	4	nsubjpass
3	were	be	VBD	O	4	auxpass
4	disclosed	disclose	VBN	O	0	ROOT
5	the	the	DT	DATE	6	det
6	day	day	NN	DATE	4	nmod:tmod
7	after	after	IN	O	9	case
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	deadline	deadline	NN	O	4	nmod
10	passed	pass	VBN	O	9	acl
11	for	for	IN	O	12	case
12	CIT	CIT	NNP	ORGANIZATION	10	nmod
13	to	to	TO	O	14	mark
14	solicit	solicit	VB	O	10	xcomp
15	votes	vote	NNS	O	14	dobj
16	in	in	IN	O	17	case
17	support	support	NN	O	14	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	21	case
19	either	either	CC	O	21	dep
20	a	a	DT	O	21	det
21	$	$	$	MONEY	17	nmod
22	30	30	CD	MONEY	23	compound
23	billion	billion	CD	MONEY	21	nummod
24	out	out	IN	O	21	advmod
25	-	-	:	O	21	punct
26	of-court	of-court	JJ	O	28	amod
27	debt	debt	NN	O	28	compound
28	exchange	exchange	NN	O	21	dep
29	or	or	CC	O	17	cc
30	a	a	DT	O	32	det
31	prepackaged	prepackaged	JJ	O	32	amod
32	bankruptcy	bankruptcy	NN	O	17	conj
33	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	``	``	``	O	14	punct
2	When	when	WRB	O	6	advmod
3	you	you	PRP	O	6	nsubj
4	do	do	VBP	O	6	aux
5	n't	not	RB	O	6	neg
6	share	share	VB	O	14	advcl
7	it	it	PRP	O	6	dobj
8	,	,	,	O	14	punct
9	you	you	PRP	O	14	nsubj
10	're	be	VBP	O	14	aux
11	kind	kind	NN	O	14	advmod
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	really	really	RB	O	11	advcl
14	abusing	abuse	VBG	O	0	ROOT
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	reason	reason	NN	O	14	dobj
17	it	it	PRP	O	19	nsubjpass
18	was	be	VBD	O	19	auxpass
19	given	give	VBN	O	16	acl:relcl
20	to	to	TO	O	21	case
21	you	you	PRP	O	19	nmod
22	.	.	.	O	14	punct
23	''	''	''	O	14	punct

1	Downing	Downing	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Street	Street	NNP	O	5	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	5	aux
4	discreetly	discreetly	RB	O	5	advmod
5	supporting	support	VBG	O	0	ROOT
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	8	amod
8	secretary	secretary	NN	O	5	dobj
9	as	as	IN	O	11	case
10	a	a	DT	O	11	det
11	candidate	candidate	NN	O	5	nmod
12	for	for	IN	O	15	case
13	EU	EU	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
14	high	high	JJ	O	15	amod
15	representative	representative	NN	O	11	nmod
16	for	for	IN	O	18	case
17	foreign	foreign	JJ	O	18	amod
18	affairs	affair	NNS	O	5	nmod
19	,	,	,	O	5	punct
20	with	with	IN	O	23	mark
21	Tony	Tony	NNP	PERSON	22	compound
22	Blair	Blair	NNP	PERSON	23	nsubj
23	looking	look	VBG	O	5	advcl
24	increasingly	increasingly	RB	O	25	advmod
25	unlikely	unlikely	JJ	O	23	xcomp
26	to	to	TO	O	27	mark
27	win	win	VB	O	25	xcomp
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	presidency	presidency	NN	O	27	dobj
30	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	Kirk	Kirk	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	given	give	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	few	few	JJ	O	5	amod
5	speeches	speech	NNS	O	3	dobj
6	,	,	,	O	3	punct
7	limited	limit	VBD	O	3	conj
8	his	he	PRP$	O	9	nmod:poss
9	press	press	NN	O	10	nsubj
10	releases	release	VBZ	O	7	ccomp
11	to	to	TO	O	15	case
12	a	a	DT	O	15	det
13	few	few	JJ	O	15	amod
14	nuts-and-bolts	nuts-and-bolts	JJ	O	15	amod
15	issues	issue	NNS	O	10	nmod
16	,	,	,	O	3	punct
17	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
18	shunned	shun	VBD	O	3	conj
19	almost	almost	RB	O	20	advmod
20	all	all	DT	O	21	nummod
21	requests	request	NNS	O	18	dobj
22	for	for	IN	O	23	case
23	interviews	interview	NNS	O	18	nmod
24	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	White	White	NNP	ORGANIZATION	3	compound
3	House	House	NNP	ORGANIZATION	4	nsubj
4	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
5	on	on	IN	O	6	case
6	Friday	Friday	NNP	DATE	11	nmod
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	stimulus	stimulus	NN	O	11	nsubj
9	had	have	VBD	O	11	aux
10	directly	directly	RB	O	11	advmod
11	saved	save	VBN	O	4	ccomp
12	or	or	CC	O	11	cc
13	created	create	VBN	O	11	conj
14	more	more	JJR	O	16	advmod
15	than	than	IN	O	14	mwe
16	640,000	640,000	CD	NUMBER	17	nummod
17	jobs	job	NNS	O	11	dobj
18	so	so	RB	O	19	advmod
19	far	far	RB	O	17	advmod
20	,	,	,	O	11	punct
21	based	base	VBN	O	23	case
22	on	on	IN	O	23	case
23	data	datum	NNS	O	11	advcl
24	about	about	IN	O	27	mark
25	who	who	WP	O	27	nsubj
26	had	have	VBD	O	27	aux
27	received	receive	VBN	O	23	acl
28	loans	loan	NNS	O	27	dobj
29	or	or	CC	O	28	cc
30	grants	grant	NNS	O	28	conj
31	through	through	IN	O	34	case
32	the	the	DT	O	34	det
33	American	american	JJ	MISC	34	amod
34	Recovery	recovery	NN	MISC	27	nmod
35	and	and	CC	O	34	cc
36	Reinvestment	Reinvestment	NNP	O	37	compound
37	Act	Act	NNP	O	34	conj
38	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	Vaz	Vaz	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	:	:	:	O	2	punct
4	``	``	``	O	2	punct
5	As	as	IN	O	10	case
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	country	country	NN	O	10	nmod:poss
8	's	's	POS	O	7	case
9	top	top	JJ	O	10	amod
10	adviser	adviser	NN	O	17	nmod
11	on	on	IN	O	13	case
12	the	the	DT	O	13	det
13	issue	issue	NN	O	10	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	17	punct
15	he	he	PRP	O	17	nsubj
16	is	be	VBZ	O	17	aux
17	implying	imply	VBG	O	2	parataxis
18	to	to	TO	O	21	case
19	many	many	JJ	O	21	amod
20	young	young	JJ	O	21	amod
21	people	people	NNS	O	17	nmod
22	that	that	WDT	O	27	dobj
23	cannabis	cannabis	NN	O	27	nsubj
24	is	be	VBZ	O	27	cop
25	not	not	RB	O	27	neg
26	particularly	particularly	RB	O	27	advmod
27	dangerous	dangerous	JJ	O	21	acl:relcl
28	.	.	.	O	2	punct
29	''	''	''	O	2	punct

1	In	in	IN	O	2	case
2	June	June	NNP	DATE	8	nmod
3	this	this	DT	DATE	4	det
4	year	year	NN	DATE	8	nmod:tmod
5	,	,	,	O	8	punct
6	the	the	DT	O	7	det
7	ministry	ministry	NN	O	8	nsubj
8	started	start	VBD	O	0	ROOT
9	to	to	TO	O	10	mark
10	levy	levy	VB	O	8	xcomp
11	a	a	DT	O	13	det
12	security	security	NN	O	13	compound
13	deposit	deposit	NN	O	10	dobj
14	,	,	,	O	8	punct
15	as	as	IN	O	19	case
16	a	a	DT	O	19	det
17	temporary	temporary	JJ	O	19	amod
18	anti-dumping	anti-dumping	JJ	O	19	amod
19	measure	measure	NN	O	8	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	8	punct
21	on	on	IN	O	23	case
22	adipic	adipic	JJ	O	23	amod
23	acid	acid	NN	O	8	nmod
24	imported	import	VBN	O	23	acl
25	from	from	IN	O	28	case
26	the	the	DT	O	28	det
27	three	three	CD	NUMBER	28	nummod
28	countries	country	NNS	O	24	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	new	new	JJ	O	3	amod
3	rules	rule	NNS	O	5	nsubjpass
4	were	be	VBD	O	5	auxpass
5	signed	sign	VBN	O	0	ROOT
6	Friday	Friday	NNP	DATE	5	nmod:tmod
7	by	by	IN	O	9	case
8	the	the	DT	O	9	det
9	director	director	NN	O	5	nmod
10	of	of	IN	O	12	case
11	the	the	DT	O	12	det
12	Department	Department	NNP	ORGANIZATION	9	nmod
13	of	of	IN	ORGANIZATION	15	case
14	General	General	NNP	ORGANIZATION	15	compound
15	Administration	Administration	NNP	ORGANIZATION	12	nmod
16	.	.	.	O	5	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	government	government	NN	O	4	nsubj
3	now	now	RB	DATE	4	advmod
4	supplies	supply	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
5	water	water	NN	O	4	dobj
6	once	once	RB	DATE	4	advmod
7	every	every	DT	SET	9	det
8	45	45	CD	SET	9	nummod
9	days	day	NNS	SET	4	nmod:tmod
10	in	in	IN	O	13	case
11	some	some	DT	O	13	det
12	urban	urban	JJ	O	13	amod
13	areas	area	NNS	O	9	nmod
14	,	,	,	O	4	punct
15	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
16	in	in	IN	O	17	case
17	much	much	JJ	O	22	nmod
18	of	of	IN	O	20	case
19	the	the	DT	O	20	det
20	country	country	NN	O	17	nmod
21	there	there	EX	O	22	expl
22	is	be	VBZ	O	4	conj
23	no	no	DT	O	26	neg
24	public	public	JJ	O	26	amod
25	water	water	NN	O	26	compound
26	supply	supply	NN	O	22	nsubj
27	at	at	IN	O	28	case
28	all	all	DT	O	22	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	4	punct

1	They	they	PRP	O	3	nsubjpass
2	were	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	detained	detain	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	for	for	IN	O	5	mark
5	questioning	question	VBG	O	3	advcl
6	and	and	CC	O	3	cc
7	it	it	PRP	O	10	nsubj
8	was	be	VBD	O	10	cop
9	not	not	RB	O	10	neg
10	clear	clear	JJ	O	3	conj
11	if	if	IN	O	14	mark
12	they	they	PRP	O	14	nsubjpass
13	were	be	VBD	O	14	auxpass
14	suspected	suspect	VBN	O	10	advcl
15	of	of	IN	O	16	case
16	collusion	collusion	NN	O	14	nmod
17	or	or	CC	O	16	cc
18	negligence	negligence	NN	O	16	conj
19	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	``	``	``	O	24	punct
2	This	this	DT	O	6	nsubj
3	is	be	VBZ	O	6	cop
4	the	the	DT	O	6	det
5	first	first	JJ	ORDINAL	6	amod
6	time	time	NN	O	24	ccomp
7	that	that	IN	O	13	mark
8	somebody	somebody	NN	O	13	nsubj
9	in	in	IN	O	12	case
10	the	the	DT	O	12	det
11	high	high	JJ	O	12	amod
12	ranks	rank	NNS	O	8	nmod
13	told	tell	VBD	O	6	ccomp
14	the	the	DT	O	16	det
15	inside	inside	JJ	O	16	amod
16	story	story	NN	O	13	dobj
17	of	of	IN	O	21	case
18	the	the	DT	O	21	det
19	Chinese	chinese	JJ	MISC	21	amod
20	sports	sport	NNS	O	21	compound
21	world	world	NN	O	16	nmod
22	,	,	,	O	24	punct
23	''	''	''	O	24	punct
24	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
25	Xu	Xu	NNP	PERSON	26	compound
26	Jicheng	Jicheng	NNP	PERSON	24	nsubj
27	,	,	,	O	26	punct
28	a	a	DT	O	31	det
29	prominent	prominent	JJ	O	31	amod
30	basketball	basketball	NN	O	31	compound
31	commentator	commentator	NN	O	26	appos
32	who	who	WP	O	35	nsubj
33	was	be	VBD	O	35	cop
34	deputy	deputy	JJ	O	35	amod
35	director	director	NN	O	31	acl:relcl
36	of	of	IN	O	38	case
37	media	media	NNS	O	38	compound
38	operations	operation	NNS	O	35	nmod
39	for	for	IN	O	41	case
40	Beijing	Beijing	NNP	LOCATION	41	compound
41	Olympics	Olympics	NNPS	MISC	38	nmod
42	organizing	organize	VBG	O	41	acl
43	committee	committee	NN	O	42	dobj
44	.	.	.	O	24	punct

1	Houston	Houston	NNP	LOCATION	3	nsubj
2	has	have	VBZ	O	3	aux
3	seen	see	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	impressive	impressive	JJ	O	6	amod
5	car	car	NN	O	6	compound
6	collections	collection	NNS	O	3	dobj
7	before	before	RB	O	3	advmod
8	,	,	,	O	3	punct
9	including	include	VBG	O	10	case
10	those	those	DT	O	3	nmod
11	of	of	IN	O	16	case
12	shopping	shopping	NN	O	16	compound
13	center	center	NN	O	16	compound
14	developer	developer	NN	O	16	compound
15	Jerry	Jerry	NNP	PERSON	16	compound
16	Moore	Moore	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	10	punct
18	auto	auto	NN	O	20	compound
19	dealer	dealer	NN	O	20	compound
20	Sterling	sterling	NN	PERSON	10	appos
21	McCall	McCall	NNP	PERSON	28	compound
22	and	and	CC	O	21	cc
23	former	former	JJ	O	21	conj
24	Shell	Shell	NNP	ORGANIZATION	28	compound
25	Oil	Oil	NNP	ORGANIZATION	28	compound
26	CEO	CEO	NNP	O	28	compound
27	John	John	NNP	PERSON	28	compound
28	Bookout	Bookout	NNP	PERSON	20	dep
29	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Anti-collision	anti-collision	JJ	O	2	amod
2	lights	light	NNS	O	8	nsubjpass
3	on	on	IN	O	5	case
4	Sea	Sea	NNP	ORGANIZATION	5	compound
5	Kings	Kings	NNPS	ORGANIZATION	2	nmod
6	had	have	VBD	O	8	aux
7	been	be	VBN	O	8	auxpass
8	replaced	replace	VBN	O	0	ROOT
9	with	with	IN	O	11	case
10	strobe	strobe	NN	O	11	compound
11	lights	light	NNS	O	8	nmod
12	that	that	IN	O	14	nsubj
13	``	``	``	O	14	punct
14	blinded	blind	VBD	O	11	acl:relcl
15	the	the	DT	O	16	det
16	pilots	pilot	NNS	O	14	dobj
17	at	at	IN	O	19	case
18	low	low	JJ	O	19	amod
19	level	level	NN	O	14	nmod
20	,	,	,	O	14	punct
21	over	over	IN	O	22	case
22	water	water	NN	O	14	nmod
23	or	or	CC	O	22	cc
24	in	in	IN	O	25	case
25	mist	mist	NN	O	22	conj
26	-	-	:	O	25	punct
27	so	so	IN	O	29	mark
28	they	they	PRP	O	29	nsubj
29	switched	switch	VBD	O	25	dep
30	them	they	PRP	O	29	dobj
31	off	off	RP	O	29	compound:prt
32	''	''	''	O	14	punct
33	.	.	.	O	8	punct

1	Bradford	Bradford	NNP	PERSON	16	dep
2	's	's	POS	O	1	case
3	resume	resume	VB	O	5	nsubj
4	could	could	MD	O	5	aux
5	help	help	VB	O	16	parataxis
6	him	he	PRP	O	5	dobj
7	with	with	IN	O	8	case
8	voters	voter	NNS	O	5	nmod
9	concerned	concern	VBN	O	8	acl
10	about	about	IN	O	11	case
11	crime	crime	NN	O	9	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	5	punct
13	but	but	CC	O	16	nsubj
14	he	he	PRP	O	16	nsubj
15	is	be	VBZ	O	16	cop
16	vulnerable	vulnerable	JJ	O	0	ROOT
17	because	because	IN	O	25	mark
18	problems	problem	NNS	O	25	nsubj
19	with	with	IN	O	24	case
20	the	the	DT	O	21	det
21	city	city	NN	O	24	nmod:poss
22	's	's	POS	O	21	case
23	crime	crime	NN	O	24	compound
24	lab	lab	NN	O	18	nmod
25	emerged	emerge	VBD	O	16	advcl
26	under	under	IN	O	28	case
27	his	he	PRP$	O	28	nmod:poss
28	watch	watch	NN	O	25	nmod
29	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	``	``	``	O	15	punct
2	It	it	PRP	O	5	nsubj
3	's	be	VBZ	O	5	cop
4	mathematically	mathematically	RB	O	5	advmod
5	impossible	impossible	JJ	O	15	ccomp
6	at	at	IN	O	8	case
7	this	this	DT	O	8	det
8	point	point	NN	O	5	nmod
9	for	for	IN	O	10	case
10	this	this	DT	O	8	nmod
11	to	to	TO	O	12	mark
12	pass	pass	VB	O	5	xcomp
13	,	,	,	O	15	punct
14	''	''	''	O	15	punct
15	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
16	Gary	Gary	NNP	PERSON	17	compound
17	Walkowicz	Walkowicz	NNP	PERSON	15	dobj
18	,	,	,	O	17	punct
19	a	a	DT	O	20	det
20	member	member	NN	O	17	appos
21	of	of	IN	O	25	case
22	the	the	DT	O	25	det
23	UAW	UAW	NNP	ORGANIZATION	25	compound
24	bargaining	bargaining	NN	O	25	compound
25	committee	committee	NN	O	20	nmod
26	at	at	IN	O	33	case
27	a	a	DT	O	33	det
28	Dearborn	Dearborn	NNP	LOCATION	33	dep
29	,	,	,	O	28	punct
30	Michigan	Michigan	NNP	LOCATION	28	dep
31	,	,	,	O	28	punct
32	truck	truck	NN	O	33	compound
33	plant	plant	NN	O	15	nmod
34	that	that	WDT	O	35	nsubj
35	rejected	reject	VBD	O	33	acl:relcl
36	the	the	DT	O	37	det
37	deal	deal	NN	O	35	dobj
38	on	on	IN	O	39	case
39	Oct.	Oct.	NNP	DATE	35	nmod
40	30	30	CD	DATE	39	nummod
41	with	with	IN	O	44	case
42	a	a	DT	O	44	det
43	93	93	CD	PERCENT	44	nummod
44	percent	percent	NN	PERCENT	35	nmod
45	no	no	DT	O	46	neg
46	vote	vote	NN	O	15	nsubj
47	.	.	.	O	15	punct

1	ValueAct	ValueAct	NNP	ORGANIZATION	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	it	it	PRP	O	4	nsubj
4	requires	require	VBZ	O	2	ccomp
5	all	all	DT	O	6	det
6	employees	employee	NNS	O	4	dobj
7	to	to	TO	O	8	mark
8	participate	participate	VB	O	4	xcomp
9	in	in	IN	O	11	case
10	rigorous	rigorous	JJ	O	11	amod
11	training	training	NN	O	8	nmod
12	on	on	IN	O	15	mark
13	how	how	WRB	O	15	advmod
14	to	to	TO	O	15	mark
15	handle	handle	VB	O	8	advcl
16	non-public	non-public	JJ	O	17	amod
17	information	information	NN	O	15	dobj
18	and	and	CC	O	4	cc
19	immediately	immediately	RB	O	20	advmod
20	told	tell	VBD	O	4	conj
21	investors	investor	NNS	O	20	dobj
22	about	about	IN	O	24	case
23	the	the	DT	O	24	det
24	probe	probe	NN	O	21	nmod
25	into	into	IN	O	26	case
26	Yee	Yee	NNP	PERSON	20	nmod
27	in	in	IN	O	28	case
28	2008	2008	CD	DATE	26	nmod
29	and	and	CC	O	2	cc
30	then	then	RB	O	31	advmod
31	wrote	write	VBD	O	2	conj
32	to	to	TO	O	33	case
33	them	they	PRP	O	31	nmod
34	on	on	IN	O	35	case
35	Friday	Friday	NNP	DATE	33	nmod
36	to	to	TO	O	37	case
37	detail	detail	NN	O	31	nmod
38	the	the	DT	O	39	det
39	charges	charge	NNS	O	2	dobj
40	against	against	IN	O	41	case
41	him	he	PRP	O	39	nmod
42	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	``	``	``	O	7	punct
2	A	a	DT	O	3	det
3	lot	lot	NN	O	7	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	5	case
5	people	people	NNS	O	3	nmod
6	are	be	VBP	O	7	aux
7	getting	get	VBG	O	0	ROOT
8	money	money	NN	O	7	dobj
9	from	from	IN	O	11	case
10	the	the	DT	O	11	det
11	government	government	NN	O	7	nmod
12	,	,	,	O	15	punct
13	''	''	''	O	15	punct
14	he	he	PRP	O	15	nsubj
15	said	say	VBD	O	7	dep
16	,	,	,	O	15	punct
17	``	``	``	O	15	punct
18	so	so	IN	O	7	dep
19	it	it	PRP	O	23	nsubj
20	's	be	VBZ	O	23	cop
21	not	not	RB	O	23	neg
22	just	just	RB	O	23	advmod
23	embassies	embassy	NNS	O	29	dep
24	buying	buy	VBG	O	23	acl
25	.	.	.	O	23	punct
26	Now	now	RB	DATE	28	advmod
27	regular	regular	JJ	O	28	amod
28	people	people	NNS	O	29	nsubj
29	buy	buy	VBP	O	7	parataxis
30	as	as	RB	O	29	advmod
31	well	well	RB	O	30	mwe
32	.	.	.	O	7	punct
33	''	''	''	O	7	punct

1	Clausen	Clausen	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubjpass
2	was	be	VBD	O	3	auxpass
3	replaced	replace	VBN	O	0	ROOT
4	by	by	IN	O	7	case
5	sophomore	sophomore	NN	O	7	compound
6	Dayne	Dayne	NNP	PERSON	7	compound
7	Crist	Crist	NNP	PERSON	3	nmod
8	,	,	,	O	7	punct
9	who	who	WP	O	10	nsubj
10	went	go	VBD	O	7	acl:relcl
11	2	2	CD	NUMBER	10	dobj
12	of	of	IN	O	13	case
13	6	6	CD	NUMBER	11	nmod
14	for	for	IN	O	16	case
15	69	69	CD	NUMBER	16	nummod
16	yards	yard	NNS	O	10	nmod
17	and	and	CC	O	10	cc
18	had	have	VBD	O	10	conj
19	a	a	DT	O	21	det
20	64-yard	64-yard	JJ	O	21	amod
21	touchdown	touchdown	NN	O	18	dobj
22	to	to	TO	O	24	case
23	John	John	NNP	PERSON	24	compound
24	Goodman	Goodman	NNP	PERSON	21	nmod
25	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	2	compound
2	Lodin	Lodin	NNP	PERSON	3	nsubj
3	denies	deny	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
4	allegations	allegation	NNS	O	3	dobj
5	that	that	IN	O	7	mark
6	he	he	PRP	O	7	nsubj
7	favoured	favour	VBD	O	3	ccomp
8	Mr	Mr	NNP	O	9	compound
9	Karzai	Karzai	NNP	PERSON	7	dobj
10	.	.	.	O	3	punct

1	Using	use	VBG	O	12	advcl
2	a	a	DT	O	3	det
3	computer	computer	NN	O	1	dobj
4	at	at	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	salon	salon	NN	O	1	nmod
7	,	,	,	O	12	punct
8	Moreno	Moreno	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
9	and	and	CC	O	8	cc
10	her	she	PRP$	O	11	nmod:poss
11	niece	niece	NN	O	8	conj
12	found	find	VBD	O	0	ROOT
13	Bianca	Bianca	NNP	PERSON	28	nsubj
14	,	,	,	O	13	punct
15	including	include	VBG	O	17	case
16	her	she	PRP$	O	17	nmod:poss
17	Aug.	Aug.	NNP	DATE	13	nmod
18	19	19	CD	DATE	17	nummod
19	,	,	,	DATE	17	punct
20	1993	1993	CD	DATE	17	nummod
21	,	,	,	O	17	punct
22	birth	birth	NN	O	23	compound
23	date	date	NN	O	17	conj
24	and	and	CC	O	17	cc
25	full	full	JJ	O	26	amod
26	name	name	NN	O	17	conj
27	,	,	,	O	13	punct
28	listed	list	VBN	O	12	ccomp
29	on	on	IN	O	35	case
30	a	a	DT	O	35	det
31	1999	1999	CD	DATE	35	nummod
32	Mexican	mexican	JJ	MISC	35	amod
33	government	government	NN	O	35	compound
34	population	population	NN	O	35	compound
35	registry	registry	NN	O	28	nmod
36	there	there	RB	O	28	advmod
37	.	.	.	O	12	punct

1	Yuan	yuan	NN	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	drops	drop	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
3	other	other	JJ	O	4	amod
4	tidbits	tidbit	NNS	O	2	dobj
5	from	from	IN	O	8	case
6	the	the	DT	O	8	det
7	backroom	backroom	NN	O	8	compound
8	discussions	discussion	NNS	O	2	nmod
9	of	of	IN	O	12	case
10	China	China	NNP	LOCATION	12	nmod:poss
11	's	's	POS	O	10	case
12	Olympics	Olympics	NNPS	MISC	8	nmod
13	bid	bid	NN	O	12	dep
14	,	,	,	O	12	punct
15	including	include	VBG	O	19	case
16	how	how	WRB	O	19	advmod
17	the	the	DT	O	18	det
18	nation	nation	NN	O	19	nsubj
19	sought	seek	VBD	O	12	acl
20	to	to	TO	O	21	mark
21	deflect	deflect	VB	O	19	xcomp
22	criticism	criticism	NN	O	21	dobj
23	of	of	IN	O	27	case
24	its	its	PRP$	O	27	nmod:poss
25	human	human	JJ	O	27	amod
26	rights	rights	NNS	O	27	compound
27	record	record	NN	O	22	nmod
28	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Atkins	Atkins	NNP	PERSON	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	part	part	NN	O	9	nsubj
4	of	of	IN	O	6	case
5	the	the	DT	O	6	det
6	lesson	lesson	NN	O	3	nmod
7	is	be	VBZ	O	9	cop
8	for	for	IN	O	9	case
9	investors	investor	NNS	O	2	ccomp
10	to	to	TO	O	13	mark
11	be	be	VB	O	13	cop
12	more	more	RBR	O	13	advmod
13	skeptical	skeptical	JJ	O	9	xcomp
14	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	But	but	CC	O	12	cc
2	Mustafa	Mustafa	NNP	PERSON	3	compound
3	Barghouti	Barghouti	NNP	PERSON	12	nsubj
4	,	,	,	O	3	punct
5	a	a	DT	O	6	det
6	member	member	NN	O	3	appos
7	of	of	IN	O	10	case
8	the	the	DT	O	10	det
9	Palestinian	palestinian	JJ	MISC	10	amod
10	parliament	parliament	NN	O	6	nmod
11	,	,	,	O	3	punct
12	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
13	:	:	:	O	12	punct
14	`	`	``	O	12	punct
15	If	if	IN	O	18	mark
16	I	I	PRP	O	18	nsubj
17	am	be	VBP	O	18	cop
18	honest	honest	JJ	O	22	advcl
19	,	,	,	O	22	punct
20	I	I	PRP	O	22	nsubj
21	would	would	MD	O	22	aux
22	say	say	VB	O	12	ccomp
23	his	he	PRP$	O	24	nmod:poss
24	mission	mission	NN	O	27	nsubj
25	was	be	VBD	O	27	cop
26	a	a	DT	O	27	det
27	failure	failure	NN	O	22	ccomp
28	.	.	.	O	12	punct
29	'	'	''	O	12	punct

1	He	he	PRP	O	2	nsubj
2	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
3	he	he	PRP	O	5	nsubjpass
4	is	be	VBZ	O	5	auxpass
5	honored	honor	VBN	O	2	ccomp
6	to	to	TO	O	7	mark
7	find	find	VB	O	5	xcomp
8	himself	himself	PRP	O	10	nsubj
9	a	a	DT	O	10	det
10	member	member	NN	O	7	xcomp
11	of	of	IN	O	15	case
12	Washington	Washington	NNP	LOCATION	15	nmod:poss
13	's	's	POS	O	12	case
14	exclusive	exclusive	JJ	O	15	amod
15	club	club	NN	O	10	nmod
16	of	of	IN	O	17	case
17	100	100	CD	NUMBER	15	nmod
18	,	,	,	O	5	punct
19	after	after	IN	O	20	mark
20	working	work	VBG	O	5	advcl
21	for	for	IN	O	22	case
22	decades	decade	NNS	DURATION	20	nmod
23	in	in	IN	O	25	case
24	support	support	NN	O	25	compound
25	roles	role	NNS	O	22	nmod
26	as	as	IN	O	29	case
27	a	a	DT	O	29	det
28	Kennedy	Kennedy	NNP	PERSON	29	compound
29	aide	aide	NN	O	20	nmod
30	and	and	CC	O	29	cc
31	top	top	JJ	O	34	amod
32	Democratic	Democratic	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	compound
33	Party	Party	NNP	ORGANIZATION	34	compound
34	official	official	NN	O	29	conj
35	.	.	.	O	2	punct

1	Once	once	RB	DATE	2	advmod
2	considered	consider	VBN	O	9	advcl
3	Robin	Robin	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
4	Hood	Hood	NNP	PERSON	5	compound
5	figures	figure	NNS	O	2	dobj
6	,	,	,	O	9	punct
7	the	the	DT	O	8	det
8	Maoists	Maoists	NNPS	MISC	9	nsubj
9	claim	claim	VBP	O	0	ROOT
10	to	to	TO	O	11	mark
11	represent	represent	VB	O	9	xcomp
12	the	the	DT	O	39	det
13	dispossessed	dispossessed	JJ	O	39	amod
14	of	of	IN	O	16	case
15	Indian	indian	JJ	MISC	16	amod
16	society	society	NN	O	13	nmod
17	,	,	,	O	16	punct
18	particularly	particularly	RB	O	22	advmod
19	the	the	DT	O	22	det
20	indigenous	indigenous	JJ	O	22	amod
21	tribal	tribal	JJ	O	22	amod
22	groups	group	NNS	O	16	appos
23	,	,	,	O	16	punct
24	who	who	WP	O	25	nsubj
25	suffer	suffer	VBP	O	16	acl:relcl
26	some	some	DT	O	25	dobj
27	of	of	IN	O	32	case
28	the	the	DT	O	29	det
29	country	country	NN	O	32	nmod:poss
30	's	's	POS	O	29	case
31	highest	highest	JJS	O	32	amod
32	rates	rate	NNS	O	26	nmod
33	of	of	IN	O	34	case
34	poverty	poverty	NN	O	26	nmod
35	,	,	,	O	34	punct
36	illiteracy	illiteracy	NN	O	34	conj
37	and	and	CC	O	34	cc
38	infant	infant	NN	O	34	conj
39	mortality	mortality	NN	O	11	dobj
40	.	.	.	O	9	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	2	det
2	CJI	CJI	NNP	O	3	nsubj
3	said	say	VBD	O	0	ROOT
4	:	:	:	O	3	punct
5	``	``	``	O	3	punct
6	We	we	PRP	O	10	nsubj
7	are	be	VBP	O	10	cop
8	in	in	IN	O	10	case
9	the	the	DT	O	10	det
10	process	process	NN	O	3	ccomp
11	of	of	IN	O	12	mark
12	finding	find	VBG	O	10	acl
13	the	the	DT	O	14	det
14	truth	truth	NN	O	12	dobj
15	behind	behind	IN	O	17	case
16	the	the	DT	O	17	det
17	allegations	allegation	NNS	O	14	nmod
18	by	by	IN	O	20	case
19	an	a	DT	O	20	det
20	inquiry	inquiry	NN	O	12	nmod
21	through	through	IN	O	23	case
22	independent	independent	JJ	O	23	amod
23	channels	channel	NNS	O	12	nmod
24	keeping	keep	VBG	O	23	acl
25	in	in	IN	O	26	case
26	mind	mind	NN	O	24	nmod
27	the	the	DT	O	28	det
28	collector	collector	NN	O	30	nmod:poss
29	's	's	POS	O	28	case
30	report	report	NN	O	26	dep
31	and	and	CC	O	26	cc
32	Justice	Justice	NNP	O	33	compound
33	Dinakaran	Dinakaran	NNP	PERSON	35	nmod:poss
34	's	's	POS	O	33	case
35	version	version	NN	O	26	conj
36	.	.	.	O	3	punct
37	''	''	''	O	3	punct

1	The	the	DT	O	3	det
2	retired	retired	JJ	O	3	amod
3	Fulbright	Fulbright	NNP	O	16	nsubj
4	&	&	CC	O	3	cc
5	Jaworski	Jaworski	NNP	PERSON	6	compound
6	lawyer	lawyer	NN	O	3	conj
7	with	with	IN	O	9	case
8	a	a	DT	O	9	det
9	focus	focus	NN	O	3	nmod
10	on	on	IN	O	14	case
11	utility	utility	NN	O	14	compound
12	and	and	CC	O	11	cc
13	municipal	municipal	JJ	O	11	conj
14	law	law	NN	O	9	nmod
15	has	have	VBZ	O	16	aux
16	raised	raise	VBN	O	0	ROOT
17	almost	almost	RB	O	16	advmod
18	$	$	$	MONEY	19	dep
19	300,000	300,000	CD	MONEY	17	nmod:npmod
20	.	.	.	O	16	punct

1	Jeff	Jeff	NNP	PERSON	2	compound
2	Downing	Downing	NNP	PERSON	10	nsubj
3	,	,	,	O	2	punct
4	a	a	DT	O	5	det
5	lawyer	lawyer	NN	O	2	appos
6	from	from	IN	O	8	case
7	Oak	Oak	NNP	LOCATION	8	compound
8	Forest	Forest	NNP	LOCATION	5	nmod
9	,	,	,	O	2	punct
10	wants	want	VBZ	O	0	ROOT
11	a	a	DT	O	14	det
12	third	third	JJ	ORDINAL	14	amod
13	HPD	hpd	NN	O	14	compound
14	storefront	storefront	NN	O	10	dobj
15	,	,	,	O	10	punct
16	preferably	preferably	RB	O	18	advmod
17	along	along	IN	O	18	case
18	Antoine	Antoine	NNP	PERSON	10	nmod
19	.	.	.	O	10	punct
